The Clover Kingdom.
In this kingdom where magic is everything,
there is one boy who can't use magic.
His name is Asta.
With guts and hard work,
he made it into the Magic Knights,
and he never gave up,
despite how much he got hurt.
He continues to diligently
aim for the top!
Even if you are a peasant,
or even if you're poor...
Anyone in this world can still shine!
He's working hard to prove that,
and to become the Wizard King!
After receiving some time off from Yami,
Asta headed back to his home village of Hage.
On the way, he unexpectedly reunited
with Yuno, who was also heading home.
Once they reached Hage,
they learned that the village
already knew that Asta
was suspected of being a devil's servant.
I saw you in the paper.
Right. About that...
That article is mistaken.
Asta isn't a devil's servant.
He's actually trying to defeat them.
Please believe that.
But no one in Hage Village had
doubted Asta, not even for a second.
On the contrary, they were very proud of him
and Yuno for becoming Magic Knights
and saving the village.
Asta and Yuno got to enjoy
a brief visit back home.
But it's not over yet.
We've only just begun.
In order to protect everyone...
...let's continue moving forward.
The Lion Awakens
Just you watch, Yuno!
I'm gonna get even stronger!
Well, aren't you all riled up
first thing in the morning, Asta!
There are other things to
think about, aren't there?
Try some. You need your nutrients.
Thanks!
It's so good! I can feel the
energy flowing through me!
We need to get even stronger
so we can go up against the
devil with everything we've got!
In that case, here. All of you have
some so you can work even harder.
Thanks, Charmy.
Magna's covered in cake!
You bastard! I have no idea who
the hell you are, but keep it down!
Don't you know this is the hideout
of the Magic Knights Squad
led by Mister Yami, the Black Bu—
I'm pretty sure this has happened before...
I-I knew it! You're...
Captain Mereoleona?!
Mereoleona Vermillion
I see your door is as weak as ever.
So... what brings you here today?
I don't see Yami, but whatever.
All of you who are here
right now, come with me.
No! I have nothing but
bad feelings about this!
But we haven't finished eating our cakes, la!
This seems fun!
I seriously have no idea
what's going on right now!
Where are we supposed to go?
Shut up. You'll see when we get there.
Strong
Magic
Region
Yultim
Volcano
Trail
We see it, all right...
Hey! Where the hell are we?!
Why did I wake up in a crazy place like this?!
This is so exciting, isn't it?!
I'm losing calories just by standing
here and getting hungry, la!
Right... This is the first
visit here for most of you.
This is a strong magic region,
the Yultim Volcano!
Yul...tim?
Lady Mereoleona, since you brought
us here, does that mean...
You'll be training, of course!
Of course...
Leo! And Captain Fuegoleon?!
It's been a while, my rival.
I've heard of your adventures
fighting the elves and the devil.
And I heard you were fighting on the
front lines with the Crimson Lion Kings!
Hey, did you get a little taller?!
Not only did I get taller,
I've grown as a Magic Knight, too!
Hey! Well, I've gotten more muscles, too!
Black Bulls...
Do you have a moment?
Vice Captain of the Crimson Lion Kings
Randall Luftair
I am the Vice Captain of the Crimson
Lion Kings, Randall Luftair.
In the previous battle, the three of
us had our bodies taken over by elves.
We ended up turning against all of you,
our allies. We're deeply sorry.
What are you talking about?
The only one to blame here is
the devil who was manipulating the
whole situation from the shadows.
I hear that the devil in the
Spade Kingdom is an even bigger threat.
We will protect this kingdom as the
proud Magic Knights that we are,
and in order to prove Asta's innocence,
we'll all have to become stronger individually.
Just like last time,
we'll be training with the Crimson Lion
Kings and the others I have invited.
Yes, ma'am!
I wouldn't call this "invited."
We were kidnapped, just like last time.
All right! Let's haul ass to
the hot springs at the top!
Hold it.
Huh? Wha?!
You won't be climbing the volcano this time.
You'll be heading underneath the volcano...
Yultim Volcano Underground Cave
Into the Yultim Underground Cave!
Yultim...
...Underground Cave?
It's what makes this volcano
a strong magic region...
An enormous mana heat
source deep underground.
The rocks deep underground
that are soaked in this mana
become lava due to the heat
and burst onto the surface.
Which means the further you go underground,
the stronger the influence of
the mana heat source becomes.
If your Mana Skin falters,
your bodies will be exposed
to the immense mana
and burn up, reducing you to ashes.
Have no fear. The goal, which is
the deepest part of the cave,
has an even better hot spring!
Well? Doesn't that make you excited?
Hot... spring?
I request that we switch over
to the sweets region where
sweet honey flows instead of lava!
You're not ready for that!
It actually exists?!
Wait. What the hell is Mana Skin?
I dunno.
You Magic Knights essentially
enhance your physical abilities
with your mana to some
degree in order to fight.
Mana Skin is the perfect
state of your basic magic.
Flawlessly don your magic like so,
and your body is constantly
protected by enormous mana.
Wait, you can't expect us to
be able to do that right away!
Then be reduced to ash.
What?!
For those who were brought
here unexpectedly,
I will allow you to use this magic item.
What's this?
It's a magic item that'll help
you use your Mana Skins,
but it's only a supplement.
If you lose control of your magic,
the item's effectiveness will be lost.
Huh?
All right! Let the training begin!
I will overcome this blazing mana with
my flame magic and reach the goal first!
And I'm going to just keep
moving forward to get stronger!
You say that, but what are you even
going to do when you can't use Mana Skin?
That one power of yours takes a lot out
of you and doesn't last for long, right?
If it stops working,
you'll be burnt to a crisp.
Yeah...
Back then, I went into my
black state by using the power
flowing through my sword and into my body,
but I couldn't control it at all.
But now, I have some control over it.
I'm going to concentrate
and control my powers
so that I don't immediately get
sucked in by the powerful magic.
Oh?
He surrounded his body with anti-magic.
All right, this will work!
Well done, my rival!
I'm feeling even more fired up!
Not bad, Asta!
I've got no time to be scared!
I'll figure out this Mana Skin
business in no time!
Ha, so you were scared!
Sh-Shut up! Don't make me kill you!
Nyah, nyah, Scaredy-Cat Magna!
Shut your stupid mouth!
Mana Skin... I should be able to handle
that now by donning my Valkyrie Armor.
It appears you're all prepared.
You are the proud Magic Knights
of the Clover Kingdom.
Get through this trial with burning
desire that surpasses even
the heat of this strong magic region!
Yeah!
I'm gonna get to the goal first!
No, it'll be me!
No, me!
Me!
It'll be me!
Hot spring...
I won't lose, either!
I'm gonna leave you behind if
you dawdle too long, Magna!
Wait up, damn it!
Let us go, too!
Yes!
Sneaky-sneak...
Charmy, where are you going?
Shh! I'm starving, so I have no interest
in going anywhere that has no food.
I'm going to run away, la.
Uh, but...
I won't stop you.
You will endure not only
scorching mana in the cave,
but also unknown creatures that
have adapted to such conditions.
If you have no desire to grow, then flee.
I want to become stronger so I can
fight alongside the other Black Bulls.
So these creatures... Are they delicious?
I assure you that they are.
Hell yeah!
Just you wait, unknown ingredients that
were seasoned by the underground mana!
Wait!
Well... I wonder how many
of them will reach the goal.
It's no fun for them to just
try to get to the hot spring.
There's another reason why
I chose this underground cave
as their training ground.
I'm going to get to the goal first!
There's no room! Let me pass by, Asta!
Hot, hot, hot!
I'm not going to lose!
The deeper we go, the more the
mana underground increases,
which is exhausting us
at an unbelievable rate.
I'm starting to get dizzy from all the heat!
At times like this...
...we just have to shout!
I'm not done yet!
I'm not going to lose, my rival!
Actually, Nero, what the
heck did you come for?
So that I can go into the hot spring.
Jeez, could you be any less motivated?!
Ugh, they're so loud!
They're distracting me and making
me lose control of my magic.
Calm down, calm down...
If I get irritated, I'll lose even more control.
Stay calm, stay calm...
Is that all you've got?
Leo and Asta are far ahead of us!
Let's show them what the
Crimson Lion Kings are truly made of!
Right!
That's the spirit!
The heat from the mana
down here is so intense...
Even with this magic item helping me out,
if I let my guard down for
one second, I'm in trouble.
My bad, Magna.
You little shit... You did
that on purpose, didn't you?!
I'll kill—
I'm gonna kill you, no matter what!
And anyway, is this really a shortcut?!
Isn't the goal deeper underground?!
Don't worry. The strong guy lurking
in this cave should be right up here.
Wait... this isn't a shortcut to the goal?!
We don't have time to fight
anything like that, you dumbass!
How am I supposed to not fight
it when it's emitting
such a powerful aura?
Hi-yah!
Nummies...
It's so hot... My mana is being used
up much faster than I expected.
Charmy, it's dangerous
to stay here much longer!
La! We need to taste the unknown creatures
and replenish our mana right away!
But you haven't been able
to catch a single thing.
Maybe they're not here.
Something's wrong... I sense the
unknown creatures down there.
La! I can feel it! The ingredients
are hiding in fear of something!
Of you, probably.
Look out!
It's so powerful...
Charmy, h-hurry and let go of the net!
I'm not letting this big one get away!
N-Now's not the time for that...
I can't... hold on any longer!
La?
La!
You okay?
That was a close one!
Luck, Magna, thank you.
H-H-H-H...
How dare you?! I just missed out
on eating the nummies in there!
Looks like that spider wanted
to eat you, too, Charmy.
La?
I think it's pretty strong. We came
here because we wanted to fight it, too.
Speak for yourself, dumbass!
Aw, it got away. Too bad.
That's my line!
So that's what the creatures
here were scared of.
Just you wait!
Not yet...
You sound out of breath, my rival.
And you're barely staying on your feet.
I'm nearing my limit...
But my rival is also suffering.
I'm getting to the goal first!
No, it'll be me!
Reinforcement Magic: Leg Strength Boost!
Pardon me!
Wha—
She's so fast!
With the mana in here being this powerful,
it's the worst possible compatibility
with my water magic.
I'm having a harder time getting
through than I thought.
How are our magic levels so different
when we're both royalty?
But I will not lose!
Not yet! Hold up, Noelle!
I can't let this get to me if
I want to be the Wizard King!
Asta!
The moment I first met you...
Listen up, you bastards!
I'm going to pile up merit,
become the Wizard King,
and shut you all up!
Despite that you were
a peasant with no magic,
I felt something in my heart
when you told of us your dreams.
Ever since then, we've fought together,
trained together,
and competed against each
other to reach new heights.
But then, when I tried to become
a member of the Royal Knights
to take down the Eye of the Midnight Sun,
who killed my brother,
I was not chosen.
I will train even harder,
catch up to all of you,
and surpass you!
Leopold...
I will get revenge for Captain Fuegoleon,
no matter what!
With that frustration still in my heart,
I've continued training hard to this day.
I'm going to catch up to you!
We're still not at the goal?
I can't keep this up much longer.
Hold up, Noelle!
I-I'm royalty! I may make others wait,
but I don't wait for anyone!
Wait up!
Swim trunks?!
N-No, it couldn't be! I must be seeing things.
Noelle!
What?!
Stay calm... Calm down and take another look...
Wait up, Noelle!
Let's go swim together!
I'm seeing nothing but the ocean!
G-Get a grip, me!
We're in a cave! A cave! We're not at the beach!
What's wrong?!
No!
What?!
Whoa!
What the heck was that for?!
Hey, Noelle! Where'd you go?!
Honestly... Th-That was his fault
for talking to me out of nowhere.
The mana seems calmer in here.
I wonder why...
Asta?
Was it my imagination?
Asta?!
You okay? What the heck is that monster?!
Crap—
Asta!
Water Creation Magic: Sea Dragon's Roar!
I missed?!
Take this!
Flame Magic: Spiral Flames!
Leopold!
You okay?!
You can stand, can't you, Leo?
Yes.
You never look this happy after
our daily training sessions.
Really?
That bug is a mutant that
recently showed up and has been
eating up all the creatures around here.
I wanted to teach it a lesson,
but I'm sure it's able to sense
those that are stronger than it is.
It never shows itself before me.
So I decided to try to throw you lot in here.
It attacked you, thinking you
were food, just as I planned.
How could you do something like that?!
If you knew that thing was down here,
you should've told us—
Don't be naïve!
The unexpected always happens in battle!
Not to mention, we're going to be
facing a devil from another world!
How do you expect to survive
if you can't even handle this?
True... I didn't picture
this as an actual battle.
I can't argue with that.
Or so I'd like to say...
But it appears that bug isn't a mere mutant.
That thing has man-made mana within it.
Mana it wasn't born with.
And...
That must be how it kept hiding from you.
Elaborate camouflage that
even I couldn't see through...
Must be an ancient curse.
Don't tell me that's...
A dungeon, eh? Things are getting exciting.
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
I'll Surpass You
I'll Surpass You.
Asta! I've made up my mind to catch
up to you and surpass you immediately!
Scenario 1
Scenario 1!
Captain Yami! I can't hold it
any longer! Please come out!
See ya!
What?!
You didn't surpass me! You cut in line!
Scenario 2
Scenario 2!
Let's dig in!
Hey, where's your food?
Ha! I surpassed you in eating!
You just didn't eat!
Scenario 3
And scenario 3!
Actually, I'm just gonna surpass
that and go to scenario 100!
No, 10,000!
You went too far!
A dungeon?!
Just watch, Asta, my rival.
I will conquer it first!
Next time on Black Clover, Page 133:
"The Lion Awakens, Continued."
Page 133
The Lion Awakens, Continued
May my roar resonate through
the depths of the earth!