The Clover Kingdom.
In this kingdom where magic is everything,
there is one boy who can't use magic.
His name is Asta.
With guts and hard work,
he made it into the Magic Knights,
and he never gave up,
despite how much he got hurt.
He continues to diligently aim for the top!
Even if you are a peasant,
or even if you're poor...
Anyone in this world can still shine!
He's working hard to prove that,
and to become the Wizard King!
Asta and some of the other Black Bulls
were gathered up by Mereoleona,
and taken away to train along
with the Crimson Lion Kings.
I'm gonna get to the goal first!
No, it'll be me!
No, me!
Flame Magic: Spiral Flames!
During their training, a new
dungeon appeared before them.
Things are getting exciting.
That was amazing!
Leopold, who sees himself as Asta's rival,
showed great growth as they
conquered the dungeon.
I will learn how to fully use that
spell and become stronger than you!
In that case, I'll become
even stronger than that!
And thus, their training ended.
Or so they thought...
You're late!
She's actually here!
What the heck's going on?!
Take care, Asta.
You've been chosen to deal with an
urgent matter of grave importance.
You should be honored.
Those Who Have Been Gathered
Vermillion Residence
You two, hurry up and take a seat.
Wait, where are we?
The Vermillion residence.
In other words, my home.
Hey, it's Mimosa, Mimosa's bro,
and Captain Fuegoleon.
I see that you've been summoned as well, Asta.
Uh, more like we were dragged here, but...
Ah, Asta. You're as unsightly as ever,
and now, a wanted fugitive.
But I guess I must admit that your recent deeds
may have been at least a little beautiful.
Th-Thanks?
I believe that was my brother's
attempt to compliment you.
So... why are we all here?
I'm not sure, but...
Captain Fuegoleon...
I may be guessing, but this seems quite serious.
Yeah...
Maybe we're receiving special orders
regarding the Spade Kingdom.
Oh, yeah!
Silence!
We are about to hold a very important meeting.
I need you to understand
that the results of this meeting will
affect the very future of our kingdom.
You must make sure you tell no one of this.
This must be a top-secret mission!
Now, let us begin!
Theresa Rapual
The old sister lady?
Um... May I ask who she is?
She's one of the sisters
from the church in Nean...
But why is she here?
This meeting is to celebrate Ms. Theresa's
fifteen years in the sisterhood.
What?!
But wait, you guys just said this will
affect the very future of our kingdom!
Ms. Theresa is currently raising
children, who have a future.
So, as I said, this affects the
very future of our kingdom.
Well, I guess that's true, but...
Why must we not mention this to anyone else?
We're not saying to keep this a complete secret.
We just mean that there's really
no reason to tell others.
Ms. Theresa dislikes flashiness and
things that bring attention to her.
It isn't a secret mission at all!
This is already too flashy and grandiose.
I just want some peace.
So basically, we're just
having a party to celebrate?
Why did you decide to host this, Fuegoleon?
When I was young, Ms. Theresa was in
charge of my sister's and my education
while doing her duties as a Magic Knight.
Oh, I guess you did mention
that before, Granny.
Good grief. If nothing else,
your heads sure have gotten bigger,
Mereo and Fueggy.
Mereo?!
Fueggy?!
After retiring from being our
tutor and a Magic Knight,
today marks fifteen years
since you became a sister.
I also heard that you acted
valiantly during the kidnapping
incident that occurred in Nean.
Granny was super amazing back then!
We will celebrate her greatness and
honor her lifelong achievements today.
We called you lot here to help celebrate.
I finally figured it all out!
In that case, we need to make
this a huge celebration!
Y-Yeah.
Yes.
How beautiful...
I'm not talking about your looks,
but there is beauty residing
in your proud spirit!
I'm finally beginning to
understand that kind of beauty.
But of course, I'm still the most beautiful!
It may be too late, but would you
consider educating my brother, too?
By the way, why isn't Leo here?
This is a party to celebrate someone
really important to his siblings.
Under ordinary circumstances,
we would have summoned him here,
but he requested that he be allowed
further training, which I granted.
Oh, I see.
That boy's got a good head on his shoulders.
You two don't have time to waste
on nonsense like this either, do you?
This celebration is just
for today. Please enjoy it.
Whoa! This all looks super good!
Ms. Theresa, please enjoy.
It could be because I've been away
from the royal capital for so long,
but I really don't care for fancy meals like this.
This is exactly why I thought about declining.
But...
It's a feast!
Wow!
It looks so yummy!
You offered to feed my
little ones, so I couldn't say no.
Marie! And the other kids!
Asta! Thank you for helping us before!
Let's eat together!
Sure!
Wait...
This ki...
Asta! Come on, hurry up!
Huh? Oh, sure.
Come on, line up!
Okay!
Here you go. This is yours, Marie.
Thank you, Asta!
Tch!
What do you think you're doing?
You may have fooled the others,
but did you really think
you could fool me, Gauche?
Shut it, you old hag.
I'm guessing you had some transformation
wizard help you transform into a kid.
I'm pretty sure I remember your
squad having someone like that.
I went to the church because
I wanted to see Marie,
but then I heard there was
a party being held here.
That's why I'm here. You got a
problem with that, you shitty old hag?
I see you're as foul-mouthed as ever.
You're fully aware that you're only
allowed to see Marie once a month.
How desperate are you to see her,
you sister-obsessed punk?
This doesn't count as my one time a month if
I'm just sneaking a peek, you wicked old hag.
Sorry to interrupt the fun, but...
What?! The party's already over?
No, that's not it.
Uh, then what is it?
I need you all to do a party trick
that will delight Ms. Theresa!
Wha?
Now, show us your party tricks!
He wants us to do... party tricks?
He wants me to do a party trick?!
What do tricks have to do with parties?!
Fueggy's always been
a bit on the awkward side,
so he doesn't know how else to phrase things.
Though I'd like to ask all of you
to entertain the children, too.
So we just gotta entertain everyone?
Let's do this.
Leave this to me. My beauty always
quenches the masses' thirst for entertainment.
In your case, my dear brother, your whole
existence is like a party trick,
so you don't have to change a thing.
You flatter me, my dear sister.
Really? A party trick out of nowhere?
I absolutely did not.
At times like this, you mother, Lady Acier,
would've been the first to act.
At any banquet, she would entertain
us all with a brilliant party trick.
I'll do it!
I'm very excited to see
your party trick, Noelle!
You've got this, Noelle!
I'll show you how royalty does a party trick!
There!
S-Something like this?
I guess that should do the trick.
Wow!
Do more!
I shall go next.
They're so lame. I could
entertain Marie so much better.
You shut your mouth.
Though, if you ask me, the fact that
you've disguised yourself as a child
is probably the most hilarious thing here.
You never shut up, do you, old hag?
Oh, so that's what a party trick is!
All right, I've got this!
Noelle! Throw me two plates!
Huh? Sure...
Hup!
I'm not done yet!
Wow!
Brilliant, Asta!
He's getting the biggest reaction.
Not bad, I guess.
What a bizarre party trick. I almost
feel beauty in how unsightly it is.
Okay, guys! Here comes the next one! Up they go!
That's so cool!
Well done, all of you. I thank you.
You're the best!
So, what party trick are you
going to do for me, Fueggy?
It appears that I cannot get
away with doing nothing.
All right, I'll have to use the ace up my sleeve.
Behold!
See these eggs?
What the heck is Captain Fuegoleon doing?
Does he actually think he's boiling them?
There.
Behold!
A hard-boiled egg, a soft-boiled egg,
and a jammy soft-boiled egg!
By carefully controlling my mana,
I can prepare eggs in three
different ways at once!
The jammy soft-boiled egg is
the most difficult to execute.
To give the yolk a soft firmness while
keeping the white in a gelatinous state,
one must control the heat in the exact—
Boring.
What?
You're far too serious.
You have no talent for this sort of thing at all.
Sister...
Just watch. I'll show you how it's done.
One must have the right enthusiasm
when pulling off a party trick.
This is how it's done!
Well? Are you not entertained?
Sister!
That lady's mean!
Why in the world are you crying?
I see you two are as clueless as ever.
I apologize for this shameful display.
But I can see that you haven't changed.
Nothing has changed at all
since I looked after you two.
What were they like back then?
Come on, Asta...
Well, they were very capable, but still
a handful. That's how I'd describe them.
I'm going to be your tutor starting today.
I look forward to it.
Ms. Theresa! I must become stronger!
So please, train me harder!
Don't be ridiculous, Fueggy.
No one can become strong overnight.
Fueggy seemed unsatisfied with my training
and would always sneak around,
training more on his own.
Training too much when you're too young
affects your mana and your growth,
so I struggled to get him to hold back.
As for Mereo, she was always a wild child.
She never listened to me
anyway, so I let her be,
and she became overpowered on her own.
I was their tutor for about ten years,
until Fueggy was fifteen
and Mereo was seventeen.
I do apologize for being such an
unruly student, Ms. Theresa.
Because you let me have my freedom back then,
I was able to become strong without
being stuck in constraints.
I'm very grateful to you, Ms. Theresa.
I just did my job as your tutor.
You're amazing, Granny,
but I guess they've been amazing
ever since they were kids, too!
That's not true.
Fueggy couldn't control his mana,
so he'd always set things on fire.
What?!
I remember that. And every time you
started a fire, you'd cry like a baby.
And when you were about eight, Mereo,
you got too worked up and set
your own clothes on fire.
I do believe I recall that happening.
I do remember that, Sister.
When you're born with overwhelming mana,
that's bound to happen when
you're still children.
But as you grow, eventually,
you naturally become able to control it.
I see! So compared to others,
I was just a late bloomer.
I see! So it's like getting
over wetting the bed!
Once you're older than ten, it mostly
calms down, but there are those kids
who still wet the bed at,
like, thirteen or fourteen.
Yes, exactly. It's similar to that.
Yeah! So just like wetting the bed!
How dare you, Stupidsta?!
Ow!
Why the heck did I just get slapped?!
Well, all kids have a couple of
embarrassing memories like that.
Speaking of embarrassing memories,
I happen to remember Fuegoleon
breaking a vase that was a
precious family heirloom.
I actually took the blame for it
so he wouldn't get in trouble.
I beg your pardon, dear sister,
but it was you who actually broke
the vase and blamed it on me.
I know it happened a long time ago,
but I cannot allow you to forget it.
Oho, so that's how you think you remember it.
It's not how I remember it.
It is the simple truth.
When you took Father's precious magic
item without permission and lost it,
you also blamed that on me, didn't you, Sister?
Enough of your rubbish. Have you
forgotten that I'd let you off the hook
every single time you took a
portion from my dinner plate?
That is also wrong.
You were actually constantly
taking a portion from
my dinner plate without permission.
You may be my sister, but I will not
allow for any more of these falsities.
Falsities? Watch your mouth, Fuegoleon.
I would also like you to take back what you said.
It looks like I'm going to have to
physically teach you a lesson again.
I would like to see you try.
This is really bad!
What's new about siblings fighting?
Just let them have at it.
Though... You there, missy.
Huh? Me?
I don't want these kids to get hurt,
so could you protect them with your magic?
A-All right.
Take a good, long look, kids.
Don't end up like them.
Okay!
It's not uncommon for kids to
remember things differently.
I, too, protected Mimosa quite
often when we were children,
but it appears as though my
dear sister has forgotten!
What? When did you ever protect me?
For example, the time I beautified
a room after Mimosa sullied it.
Oh, really?
I must ask you to stop!
Especially in front of Asta!
Not to mention, every time you
claimed to be practicing magic
while littering flower petals all over the
house, it was I who cleaned them all up!
I do believe that's just a matter of opinion.
Could you please stop playing dumb?!
I am beautiful, and therefore,
I do not like conflict.
However, I shall not allow
you to slander my good name.
I am tired of your excuses, Brother,
so I shall gladly shut your mouth for you.
I'm not sure I've ever seen Mimosa like this.
I guess strange things do happen.
I'm done holding back.
Oh? Looks like you'll at least
be able to entertain me.
Hey, you jackasses!
You're putting Marie in danger!
Whoa! Gauche?!
What are you doing here?
I won't let any of you get
a chance to hurt Marie!
Mind your own business! I'm in the middle
of disciplining my idiot of a brother!
This is getting way out of hand, you two!
That's enough!
Whoa...
She completely stopped all
the fights in an instant!
Sit!
Honestly, all siblings fight,
but there are limits!
I'm terribly sorry that I lost my
composure with you, Brother.
Nay, I just failed to be beautiful.
As for you two, it seems like
you need a stern talking-to.
You're both over thirty!
Stop fighting hard enough to
bring your own house down!
We're terribly sorry.
Hey, hang on a damn second, you old hag.
Why the hell do you look so smug?
Oh, I was wondering where you went.
You only got in trouble
because you came here when you're
not supposed to, Big Brother!
Marie!
I'm glad your sister is so much
more intelligent than you.
Good work, you two.
Thank you for looking out for the children.
N-No problem, ma'am.
Well, it's about time we headed home.
Ms. Theresa! Are you heading home already?
I've had enough of you two for today.
I apologize again for our rudeness.
So please, allow us to do
something nice for you again.
This only happened because you tried to
do something you're not accustomed to.
It's true that we're inexperienced, but...
But I'll gladly accept your feelings, you two.
How about...
you celebrate my hundred years
of continued service in about 85 years?
The Crimson She-Leopard is so damn cool!
I'm pretty sure she could
take down a devil on her own.
That was so much fun!
I haven't lived all these years as an
old hag with nothing to show for it.
Another mixer?
What in the world is Finral thinking?
Next time on Black Clover, Page 135:
"The One Who Has My Heart, My Mind, and Soul."
Page 135
The One Who Has My Heart, My Mind, and Soul
Ugh, Stupidsta. The one who
has my heart? I-I'm royalty!