The Clover Kingdom.
In this kingdom where magic is everything,
there is one boy who can't use magic.
His name is Asta.
With guts and hard work,
he made it into the Magic Knights,
and he never gave up,
despite how much he got hurt.
He continues to diligently aim for the top!
Even if you are a peasant,
or even if you're poor...
Anyone in this world can still shine!
He's working hard to prove that,
and to become the Wizard King!
To defeat the devil Megicula,
who inhabits the Spade Kingdom,
Asta and the others have been training hard.
Sea Dragon's Roar!
Spiral Flames!
The Queen of the Heart Kingdom, Loropechika,
who had been cursed by Megicula,
gave them six months.
In that span of time, Asta and the
others must surpass their limits.
I'm so beat!
And hungry...
Well done on your training, Asta.
Finral?
I-Is something wrong?
Well, you see...
I'm actually cursed, too!
What?!
You're not actually cursed.
You just have an incurable
case of girl-craziness.
Noelle! You're as beautiful as ever tod— er...
That's exactly the part you need to fix, Finral!
See?
That! That! That! That!
You're right.
Y-Y-You've got it all wrong!
Langris told me...
You're cursed!
What?!
You're a hopeless playboy who hits
on any woman in your path!
Playboy
P-Playboy?
All that running away and trying
to act cool made you a bigger
failure than you already were!
Failure
Failure?
And once you pick up bad habits,
they won't be easy to break!
Bad Habits
Bad habits?
How could someone like you with so
many faults make Miss Finnes happy?!
See?
I already have my heart set on someone.
I can't let this curse plague me forever.
Otherwise, I won't be able to make
Miss Finnes happy, just like Langris said.
Isn't that the person Captain Yami mentioned?
I never thought Finral could
be so serious about someone.
Asta, please.
I need to defeat this curse,
so join me in training to
make my heart stronger!
Finral...
Ow!
Heck yeah, I will!
Let's beat this curse out of you
so you can be the man she deserves!
Asta...
Training to make his heart stronger?
The Dreavy Hinker
Cheers!
Of course it's a damn mixer!
The One Who Has My Heart,
My Mind, and Soul
I had no idea! Apparently mixers
make your heart stronger!
I really hope I get to fight this time!
Rebecca Scarlet
To think that Asta would invite me to
a mixer... I wonder what brought this on.
I'm not going to complain
about the chance, though!
Karen Lapis
When the heck did Rebecca get so
friendly with the Magic Knights?
I just want to get married already.
I don't even care who it's with.
Eliza Zakkeroni
I have no interest in real men.
I only showed up because I was invited.
I just want to go back home
and read the rest of my novel.
It'd be rude if I didn't try
to sweet-talk these women
on this battlefield known as a "mixer."
Therefore, it's the perfect training for me.
I will do my absolute best
to overcome this curse.
Training? Please. I almost
changed my mind about him.
It's a good thing I came
along because I was worried.
But wait, what am I even worried about?!
Asta, you've got something on your face.
Wh-What's going on over there?!
Wait, stop! You're going to bring our
shop down in more ways than one!
Silence, you puny insect.
Why did I bother hiring you again?
A-Anyway, break anything else
in here, and you're fired!
Nero! Why are you here?
Just because.
Just because?
I can't have you underestimating
the work of a waitress—
Sh-She's actually really cute!
If Asta sees Nero looking this cute,
he might end up f-f-f-f-f-f-fa...
Noelle?
I-I'm going to go check out Asta's table.
You take care of the other ones.
Wh-Why am I trying to keep Nero and Asta apart?
It doesn't matter to me one bit
who Asta falls in love with!
Hey there, missy!
Get me another beer, will ya?
Fetch it yourself, you insect.
Hey, you're the girl from before!
Here you are, sir.
A-An angel...
Hey, what are you doing? It's your
turn to introduce yourself, Finral!
Oh, I just came here to eat today.
What?!
Honestly... I just wanted
to enjoy some quiet time,
but you two had to drag me out here.
Say what?!
Yikes... There's always
at least one clueless guy
who thinks this is the cool thing to do.
I'm pretty sure he was the
gaudiest one at our last mixer.
B-But since we're all enjoying a meal together,
I'd love to hear about you
being a Magic Knight, Finral—
Yeah... that's not my thing.
What's not your thing?!
This hurts so bad!
A girl is actually interested,
and having to ignore her is just torture!
But this is all part of my training,
training, training!
Hurgh!
M-My right hand is desperately trying to give
her some flowers like I usually would.
Calm yourself, right hand!
Curses! It's just in my very
nature to try to hit on girls!
What is this guy trying to do?
I-I see! Finral's doing his absolute
best to battle his curse right now!
I wonder when we're gonna start fighting.
Looks like things might be okay after all.
My bad! Sorry I'm late, bah-ha!
I've been super busy lately. I mean,
this kingdom was in peril just the other day!
I can't really talk about it since
it's top secret, bah-hanestly.
But I'm the one who saved everyone.
< Lies >
I mean, I'm the one who fixed all
the Magic Knights that went crazy.
< Lies >
It's only a matter of time until
they make me a captain, bah-ha!
Bah-ha! It's such a pain, but it's my job.
It appears the king has
taken quite a liking to me.
< This is true >
Whoops. I just said it was top secret,
but I think I might've said too much.
And you were reading a dirty
magazine again during all that,
though I can't say much more. Bah-ha!
You clearly just told her.
A mysterious guy is always more charming.
I see they're putting on their
hellish display of a mixer again.
Oh, of course! Sorry, it just slipped!
Um... What was his name again?
According to the guys who
went to the Heart Kingdom,
apparently there's some secret
behind my bronze magic.
Good grief! It looks like I'm the
only guy who can save the world.
I'm starting to scare even myself, bah-ha-ha!
Oh, right. His name's Bah-ha-ha.
You there! Bring us some
more drinks, bah-hay-bee!
But I was really shocked when I
read that article about you, Asta.
I figured it was some kind of mistake, but...
Well, it wasn't totally a mistake.
They are planning to execute me.
E-Execute you?!
Oh, it's not a huge deal, though.
So don't worry about it, Rebecca.
Hey, so you came to this mixer
to get stronger, too, right?
Wanna fight me?
Huh? Wh-What's he talking about?
Is "fight" some kind of code word?
I-I think we should get to
know each other better first.
Huh?
I wanna have some fun
conversations with girls, too!
No, no, no, what are you saying, Finral?!
The fact that I haven't tried
to pick up a girl once yet
makes this training a huge success!
Then again, I do feel bad for
the girls who actually showed up.
I'll need to explain everything
and apologize later.
It's you...
Huh?
My ideal partner actually exists in real life!
Wh-What?!
Take these to table 3—
W-Wait, you gonna be okay?
That other one never works,
but this girl has what it takes!
Here you are.
Isn't he from the Golden Dawn?
Thank you very much.
What is he doing here?
U-Um...
Girls from the Blue Rose Knights?
Thank you for wait—
The Captain of the Blue Rose Knights...
And the Captain of the Black Bulls?
Does this have to do with the
investigation of the devils?
I appreciate my knights holding
this dinner party for me, but...
This is great. It's even better knowing
the Blue Rose Knights are paying for it.
You can say that again!
Anyway, I wonder where Asta went!
I was totally gonna invite him.
Did they really just come here to eat?
I heard that this was supposed
to be a dinner party,
but seeing how we're lined up, and seeing
Captain Charlotte all dressed up...
This is totally a mixer, isn't it?
Let's have a blast today.
P-Please take it easy on me.
I want Sis to be happy, but I don't
want a guy stealing Sis away from me!
What the heck am I supposed to do?!
You're gonna get a stomachache
if you eat that fast.
Mind your own business, Funglasquent!
Again, stop trying to abbreviate
"Funny Glasses Delinquent," you giant woman!
I'm actually worried about you here.
You have no idea how I feel!
Uh, what?
This calls for an eating contest, Glasquent!
B-Bring it on, Giant Woman!
Doesn't this dress show too much skin?
No, I need to believe in Puli's advice.
Member of the Blue Rose Knights and a
4th Class Junior Magic Knight, Puli Angel.
She actually has another side
to her personality.
Countless Magic Knights have gone
to her for relationship advice.
Puli was acting as a Cupid, or rather,
an angel of love, just as her name suggests,
and saving poor lambs lost
in their quest to find love.
You're more beautiful today
than ever, Captain Charlotte.
Captain Yami doesn't stand a chance
against how sexy you look right now.
My knights are working so hard to support me.
I need to do everything I can.
Hey, Prickly Queen.
You look like you must be
really cold in that dress.
I don't want to hear that from a man who
wears nothing but underwear and a robe!
This isn't underwear!
These are my dress clothes!
I know Yami is like this, so I'm embarrassed
that I ever expected anything more!
I had heard how dense he was,
but this is really bad.
We need to hold an emergency meeting.
I'm sorry that I'm such a
spineless captain, Puli.
No, no! We've only just begun!
Captain Charlotte!
You've got this!
When did you...
Looks like the Black Bulls' captain
prefers the prim and proper type.
We'll fix you up in no time.
N-No! What I'm wearing now is fine.
It's not! You need to be more aggressive
in making yourself appealing!
A-Appealing?
First, you're going to show him you can be
considerate by getting some food for him!
When a huge plate of food arrives,
immediately get some for him and serve him.
That's the kind of kindness
that'll grab his heart!
What's important here is your desire
to do something for the one you love.
I-I see...
Next, a good listener is always attractive.
Isn't it great to have someone
listen to you talk about yourself?
That's why you let them keep
talking until they're satisfied.
Your responses can be whatever, really.
"Oh, really? I had no idea! Wow!"
Is that how this works? I had no idea.
And this is the most important thing!
The most important technique!
T-Tell me!
It's to nonchalantly touch him.
T...Touch... him?
Nope, nope, nope, nope! Absolutely not!
Listen to me, Captain.
Serving his food and listening to him
is just 10% of how to get a man.
The other 90% relies on touching them.
That's a lot relying on touch!
It's no use... There's no way I could...
You can do this, Captain!
Are you going to let your rival beat you?!
I...
The Blue Rose Knights are with you, Captain.
Thank you so much, everyone.
I hear you loud and clear.
I'm going to touch Yami!
Master Finral, you're so cool and apathetic.
You're just like the Magic Knight Fiorel
from the novel I'm reading.
He's the ultimate Magic
Knight who can use light,
dark, flame, wind, water,
and earth magic, and...
That's way too many attributes!
What kind of novel is that?!
So, um... Are you a strong fighter, Luck?
I can show you personally.
O-Oh, my. Isn't he being a bit forward?
Wow, the Heart Kingdom
sounds really beautiful.
I'd love to go see it.
Sure! I'll take you there once
everything's taken care of.
We'll even take your siblings!
I seriously can't let my
guard down around that girl!
I really need to just fire her now.
Noelle?
I-I really only have friends
in the Black Bulls,
so it'd make me really happy if we could
get to know each other, Miss Puli.
Oh, I really love to make dolls,
so I hope you don't mind if
I make one of you, too.
Wow, I'd be honored! I guess I should
give you my measurements, then!
U-Um, I—
I've got Coach Charmy on my side!
Like hell I'm going to lose!
Suddenly touching Yami
is far too difficult for me.
F-First, I should try to get him some food.
Here. Eat up.
Oh, thank you.
I was supposed to get him some food,
but he beat me to the punch!
You sure did take your sweet
time powdering your nose.
Bet you're starving now
that you've let it all out.
That's not what happened! I was talking
with my squad members, and it took a while!
Ah... Yeah, I've been seeing your
squad members everywhere around here.
You knew? Wait, of course you knew.
I'm sure they tagged along
because they were worried...
Because you sure can't hold your liquor.
That's not— er, I guess
you're not totally wrong...
Even when they're not on missions,
my squad members try to support me.
They're also the ones who planned
this dinner party tonight.
I only ever think about fighting
and forget about everything else...
So I end up relying on them.
Wait, I'm supposed to listen,
not keep blabbering on!
That's fine. As long as you're
figuring out how to rely on others.
Well, look at me. Whenever I shi—
I mean, powder my nose, I get my
minion to use his spatial magic.
Y-You should do that on your own!
You know, that meat there... It's great
with a bit of pepper sprinkled on it.
Oh?
Our hands just nonchalantly touched...
Yami's hand j-just...
Captain?!
Sis?!
Did you really have to act like you
got touched by the biggest germ ever?
That hurts, man.
I don't think that's what just happened here.
I want you to know how amazing
Fiorel is, Master Finral!
Why don't we have a reading party?
In my room, you know, alone together.
No, that's okay. I'm not
interested in that kind of thing.
Why, of all times, did a girl who might
actually like me show up at this mixer?!
Don't you dare touch her, Finral!
Once you touch her, you're finished!
You're going to end up sweet-talking her!
Resist, Finral! Resist! Resist!
Aw, I'm jealous. Looks like Finral's
already fighting something.
We should fight, too!
Like, right here and now!
Right here and now?!
D-Do I look like such a floozy to you?
Resist, resist, resist, resist, resist, resist,
resist, resist, resist, resist, resist, resist,
resist, Finral!
Finral seems to be in a lot of pain.
Captain Charlotte?!
A beautiful lady's in trouble!
Ah, Captain Charlotte.
You're more beautiful than ev—
I know I just saved you,
but I didn't have a single
ulterior motive in mind!
Because my heart already
belongs to someone else!
Finral!
What?!
Looks like everybody's having fun down here.
How long do you plan on holding me?
I knew it. My ideal gentleman
just doesn't exist in real life.
After dealing with how aggressive
you are, I realized something.
I was ready to marry anyone,
but I was clearly rushing into things.
Goodbye.
Sheesh... I came to check on
him since he said he'd figured out
how to train to get over his curse,
but it was apparently all a farce.
I'm sorry for wasting your time, Miss Finnes.
No, thank you for bringing me here, Langris.
It appears Finral does fancy the ladies,
but I believe that's just
another part of his kindness.
That's not true. He's just a
good-for-nothing, girl-crazy loser.
Let's head home.
So you two were here, too, huh?
Wh-What a coincidence...
A coincidence.
Yeah, of course it's a coincidence.
You should be a little more honest with him.
Asta is insanely dense.
H-Huh? Wha?! Th-There's nothing
that I want to say to Stupidsta!
I'm sorry, Asta. After I dragged
you here to help me with my training,
I just keep striking out.
I'll never be able to face Miss Finnes like this.
That's not true, Finral!
Your training's just begun!
Asta...
Man, that sure was a piece of work.
So what do you think about guys
like Finral, Prickly Queen?
No man could possibly move my heart.
Because someone has already claimed it.
Yeah, I know.
Huh?!
You always did say that
your work was your partner.
Hngh...
You okay there?
It looks like you still need the angel's help.
H-He's so close!
Well, let's both do our
best these next six months.
Yes.
Asta just keeps getting braver,
and I seem to have more rivals,
but I'm not going to give up just yet!
Next time on Black Clover,
Page 136: "A Black Deep-Sea Story."
Page 136
A Black Deep-Sea Story
Kahono? Wait, another rival?!