The Clover Kingdom.
In this kingdom where magic is everything,
there is one boy who can't use magic.
His name is Asta.
With guts and hard work,
he made it into the Magic Knights,
and he never gave up,
despite how much he got hurt.
He continues to diligently aim for the top!
Even if you are a peasant,
or even if you're poor...
Anyone in this world can still shine!
He's working hard to prove that,
and to become the Wizard King!
In order to defeat Megicula, the devil
who inhabits the Spade Kingdom,
the Magic Knights have been training hard.
Meanwhile, deep within the sea,
another problem was arising.
Kiato! Kahono! You two make a run for it.
But...
Go ask the Magic Knights for help.
What? But we've gotten this far!
Father!
Dad!
Let's fall back for now, Kahono!
Okay.
A Black Deep-Sea Story
Raquey is hot all year round due to
the strong mana that surrounds it,
making it a popular resort location.
It's also an excellent training ground
for those who use water magic.
If I can only maintain this force...
It's not enough to just be able to split them.
I need to make sure there's
more mana in both of them.
A song? Or is that crying?
I'm not sure why, but it
feels sort of... nostalgic.
Wait, why did I just see my mother?
Black Bulls, fight!
Push harder!
Harder! Even harder!
Fight... Fight...
I'll get you this time!
You out of steam already?
Well, I mean... It's not like
I usually run this much.
And what's the point of
training like this, anyway?
You know how much Mr. Yami and Asta
did in that battle with the elves.
The stronger your body is,
the stronger your magic will be.
That's right, Finral! If you get as buff as
Captain Yami, you'll be unstoppable!
Isn't that hurdle a bit high?
We should all get super buff, and then
you should all try to fight me!
All right! We need to be
even louder this time!
Whoa, there!
Ow...
Tch. Damn, I missed one.
Zora, you bastard! What the hell was that for?!
Well, I specialize in traps, so I'm
training with traps, you moron.
Train together, my ass.
I didn't join the squad so I could
be all buddy-buddy with you guys.
What'd you say?!
Luck, you bastard!
Are you trying to bury us?!
Sure am!
Here you go!
Ugh. They're all so noisy.
I-I can't hide my face while doing this pose!
I-I'm so embarrassed!
I've been eating so much of Charmy's
cooking that my weight's not going back down.
Gonna lose weight, gonna lose weight,
gonna lose weight, gonna lose weight...
In order to bulk up, you need
to stress your muscles.
It's said that it's effective when
weight training to do three sets,
and it's important to monitor your
protein amounts and timing—
Who knew that the deltoids and trapezius
were connected this way?
I'm going to learn even more
about human anatomy, and create
an even more accurate Marie doll.
By the way, Gordon,
I thought you mentioned that you
don't handle sunlight very well.
Were you able to get over that?
Yeah, I'm fine now.
It's all thanks to this sunblock.
You can try some if you'd like.
Ah, thank you.
You need to be meticulous
when dealing with UV rays.
Here you go.
That's cold! What the hell
do you think you're doing?!
Huh?! Uh... What?!
Hey... Here... you... go.
Drinking first thing in
the morning's not so bad.
Here you go.
So aren't you gonna train
like the rest of them?
You're just gonna ignore me?
Guys! Food's ready!
Thanks for the meal!
Man, that was great!
It's that sound again.
Noelle?
I think I heard it for the first
time somewhere around here.
Hey!
Asta...
Is something wrong?
Do you hear that strange sound?
Sound?
Huh?
Kahono!
Kiato!
What are you doing here?
Kahono
I could ask you the same thing,
but this is great.
We were just about to go find you.
Kiato
The sea goddess is as beautiful as ever.
Did something happen at
the Underwater Temple?
Oh, right. We wanted to ask you guys for help.
Please come with us.
Underwater Temple
They were attacked by a monster?!
It was probably a guardian of the sea.
They've been around since time immemorial,
and are said to be the sea god's servants.
But why would a creature like that attack
people from the Underwater Temple?
Gifso
Something has disturbed the
underwater mana these past few days.
Some of the creatures around
here have become violent.
I decided to dig into this a
little further, then I saw it...
I couldn't see it clearly because
of the disturbance in the mana,
but south of the Underwater Temple,
there is a place called the Void of No Return.
That's where I saw the guardian
of the sea letting its rage
overtake it, going berserk.
I'm sure the disturbance in the mana
here is due to the guardian's rage.
The shrine mages tried to
quell the guardian's rage
with their song and dance, but...
They all got hurt trying to defend us.
Kahono...
What I'd like to ask from you
is to protect Kiato and Kahono.
Please get them to the Void of No Return safely.
Why the hell are you asking us, though?
We're pretty busy with our training, you know.
You were just drinking booze, Yami!
I beg of you!
I ask this knowing how
powerful the Black Bulls are!
You're among the few
Magic Knights who can reach this
Underwater Temple safely
despite being land dwellers.
Because of the sea goddess's protection.
This may sound harsh,
but you got any proof that
this song and dance can calm
down that guardian of yours?
Well...
We're not protecting this
kingdom as volunteers.
I can't just loan out some of my squad
members when your resolve's that weak.
So basically, you just need to
know there's a chance, right?
Huh?
Noelle?
The disturbance in the mana that's
affecting this whole underwater area...
Maybe a devil's behind this, too.
It's the Magic Knights' job to protect people.
I'll get those two there safely, no matter what.
Noelle...
Sea Goddess...
We...
We'll definitely quell the guardian's rage!
We've sung and danced solely for the sea god!
We'll make sure the guardian
hears our prayers, too!
I guess I'll acknowledge your resolve.
So, what's this chance you mentioned?
I... have an idea.
It's right over there, Noelle.
The Void of No Return.
Just as the name suggests,
it's said that any creature that
wanders in there can never return.
I thought the stories about
the guardian of the sea
and the Void of No Return were
just fairy tales when I was a kid.
H-How deep does that thing go?
So, what's your plan?
I'm going to make the Sea Dragon's Cradle
smaller and more powerful.
That's going to limit who
I can take with me, though.
Which means other than you, Kahono, and Kiato,
we need one more—
Me, me! Me, me, me, me, me!
Me! I'll go!
Let's hurry up and kill that guardian!
I wonder how strong it is.
I can't wait to find out!
Let's just finish off the stupid thing so
I can work ou... I mean, so I can go see Marie.
How can you say something
like that right now?!
Don't worry! Life is an endless cycle!
To taste noms that have been
aged since time immemorial...
Yeah, you guys aren't going.
What?!
Tch!
And you're not going, either.
What?!
But why?! Is it because I can't swim?!
Oh, right. No way in hell you're going, then.
Crap!
How stupid can you be?
Finral.
You go.
Huh?
If things get dangerous, get everyone back
here safe, even if it costs your life.
Got it?
Yes, sir!
Oh, and Noelle.
You decided to do this, so make sure
you see it all the way through.
Yes, sir!
Such violent mana!
If I let my guard down for
even a second, we're finished.
Look!
What the heck are those guys?!
I don't know. We've never
seen them before, either.
Kahono!
Leave it to me!
Song Magic: Mother Lullaby!
It could be that the
powerful mana in the area
caused the fish here to turn into monsters.
Is that even...
There are so many of them!
There's no end to them.
We'll just have to keep going.
Noelle!
Leave this to us.
Song Magic: Destructive Beat!
Wait! Kahono! Kiato!
Big Brother!
Got it!
Combo Spell: Sea God's Descent!
There are too many of them!
Noelle...
What am I even doing? I'm supposed
to protect Kahono and Kiato,
and yet I'm just watching
while they do all the fighting.
Noelle, run!
Wh-What are you talking about?
If I leave, you're going to
be thrown into the ocean!
Don't worry. I promise to take those
two and meet back with you safely.
But how...
Well, our captain did say to bring everyone
back even if it costs my life.
And I'm not so much of a failure
that I'd leave a girl behind
in such a dangerous place.
So go on! Quickly!
Finral...
Noelle!
Kahono!
Everyone...
I can't just...
That's right. If I let this stop me,
I'll never be able to defeat
the devil and avenge my mother!
The Spirit Guardians borrow some power
from natural mana to use powerful magic,
but they still cannot defeat devils.
Natural mana...
If I can somehow get all this chaotic
underwater mana on my side...
Please... lend me your strength!
What?
This is...
Huh?
It's so powerful!
It requires so much magic control
just to protect all of us, let alone this...
This is amazing! I always knew
you were amazing, Noelle!
Sorry for putting you in danger like that.
Now, we're heading right to
the guardian of the sea!
Wh-What's that?
That's a kraken!
The kraken is the protector of the sea.
It protects all the creatures within the sea.
So right now, it's protecting the guardian?
Ooh, a squid leg!
Not bad, Finral!
Here it comes!
This ink isn't just to obstruct our vision.
It's disturbing the mana
around us. At this rate...
Water Creation Magic:
Valkyrie Armor!
Noelle!
Sorry, but I need you to take a little nap.
Now's our chance!
Right!
Ruins?
I had no idea there was a place like
this at the bottom of that hole.
I wonder if people used to live down here, too.
Is that... the guardian?
Such powerful mana...
It's as though it's just unleashing pure rage.
Are we being threatened?
I see. The guardian was
uneasy because of its baby.
And the creatures of the sea were
just trying to protect the
guardian and its baby.
This is...
So that sound I've been
hearing was your lullaby.
Wait! Was that...
Thank you, Sea Godde—
A-Are you hurt?
Huh?
No, I'm fine. It's nothing.
Maybe my mother came here once, too.
Though I'm sure I took much
longer and was far clumsier.
Even so, I made it here.
I'm growing, too.
Thank you all so much!
But are you sure this is
all the thanks you need?
Gramps was super excited about holding a feast.
This is the best, la!
F-Feast?
Kahono, Kiato! Tell Gramps hi for me.
Sure!
Come visit again once
things have calmed down.
Then I'll give the sea goddess
the best welcome ev—
Let's go on another double
date, Asta and Noelle!
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wha...
Sure thing!
H-H-H-How could you agree to that?!
Kahono's so forward. I love it!
Damn it, no! I have Miss Finnes!
Good work.
Yami...
Come to think of it, it was also here
that a good-for-nothing like you
decided to willingly join a
battle for the first time.
Yeah, I guess that also happened.
Do you remember what I told you when
you were still a good-for-nothing?
You've probably got your own
way of fighting, right?
Yes. And I've already found it.
Now, I'm working hard toward my
next goal... or at least, I'm trying.
I see.
That's great and all, but...
Yes?
You totally brought a squid leg over here
with your spatial magic, didn't you?!
I-It was a spur-of-the-moment thing! I'm sorry!
I don't want to hear your lame excuses.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Welcome... back... everyone!
Thanks, Henry!
Right. Guess it's chow time.
I'm starving!
What are you making for us?
We'll start simple with a seafood barbecue
and enjoy its natural yumminess!
Plenty of protein!
A gift for Marie!
I want to eat squid.
A squid almost finished... I mean,
I'm done with squid for now.
Just watch, Mother.
I'm going to become even stronger.
Noelle! Asta! Let's continue to do our best!
I'm going to become an idol! Just you watch!
Next time on Black Clover, Page 137:
Page 137
Charmy's Century of Hunger, Gordon's Millennium of Loneliness
"Charmy's Century of Hunger,
Gordon's Millennium of Loneliness."
I hope you'll cheer me on!