The Clover Kingdom.
In this kingdom where magic is everything,
there is one boy who can't use magic.
His name is Asta.
With guts and hard work,
he made it into the Magic Knights,
and he never gave up,
despite how much he got hurt.
He continues to diligently aim for the top!
Even if you are a peasant,
or even if you're poor...
Anyone in this world can still shine!
He's working hard to prove that,
and to become the Wizard King!
The Black Bulls visited
Raquey to do some training.
Asta and Noelle reunited with
Kahono and Kiato there,
but under the sea, trouble was brewing.
An underwater creature they called
the guardian was wreaking havoc,
causing trouble even for the Underwater Temple.
In order to quell the guardian, Noelle and
a few others headed into the water.
Just watch, Mother.
I'm going to become even stronger.
But it wasn't only Noelle who
vowed to become stronger.
So this is...
The food that's going to explosively
enhance our mana just by eating it.
You can do that just by eating food?
I guess I'll dig in.
You don't have any magic, so it's not like
anything's going to change for you.
Who knows?! I might get more anti-magic!
Let's eat!
Holy crap! I can feel it instantly!
It feels like my mana's
overflowing from within me.
The hell is this?!
My body's just...
This is so much fun!
You guys!
What's going—huh?!
She's in trouble, too?!
M-Miz Charmy! You need to
do something about this!
No... This food isn't good enough.
No, wait! Stop!
I know! I'll have to go see him!
Charmy's Century of Hunger,
Gordon's Millennium of Loneliness
Magic Knights Headquarters
Jamo
You want to be my student?
Her fiery, glistening eyes...
Her fiery, glistening drool...
And...
Her fiery, glistening forehead!
As always...
She's really something else!
All right, you got it! You're my
student starting today, shrimp!
Thanks!
Food that'll enhance mana, eh?
I can make food that will
recover mana with my magic.
But what I need right now is food that
will explosively enhance my friends' mana!
I see. That's not gonna be a simple task.
Are you ready for this, shrimp?
Sure am!
La!
986, 987, 988, 989, 990...
The sheep cooks are your magic.
But just leveling up your
magic won't be enough.
991, 992...
993, 994, 995...
You need to seal away your magic and
train yourself past your physical limits,
so that not only the Sheep Cooks
but also you, shrimp,
996, 997, 998...
can acquire the food that will enhance mana.
999... 1,000!
We've got your stamina up now.
According to this book, the next
thing you need to do is acquire three
unknown ingredients that
even I've never seen before.
Three unknown ingredients?
The first is the bulb of a
mentanpin mandoradora!
Got it!
The second is the noonesheardofthis coelacanth!
The third is the butt hide
of a surprisesquatch!
La!
Say what?!
The shrimp did what?!
La... La... La...
You didn't have to push yourself that hard!
Just as you said, Master.
Now... I...
Tonight I, Charmy Pappitson, will serve
the best mana enhancement dishes ever.
So these are true mana enhancement dishes?
Uh, why did I get called in all of a sudden?
You're insurance if things go south, duh.
Wait, when what goes south?!
Miz Charmy... You pushed yourself so hard.
Eat up!
I-I'm gonna pass.
I think I will, too.
We should get going.
Please eat it!
Please show Miz Charmy
her efforts weren't in vain!
I beg of you!
These dishes were created by the shri...
by Charmy for her friends, and she
risked her life for these ingredients!
Who the heck are you?
Master... Asta...
Oh, fine.
C-Could it be...
Hey, hey, hey! What the hell's going on?!
This isn't good. Everyone!
Spatial Magic: Fallen Angel Gate!
Ow...
The hell are you guys doing?
Captain Yami?
You thinking about using
my wheels to go somewhere?
Now's not the time for that, Yami!
The hell is that?
That's... demon food!
Demon food?!
You just now thought that up, didn't you?
Quit making random shit up, you jerk!
Who the hell is that?
This is the first time I'm
seeing it with my own eyes,
but the combination of pure devotion and mana
sometimes gives life to food.
Uh, that doesn't happen!
Then how would you explain
what we're seeing right now?!
All the feelings that Charmy put toward
enhancing mana were the real deal!
And that's exactly how the food ended
up with an explosive amount of mana!
The food has life now?
Huh?
Miz Charmy, what's wrong?!
The hell?!
Magna?
I dunno why, but I don't have any strength.
Luck?!
It's stealing away our mana!
What's going on?
The demon food is absorbing all of our mana
so it can become even more powerful!
No, really. Who are you?
The noms I made...
Hey, kid. What the hell are you zoning out for?
Don't you think your sword
can do something about that
stupidly big food monster?
Well...
Tch. Okay, fine.
I'll go out on a limb and—
You can't!
What do you mean?
That food is filled with
Miz Charmy's feelings...
Yes! It's food!
The hell are you talking about?
Asta...
Please put a stop to it!
Okay!
Wait, are you seriously...
I'll gobble up all of Miz Charmy's food!
Don't blame me if you get a stomachache.
Our mana's gradually coming back.
Mana's flowing out of the
part the kid's eating?
I'm not gonna let Asta have all the noms!
We can't just leave this to those two!
I guess not.
Well, now that that's settled,
this shouldn't take too long.
Eat every last bit of that
stupidly big food monster.
Wait! Me, too?
Absolutely not!
Again...
Who are you?
Good job, you guys.
This looks like a scene right out of hell.
Miz Charmy...
La?
I feel like that food was
different from your usual food.
Huh?
I can't really put it into words,
but it seems like it was
solely made to enhance mana.
Your food is usually filled with your desire
to make the people eating it happy,
but that seemed to be missing...
Wait! I'm sorry for being out of line!
Master!
We might've forgotten the most
important thing as chefs.
Charmy... no, shrimp! Back to square one!
Yes, Master!
One more time!
My days now are spent
surrounded by many friends.
I might be happier now than I've ever been.
We have to win in this fight against the devil.
If we don't, our happy days will come to an end.
I think that last one was pretty good.
Asta...
Do you think I could join in on your training?
Of course!
Noelle, go ahead and take a break!
Uh, sure.
Come at me with everything you've got!
O-Okay...
With everything I've got...
That wasn't my intention,
but I'm sure Asta will be okay.
Okay, here I go.
Poison Curse Magic:
Dwelling of the Poison Cloud.
Gordon! Are you okay?!
As expected.
I'm no match for you.
I was fighting with everything I had.
Maybe I've gotten weaker.
When I first came to the
Black Bulls, I was truly alone.
But I was sharp as a knife and had the
strength to not let anyone near me.
And yet, now I'm...
Please don't try to find me.
I can't just stay complacent,
surrounded by my friends.
In order to defeat the devil, and to
regain my strength from before...
I must be alone once more.
The Forest of Poisonous Magical Beasts
In the past, Lady Mereoleona walked
through a strong magic region alone
and became as powerful as she is now.
That's why I'm going to go through the
Forest of Poisonous Magical Beasts
that lies right before the Witches' Forest.
Noble Realm
Common Realm
I'd go to the strong magic region...
but that's a bit scary,
Forsaken Realm
Strong Magic Region
so I'll do my best in this forest.
Common Realm
Forsaken Realm
Things seem to be going well.
Probably because I'm all alone again.
Okay, I'll take a break now.
I am pretty hungry.
Huh?
My week's worth of food!
Wait!
3 Days Later
I can't find my backpack.
Maybe I'll head back...
I think I've gotten a good
taste of being alone again.
Huh?
I don't know how to get home.
Eating all alone never tastes good.
Eating with everyone was pretty rowdy, but fun.
If my friends were here at a time like this...
Gordon! I'll go get you some yummy food, stat!
Get a grip, Gordon. As your partner
in the G-G duo, I'll be by your side.
Gordon, are you tired? Eek!
I know you've got more to you than that!
I'm done trying to kill Magna,
so you're next, Gordon!
What the hell am I doing?
Now's my chance to test out the strength
I've regained by being alone.
Poison Curse Magic:
Dwelling of the Poison Cloud.
One more time!
But why?
My poison curse magic didn't work.
I really must be weaker.
Thank goodness... This is the
first water I've had in three days.
I'll live here on my own for a while.
I'll find food on my own and sleep alone.
And wash my face alone, like this...
Back at the Black Bulls' hideout, Asta and
I would always wash each other's backs.
There were nights I'd drink with
Vanessa as we talked about our dreams.
There were times I helped Gauche
take care of his Marie doll.
There were even times Luck and I
risked our lives fighting each other.
I must get stronger.
But to think that being alone is so painful...
Even though this was normal for
me before joining the Black Bulls...
I wonder what everyone's up to right now.
This is...
We've got to hurry!
All right, let's get moving!
Right!
They're going to come find me, right?
You guys are here already?
The... mother of that
magical beast from earlier?
This is...
We've got to hurry!
All right, let's get moving!
Right!
Poison Curse Magic: Aufwachen Dachs!
It's no use... My magic is having no effect at all.
I'm finished... I'm going to die here all alone.
I see...
So they didn't abandon me.
I finally see that it wasn't
loneliness that I needed.
I became stronger because I had friends!
This loneliness is poison itself.
And the antidote for this poison...
is my friendship with my teammates!
I'm sorry...
I panicked, and I ended up hurting you.
That's unforgivable for a Magic Knight who's
tasked with protecting this kingdom...
You're my fellow comrades
living in the Clover Kingdom.
No... You're my friends.
Thanks for leading the way.
I see. You both have immunity to poison magic.
So that's why my magic didn't work.
I'm home.
Ah...
Everyone must've gone looking for me.
They might all be in danger somewhere.
Now it's my turn to go find them.
I'll never leave my friends again.
This is great!
Listen up! Surpass your limits!
Eat and drink all you can!
I've definitely surpassed them!
Mister Yami, the workers
here sure are staring at us.
Hell if I care!
They're doing an inventory count and
selling off all their ingredients,
and this says...
we get 90% off our bill for
an unlimited time period!
I'm not going to lose!
No matter how much food there is,
I'm going to eat all of it!
In the name of my tummy!
Next time on Black Clover,
Page 138: "In Zara's Footsteps."
Page 138
In Zara's Footsteps
Who's Zara, la?
Huh? Zora's dad?