The Clover Kingdom.
In this kingdom where magic is everything,
there is one boy who can't use magic.
His name is Asta.
With guts and hard work,
he made it into the Magic Knights,
and he never gave up,
despite how much he got hurt.
He continues to diligently aim for the top!
Even if you are a peasant,
or even if you're poor...
Anyone in this world can still shine!
He's working hard to prove that,
and to become the Wizard King!
Tolsa Village
Those flowers are for me?
Yes. You like them, don't you?
Aren't you supposed to be selling them, though?
It's fine. You're my hero, Zara.
Dad.
Zora! Come here a sec!
Well, I'll be going now.
What was that about?
Don't these smell great, Zora?
I love this scent.
Yeah, I know.
In Zara's Footsteps
What a pain. Like I have time for that.
Train together, my ass.
I didn't join the squad so I could
be all buddy-buddy with you guys.
I left on a journey to train
since I didn't have time
to bother with the rest of the Black Bulls,
but how long am I going to keep doing this?
Right, Dad?
Could it have been someone from
the village? Yeah, no way.
It's true that Dad was called the pride of
Tolsa Village because he was
the first peasant Magic Knight.
But that's all in the past.
Damn it!
He's not even using a grimoire?
Guess he has potential.
Well, do your best, I gues—
Who's there?!
Whoops, my bad.
Wow! You hit the target all the way from here!
Your flame magic is amazing, Kaito!
I can't wait for you to take
the Magic Knights Entrance Exam!
Oh, stop. This isn't the time for that.
I'm guessing that brat's some rich kid who
came to a summer resort for some R&R.
What's that look for?
Apologize!
Did you just tell Kaito to apologize?!
Watch your tongue!
Oh, stop. He's just a child who doesn't even
have a grimoire yet, and a peasant at that.
Here you go.
That should settle things, right?
Let's go.
I'm sorry I'm a peasant.
What?
But when I turn fifteen and get my grimoire...
I hope you're not about to say you're
going to join the Magic Knights.
I am! I'm joining the Magic Knights!
Don't bother. It's impossible for peasants.
But there are peasants in the Magic Knights!
Are there?
They've made quite the buzz lately.
I'm sure they only got in because they had
dirt on a current Magic Knight or something.
I know for a fact that Zara
Ideale didn't join that way!
Zara Ideale?
I've never heard of him.
What squad?
The Purple Orcas!
The Purple Orcas?
The squad at the center of
all the unsavory rumors after
their captain got replaced
because of a scandal?
Zara's an amazing Magic Knight!
Yeah?
How? If he's that amazing,
he must be renowned for something.
Well? Isn't he?
H-He died during a mission.
See? This is exactly my point.
Peasants should know their place and
just stay in their villages until they die.
Shut up!
What's that magic?
Teach him a lesson.
Okay.
You stupid peasant!
Apologize to Kaito!
No!
Apologize!
I didn't do anything wrong!
I see...
That's enough.
Wh-Who are you?
That reeks!
Hold it!
That power...
Y-You'll regret this, you peasant!
Are you stupid?
Don't pick fights when you're
up against three guys like that.
You don't even have a grimoire.
There's no way you would've won.
Try using that tiny little brain of yours.
Though... what you said about Zara Ideale
being an amazing Magic Knight
isn't exactly wrong.
Ina? Is that you?
Dad!
Ina, what happened to you? Don't tell me...
This masked guy... saved me.
What? I-I'm sorry for any
trouble my son caused you.
Ina, what happened? Tell me.
Did you do something you can't tell me about?
Peasants should know their place and
just stay in their villages until they die.
Why was I born to peasants?
If I wasn't born into a peasant family,
I would've had greater magic powers.
If only you weren't my father!
Hey!
Wait!
He's exactly right.
What?
If I weren't in this state, he wouldn't
have to help me with my work.
I could've given him more
time to train with magic.
I'm a failure as a father.
L-Let go of me!
Wh-Where are you going?
Wait, have I seen that
young man somewhere before?
What the hell are you doing?!
Cool Mask Guy.
Huh?
That's what you'll call me.
What the hell are you talking about?
Listen up, you shitty little shrimp...
No, you snot-nosed shrimp.
Who're you calling a snot-nosed shrimp?!
You probably know this,
but I'll remind you anyway.
The amazing Magic Knight you were
just praising was also a peasant.
So what if he was?
Are you trying to say he's
way different than me?
It's true that Zara Ideale never
lamented his upbringing,
and never said anything bad about anyone.
You knew Zara, Mask Guy?!
That's Cool Mask Guy to you.
But as you said, he's way different than you.
I know... that I'm aiming too high.
I'm aiming too high?
Yeah. You're a peasant, yet you
want to join the Magic Knights.
I don't remember how many times I've failed
the Magic Knights Entrance Exam, Zora.
But I don't believe I'm aiming too high, either.
I'm always telling you that I'm gonna
join the Magic Knights, aren't I?
That's because I really believe I can!
You said you were gonna join
the Magic Knights, didn't you?
So you heard me. You got a problem with that?
I never said I did.
But if you're able to say that, doesn't that
mean you really believe you can do it?
That's not what you'd call aiming too high.
Zara Ideale said the same thing.
I really believe I can do it?
Let me give you some advice, snot-nosed shrimp.
Stop calling me a snot-nosed shrimp!
Wait, what's that?
Isn't that doll... you?
This is the envoy of justice,
the Super Magic Knight Zora.
I'm twelve years old, you know...
He has a mouth on him,
but he's as good as his word.
He's a warrior who protects
the country behind the scenes.
What the hell kind of backstory is that?
You look like that, but you're
into dolls? Really?
Zora was also the child of a peasant,
but he didn't idolize nobles or royalty.
That's because he could do something
nobles and royalty couldn't.
Stop ignoring me! Wait, something
nobles and royalty couldn't do?
Now, I wonder what that could be?
How the hell would I know?
I'm sure you wouldn't.
But if you don't know that,
you'll never be able to join
the Magic Knights.
Zora was also the child of a peasant,
but he didn't idolize nobles or royalty.
That's because he could do something
nobles and royalty couldn't.
Now, I wonder what that could be?
Ina, let's take a lunch break.
I'll take care of the afternoon work.
You can go practice your magic if you want.
You got lucky yesterday,
but you'll pay for embarrassing me.
I've come to collect.
Do you know what this is, peasant?
A magic item?
Now that I have this...
Whoa, now... A kid shouldn't
be playing with that.
Apologize. That's not too difficult, is it?
You just need to grovel right there.
I didn't do anything wrong!
What did you just say?
You're not going to get off with just
a few scratches. Hurry up and—
You dumbass!
That's the second time. Stick to
your usual toys, you brat.
You're really strong, huh?
You're not a Magic Knight... are you?
Who knows?
Ina...
So you must be the little thief.
May I help you?
What do you think you're doing to my son?!
See for yourself.
That's... a magic item!
Your son stole it from my villa.
I-I did not!
What are you talking about?
You clearly had the magic item.
Your son took it! I just picked
it up after he dropped it!
Is that true, Kaito?
Don't let him fool you.
You can never trust a peasant.
You taught me that yourself, Father.
That I did. You're coming with me!
I'm taking you to the royal capital
so they can arrest you
as the burglar that you are!
Ina!
Let go of me! I'm not a thief!
Let go of my son!
And what if I refuse?
I believe my son!
I won't let you take him!
Dad...
You filthy peasant...
You'll pay for your insolence!
Dad!
What?!
Dad! The flowers!
Don't worry.
You wouldn't have to get hurt
if you just knew your place.
That magic...
You'll be wiping off that smug look soon enough!
I have proof that your son is a thief!
I'll just ask the Magic Knights to deal with it!
Then let's see this so-called proof.
Wh-Who are you?
That robe...
You're a Black Bull!
So he really is...
Perfect timing! I need you to
capture these thieves for me!
And I'm telling you to show me proof.
O-Of course!
You saw him take it from the villa, didn't you?
U-Um...
I just happened to be present
when your precious little boy
used a magic item to mess
with the snot-nosed shrimp here.
After I interceded, I saw him
drop it and run off like a coward.
I'm guessing your dad found
out the magic item was missing,
so you tried to place the blame
on the snot-nosed shrimp.
You're the only thief here.
They say lying is the first
step to becoming a thief,
but I guess it was the other way around for you.
You're just the stupid son
of a worthless noble.
Is this true, Kaito?
Here's your proof.
Wh-What happened?!
You took it, didn't you?
Y-Yes! I'm really sorry!
W-Wait, Kaito!
I'll let you off the hook today!
Let them off the hook, my ass!
They say a child is the
reflection of his parents.
Clearly, you two are the
dictionary definition of that.
I've been sick of nobles for a long time,
but you have no right to raise a child!
You're a worthless noble
and a failure as a father.
This item is too good for you.
Get moving, or I'll kill you.
Yes, sir!
They even run away the same way.
Dad...
I never knew you could use such powerful magic.
I've failed the Magic Knights
Entrance Exam numerous times.
It's embarrassing to say, but this
injury came from one of those failures.
But still, I can't give up.
Even while I do my usual work,
I constantly train with my magic.
Because I want to be like my hero.
He also failed numerous times,
but ultimately, he joined the Magic Knights.
I'm sure he worked really hard for it.
Zora was also the child of a peasant,
but he didn't idolize nobles or royalty.
That's because he could do something
nobles and royalty couldn't.
Now, I wonder what that could be?
I figured it out, Cool Mask Guy.
Cool Mask Guy?
The thing Zora was able to do.
Then you should know what you
need to say to your dad, too.
I'm sorry, Dad... for what I said to you.
Ina...
I'm sure you'll be able to join
the Magic Knights someday!
I won't be joining alone.
Huh?
Let's both do our best together, Ina!
Yeah!
By the way...
Why did you even bother with me?
No particular reason.
I see.
I guess you really are a Super Magic Knight.
What?
You're a Magic Knight.
You're wearing a robe, aren't you?
I never got as far as
becoming a Super Magic Knight.
Now, I'm just striving to
become a true Magic Knight.
Just like you.
Yeah! I'll join the Magic Knights someday!
Well, do your best, snot-nosed shrimp.
Yeah!
A rainbow stinkbug!
It reeks!
I'm the one who'll become the Wizard King.
Nope, it's me!
They're only able to say that because
they truly believe they can.
Just watch, Dad.
I'll make it to this zero stage.
Guess whipping the other Black Bulls
into shape would help with that.
Those jerks are such a handful.
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Super Magic Knight Zora
Super Magic Knight Zora!
Boom! The envoy of justice,
the Super Magic Knight Zora!
I'm twelve years old, you know...
And now, I'm 25!
I now have something more
suitable for my age!
Newly sculpted, painted, and fully articulated!
The envoy of justice, Super Magic Knight Zora!
Hey.
Gulp.
So you really do like playing with dolls!
W-Wait, I can explain...
He has a mouth on him,
but he's as good as his word.
This delusion of a warrior who
protects the land from the shadows...
Did you really think that up at your age?
No, that was my dad, Zara Ideale.
Lying is the first step to becoming a thief!
Zara's an amazing Magic Knight!
He'd never think up something so dumb!
I'm not lying!
Well, that was totally out of character.
I'm rather delicate, so I guess I got a
bit sentimental when I went back home.
Next time on Black Clover, Page 139:
"A Witch's Homecoming."
Page 138
A Witch's Homecoming
That drunk's going home, too?