The Clover Kingdom.
In this kingdom where magic is everything,
there is one boy who can't use magic.
His name is Asta.
With guts and hard work,
he made it into the Magic Knights,
and he never gave up,
despite how much he got hurt.
He continues to diligently aim for the top!
Even if you are a peasant,
or even if you're poor...
Anyone in this world can still shine!
He's working hard to prove that,
and to become the Wizard King!
Lord Julius...
I told you that you're not allowed
to go wandering off for a while.
I'm surprised you knew I'd come through here.
Do you realize how many
years I have served you?
Now please return to the office and
take care of that pile of documents.
Oh, I'm done with the ones for today, though.
What?
Going through those is the best way
to find out what's going on out here.
But nothing beats coming out
here and seeing it for myself,
so I'm off to wander around.
Please wait.
I understand how you feel,
but with the threats of the Spade Kingdom and the devil looming over us,
if something were to happen...
True. I've lost most of my mana and magic,
so there isn't much I can do right now.
In that case, I have some
favors to ask of you, Marx.
First...
A Favor for Julius
Here I go, Asta!
Got it!
Water Creation Magic: Sea Dragon's Waterball.
Come on! You can do better than that!
Noelle! Hit me with all you've got!
You don't have to go easy on me
just because we're teammates!
Fine. Don't come crying to me later.
Water Creation Magic: Sea Dragon's Roar!
I'd like you to get stronger and
fight alongside us in six months.
Not yet... This isn't nearly enough!
Aw, you stopped it.
You're...
Sally
Sally?!
Heya, Asta! How have you been?
What are you doing here?
Wait, did you escape?
Nah, the white mushroom head brought me.
Who are you calling a white mushroom head?
Hey... You're the Wizard King's attendant and...
Uh, who are you?
Magic Item Research Lab Specially-Appointed Researcher
Makusa North
I'm Makusa from the Magic Item Research Lab.
Huh?
Creating magic items?
Yes! Lord Julius saw potential in
Sally's knowledge of magical science
and asked her to create a new magic
item to help with the upcoming battle.
I was against this, but...
So, like, I need a bunch of data to make one,
so I decided to experiment on you guys.
Like we'd ever agree to that!
You may have turned over a new leaf,
but who knows what you'll do?
You got it!
W-Wait, what are you talking about?!
Do you remember that I promised
you could do whatever you wanted with
my body once the battle was over?
Well, I'm glad you remember that, too, Asta.
Just remember! Nothing that
hurts super bad, okay?
Is that really the problem here, Stupidsta?
What if she tries to dissect you?
D-Dissect? She couldn't possibly...
If so, we'll have to call off
this experiment right away.
Then let's get started!
Or so I'd like to say... but I think
I'll save you for last, Asta.
The thing I'm trying to make is supposed to
increase one's mana, and you don't have any.
Maybe I'll experiment on you first!
A-Again, I want no part of this.
I'm royalty, and even if I wasn't,
there's no way I'd agree to this!
By the way, where are the other Black Bulls?
Oh, they're all either out
training or on missions.
They ones out training should
be back any time now.
Gah.
Hey, how long have you guys been there?
Right. I just remembered
I need to do something.
Restrain yourself, me...
Well, see ya!
Woohoo! So many test subjects!
Hey!
Stop at once!
You are not allowed to conduct any
experiments without Makusa's or my supervision!
Hey, look! It's the Wizard King!
Huh?!
There!
Sally!
Asta, Noelle! Please don't worry
about us! Just go after Sally!
Got it!
This is probably far enough.
Like hell I'm gonna let that
crazy chick experiment on me.
L-Let go of me! I'll kill you!
Aw... But when the magic item's done,
your magic's gonna get explosively stronger,
so help me out, Funglasquent.
Who the hell are you calling a mohawked
virgin delinquent in glasses?!
Since you use flame magic, Glasquent...
Stop making it even shorter, damn it!
The dark magic item equation will be this...
And then the mana exponent
will end up like that...
This is the experimental liquid I'll use!
Now I'll just use my Sticky Salamander
instead of the magic item and...
Inject!
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-What the hell?!
There's an insane amount of
flame mana flowing out from me.
I know, right? Amazing, isn't it?
Huh? H-Hey, hang on a sec!
There's too much flowing out... I'm gonna...
e-explode...
Huh? Maybe the dark magic item
equation is still incomplete.
And maybe the experimental
liquid's too potent.
But I got some data, so on to the next one!
Don't worry! I won't dissect you!
Transformation Magic—
Hold it! Now's not a good time!
Huh? But why?
Wait, that's...
Marie?!
No one's laying a finger on my angel!
B-But that's not the real Marie!
And she's all sticky!
Even if she's all sticky,
Marie is still Marie!
You guys use combo magic, so it might
be fun to experiment on you both at once!
The two of us together?! How embarrassing!
Marie!
Y-You can't! You said you were
going to restrain yourself!
But this is an insanely rare
vintage I may never see again.
Let's go, Vanessa. I'm telling you,
this is definitely a trap.
Experiment! Experiment!
A bewitching trail of noms.
Could this be the path to heaven?
Welcome!
Restrain yourself... Restrain yourself...
E-Explode...
Finral! Vanessa!
Are you guys okay?!
Huh? Did something happen?
Looks like we got here too late.
We need to stop Sally, quick!
H-Heaven...
Hm... So far, none of these
experiments are going as planned.
I still need more data.
Hold it, Sally!
Charmy, are you okay?
What's this? Asta, you're supposed to be last.
What, you couldn't wait any longer?
Hngh!
I'll never go back on my word!
You can do whatever you want with my body,
just stop messing with everyone else!
You're still going on about that, Stupidsta?!
Maybe you won't just end up in a daze!
Yeah, but the only reason we
made it to the royal capital is
because Sally and the others showed up.
That's how we protected everyone!
So I'm going to keep my promise!
Good point. Keeping your promises is important!
Don't forget the anesthesia!
Oh, don't worry. This won't hurt one bit!
Here I come!
Asta!
All mine!
I'll have to culture it when I get back!
Wait. You just needed my hair?
Well, remember what you said, Asta?
You said I could experiment all I wanted
as long as I didn't harm anyone.
Oh, yeah. You said I couldn't
bother anyone, either.
Don't worry. They'll all be back to normal soon.
Their magic just got too powerful for
a moment, so it sorta knocked them out.
Sally! I guess you remembered
our promise, too!
Aw, but Asta,
your hair's not going to be enough,
so could I have some nail clippings, too?
Of course!
Wh-Why are you touching him like that?
Actually, that's not quite enough, either,
so could I have some of your blood?
While we're at it, maybe your heart,
your lungs, and your eyeballs?
You most certainly can't!
Anyway, just make sure this research
will help everyone out, okay?
Ugh... That was awful.
Why, you little...
Go to hell!
Now, now, guys. You're all better now.
As for the results of this experiment...
I can't understand a single thing here,
but it sure is interesting!
Makusa will take this information back
to the capital and inspect it carefully.
The magic item will be created after that.
Do your best making it,
Sally and researcher guy!
Okay!
We will!
Well, we ended up being guinea pigs,
so I'm hoping the data gets put to good use.
Yeah!
Don't you dare slack off!
I'll kill you if you mess it up!
What are you waiting for, Finral?
Use your spatial magic already.
R-Right...
I do still have seniority here...
Let's go, Sally.
Sure thing!
"I prefer doing research that helps people out."
Sally! See ya later!
That might actually be true now!
We're almost to Arandom Village.
To think that the two of us
would end up on a mission
together despite being in separate squads.
This isn't a field trip.
I will find anyone who threatens
our kingdom and strike them down.
What in the world happened in this village?
Lord Julius,
I've brought the captains of the Crimson
Lion Kings and the Silver Eagles.
Thanks! Sorry to summon you
both here when you're so busy.
It's fine.
What did you need, sir?
Have you two ever heard
of a village called Arandom?
Noble Realm
Common Realm
A while back when I was wande—
Forsaken Realm
When I was investigating
various parts of the kingdom,
it was a small village I visited
in the Forsaken Realm.
According to some reports, bandits have
shown up around that village lately.
Then we should send a team
to deal with them at once.
No, that probably won't be enough.
I have a feeling there's something rather
unfavorable going on in this kingdom.
Unfavorable?
What could that be?
So I'd like you two to conceal your
identities, interact with the villagers,
and gather information on the bandits.
This will be an undercover investigation.
An undercover investigation?
We're just wandering around in disguise!
Um... About these disguises...
I think these will just draw
attention in the Forsaken Realm.
True, I can't deny that,
but since neither of us is
familiar with how peasants live,
our cover will be blown immediately.
Though few, there are traveling mages who
were once royalty or nobility,
but forsook their titles.
Oh, I see. By the way, as for where
we should gather information...
The village square should do.
I agree. Lord Julius said to act casually
around those who interact with us.
Let us go blend in with the masses.
Is that even possible?
Also, you probably don't need
to be so serious about this.
How do I explain that to them?
Forsaken Realm
Arandom Village
Th-This is...
We'd heard there were places that
had yet to be restored, but...
To think it'd be this bad.
This matter will need attention eventually,
but our mission comes first.
I'll go gather information over there.
And I'll head over there.
You there.
Huh? I don't think I've seen
you around here before.
I'm a traveling mage named Leon.
A-And I'm, um... Mark.
Traveling mages?
We heard that there were bandits around here.
I'd like you to tell us what
you know to ensure our safety.
No idea. Go bother someone else.
As I thought. They're wary of
us because of our disguises.
What shall we do, Fue... I mean, Leon?
Oh, yeah! If things get
difficult, try saying this...
Chrono... vala.
Chronovala?
D-Don't tell me you're...
You're friends of Chronovala's?
That old lady helped us out so much!
Whenever I didn't have enough customers,
she'd help find me some.
I made a fortune that day!
But before I knew it, she disappeared.
How's she doing, anyway?
Chronovala... Chrono...
Novachrono!
I get it! Chronovala must be the alias
Lord Julius used when he wandered out here.
So you know her!
That old lady was great.
Here, take this!
Though my fields have been destroyed,
so I don't have much.
I couldn't take them for free.
Will this be enough?
Th-This much?!
This is way too much, even if
you bought everything here!
Then use the rest to help get
this village back on its feet.
Are you really sure about this?!
Wow...
Who are those guys?
Apparently, they know Chronovala.
Amazing, Lord Julius. People respect
you so much, even as an old woman.
But we've brought a lot of
attention to ourselves when this
is supposed to be an undercover investigation.
I hope Captain Nozel is faring better...
You know Chronovala? She saved my baby's life!
She did?
I went into labor out in the fields,
and she called a doctor for me.
I know! Here, you can hold him!
I named him Vala.
Wait, I—
I haven't held a baby since Noelle was born.
Noze...
Noze?
Everyone here seems to know Ju—Chronovala.
It appears so.
I am the mayor of this village, Mayer.
We can't offer much, but please
stay the night in our village.
Yeah, that's a great idea! Stay the night!
We can't make much, but we'll treat you!
What shall we do?
We have no reason to decline.
Well, he did say to act casually
with anyone we encountered.
W-Well, if that's the case...
I guess we never got any
information on the bandits.
I wonder what the unfavorable
thing going on here could be.
What is it?
As I figured...
Looks like they're asleep.
Let's go.
So you're the bandits ravaging this area!
So what if we are? Give us all your money!
Or you're gonna get hurt.
Get 'em!
Y-You're...
The villagers?
I was hoping that wasn't the case.
This is the end.
Mayor!
We knew this would happen, even though
we were just trying to survive.
After the Eye of the Midnight Sun's attack,
our village was left in shambles.
But we never received aid
from the royal capital
and were driven into even worse poverty.
Still, stealing from others in order
to try to restore our village
was far too selfish of us.
I was the one who led my people to do this.
Please, let it just be me who
gets taken to the Magic Knights.
What are you talking about?!
You were just looking out for us!
I had no idea they were this dismayed.
If only we'd acted sooner,
this never would've happened.
We can't let the mayor take
all the blame for this!
We're going down with you.
N-No!
Y-You're...
Lord Fuegoleon and Lord Nozel!
M-M-M-Magic Knights captains?!
What?!
We can see that your village
is in need of assistance.
We can let this misconduct go.
You're too soft, as usual.
A crime is a crime.
Do not let your emotions get in
the way. They must be judged.
And you're being far too cruel.
You are hereby ordered to help restore
all of the villages in this area.
But a crime is still a crime.
Atone for what you have done.
D-Does that mean we're...
The royal capital has not forsaken you.
But we may not have been
aware of the entire situation.
We are going to work even harder to restore
this whole kingdom. Please have faith.
Thank you very much!
Thus ends the report on everything
that happened in that village.
Great job. You made the right choice.
We've sent squad members to the other
villages to see what kind of aid they need.
Yes. Our job is to protect this kingdom,
as well as to make sure its
citizens can live in peace.
By having to face the truth, perhaps your
view of this kingdom has changed a bit?
As I thought...
That's why he sent us.
Nozel, Fuegoleon...
I want you to work even harder to lead
the kingdom and the Magic Knights.
As you wish!
Yup. I'm counting on you two.
Now, then... I feel like
wandering around a bit myself.
Absolutely not.
Aw...
Then maybe I'll talk to Yami...
Since there isn't much I can do right now.
That may be true, but this kingdom
still needs you very much.
Yuno struggles with the Golden Dawn since
they are made up of nobles and royals.
Next time on Black Clover,
Page 141: "The Golden Family."
Page 141
The Golden Family
Just like Asta, Yuno has the
magic of never giving up.