The Clover Kingdom.
In this kingdom where magic is everything,
there is one boy who can't use magic.
His name is Asta.
He puts in blood, sweat, and tears
in hopes of becoming the Wizard King.
But there are also those in the kingdom
who possess at least a little bit of mana,
yet can barely use any magic at all.
The very few out of the population,
those who live in the shadows...
They are also trying to survive.
Those Remaining
Looking back a bit, to just before
Tiulyu Town
the Eye of the Midnight Sun
attacked the royal capital...
This town was neither rich nor poor,
neither big nor small.
A very mundane town found
in the Common Realm.
Ow...
Endure it. It'll get better soon enough.
Thank you.
It's fine.
Are you all right?
Yes.
I should go.
You can stay a while.
No one's going to come by.
I'd love to, but he'll be home soon.
I see.
See you later.
It's as delicious as ever. Thank you, Dazu.
It's nothing.
It really is delicious. At least you can cook.
Tell me about it.
Oh, dear. It looks like my soup has
gotten cold while we were talking.
I'll reheat it right away.
You don't need to go all the way
back to the kitchen for that.
Go on. Warm it up with your magic.
That's a great idea.
Then allow me to borrow some
of your flame magic, Mother,
and some of your spatial magic, dear.
Ah, it looks like it's warmed up.
Your catalyst magic really does come in handy.
You can borrow magic from
others and use it for yourself.
Impressive indeed.
Indeed.
My, it's delicious.
Run away!
Mommy!
Someone help me!
Accursed humans...
You will face the wrath of the elves!
Now is the time for our revenge!
Dear! Mother! Hang in there!
H-Hurry and help us...
Hurry up, you stupid...
It's too early for it to be dawn.
Curse you, human...
That's... the magic of the
Captain of the Golden Dawn.
How beautiful...
Did they save the kingdom?
A Few Days Later
Something wrong?
Look...
"The Devil's Servants"?
"The Magic Parliament will
put Magic Knights on trial
on suspicion of communicating with
the devil and using forbidden magic."
Apparently that incident
affected the entire kingdom.
According to the rumors,
those who attacked everyone
were being controlled by the devil
and had gained terrifying powers.
Devil... Terrifying powers?
The devil... did this?
I would like all of you to train your
squad members as much as you can.
We only have six months,
but do everything you can to
raise everyone's magic stages
so that we can face the Spade Kingdom
and protect this kingdom.
So, Damnatio, does that work for you?
Whatever do you mean?
In order to defeat the devil, the Magic Knights
will have to get stronger
in the next six months.
I'd like you to think about
what to do with Asta
after we've taken care of this matter
with the Spade Kingdom, if you would.
I have no objections.
What's the meaning of this?!
The Black Bull named Asta
and that woman named Nero...
You're going to wait six months to
try those servants of the devil?!
It's just as I explained it.
Our top priority now is to cooperate with
the Magic Knights and the Heart Kingdom
so that we can face the threats of
the Spade Kingdom and the devil.
But—
This has already been decided.
Are you truly okay with that, Lord Damnatio?
I am not. But there is an order to things...
And priorities.
Then that's all the more reason
to execute that devil first!
The chaos in our kingdom caused
by the Eye of the Midnight Sun
was the work of the devil, was it not?!
My nephew was among the victims...
Enough.
B-But to ensure the safety
and peace of our citizens,
we should execute them immediately!
That's why the Magic Parliament—
Take your leave!
P-Please excuse me.
The Wizard King has Lord Damnatio
dancing in the palm of his hand.
We're going to leave servants of
the devil be for six months? Impossible!
I must bring the scales of justice that
have tilted toward the darkness
back to the light.
I must bring peace and harmony
back to this kingdom.
That's him?
Yes, there's no doubt about it.
He hates the devil even more than
others in the Magic Parliament.
Let's go.
Pardon me.
Master Kabwe, I presume?
I am indeed Kabwe. Have we met before?
No, we have not.
May we have some of your time?
I'm sorry, but I'm a bit busy...
I lost my family in the attack
by the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
Not just my family. My town
burned, and many perished.
I'm sorry to hear that.
There are many in this kingdom
who are suffering just as you are.
Yes, you're exactly right.
Are you not also going through
the same thing, Kabwe?
How did you know that?
We want your help so that we can
seek revenge for the many victims.
My help?
What do you intend to do?
I... We want to destroy the servants
of the devil with our own hands.
The servants of the devil?
It appears that I'll have
to hear more about this.
Yes.
That would be appreciated.
As the royal capital began to calm down
after the Eye of the Midnight Sun's attack...
The Wizard King Julius Novachrono was
swamped with paperwork from
the aftermath of the attack,
and the Magic Knights were
training vigorously daily so that
they could take on the threats of
the Spade Kingdom and the devil.
What's wrong, Noelle?
Come at me more! Come on!
I could keep going, but I'm a bit
thirsty. Let's take a little break.
I'm not thirsty yet, though!
But I am! And I'm royalty!
You always say that, but that has
nothing to do with anything, does it?
Shut up! I said we're taking a break,
so we're taking a break!
You just keep working out,
then, Meathead Asta.
What's Noelle so mad about?
What do you think, Nero?
Dunno.
Guess I will work out, then.
One! Two! Three! Four! Five! Six!
Seven! Eight! Nine! Ten! Eleven!
Twelve! Thirteen! Fourteen! Fifteen! Sixteen!
Hey, Gauche, Finral.
Hey, Noelle. Could you get
me a glass of water, too?
Get one yourself.
Again, I have seniority here...
The hideout sure is quiet today.
Everyone but Henry is out training.
And you're slacking?
I'm just taking a short break!
What about you? Were you off seeing Marie again?
What?
Wh-What?
I was training this good-for-nothing.
I'm going to go serve my angel, Marie, later.
So you are going.
Yeah, I'm beat.
The combo move we came up with using my
spatial magic and his mirror magic...
The timing's just been impossible to get down.
I need to go cleanse my body
before I go see my angel.
It'd be rude to go see her drenched in sweat.
Sister Theresa's apparently
gone until tonight.
Apparently, all the sisters from the
church are getting together or something.
So he's going to go see her
before the sister comes back.
Or rather, he's forcing me to take him...
When the cat's away,
the mice will, well, you know...
Marie, I'll come to see you soon.
Gauche, I'll wash your back for you.
I hope you'll wash my back, too.
1,090! 1,091! 1,092! 1,093!
1,094! 1,095! 1,096! 1,097!
1,098! 1,099! 1,100! 1,101!
How long is he going to keep that up?
1,102! 1,103! 1,104! 1,105! 1,106!
Maybe I should take him something to eat.
Even I can make a sandwich.
A Town in the Common Realm, Nean
Here it comes, Marie!
There!
Nice kick!
There. That must be her.
Yes. That's Marie Adlai.
The daughter of a fallen noble. Her older
brother is a former criminal, and...
She was controlled by a devil during the
attack and harmed many innocent people.
Let's take care of this before the
old hag from the church returns.
Indeed.
I'm sorry.
Servant of the devil...
You're coming with me!
You brat...
What are you doing to Marie?!
Are you planning to take her again?
We won't let you take her!
No way!
Little brats...
Who the heck are they?
H-Hey! Theresa! Theresa!
Theresa's out right now.
Th-They're trying to take Marie!
Wh-Who are you guys?!
Neige!
We are the Devil Banishers!
Devil... I won't let you take Marie!
Snow Magic: Snow Cry!
Of course this happens
when Theresa isn't here...
There are more of them?
Snow Magic—
Wh-When did they...
I couldn't sense their mana.
Neige!
Hey! Stop! Let go!
Stop!
Everyone!
You're not getting away again,
servant of the devil.
But I'm not a servant of the devil...
We must return the scale that's tilted
toward darkness back to the light.
Y-You lot!
What are you going to do with her?!
We need to contact the Magic Knights!
Let's go!
Marie...
Marie!
Someone... Save me! Big Brother! Big Brother!
What's the matter?
I thought I heard an angel
call for me just now.
You're hearing things.
I'm sure Marie must be anxious to see me, too.
What in the world is that?
Is that for the magical beasts?
How rude! It's a sandwich!
If you want a bite, just say so!
No, I don't want it.
Hey, Finral.
Wake up! Let's go.
Sure, whatever.
Seriously, none of you know
how to treat a senior comrade.
All right, Noelle. We're going out for a bit.
Not a bit. We'll be gone for a while!
If Yami finds out, I'm gonna
get a scolding, too.
Here.
Now, I should...
8,122! 8,123! 8,124! 8,125!
8,126! 8,127! 8,128!
How long are you going to do this?
Until 10,000!
Wait... 8,003?! No!
I lost count because you talked to me!
Now I need to start back at one!
One, two, three, four, five, six...
That must be Asta.
Seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve...
Yes. He has no mana and cannot use magic,
but somehow he joined the Magic Knights.
Thirteen, fourteen, fifteen, sixteen...
He's nothing but a filthy devil's servant.
Let's do this.
All is according to plan.
131, 132, 133, 134...
135... 136?
Huh? Only one person?
What's the matter?
Hey, talk to me! What happened?
T-Take this, please.
What is this?
Poison?
Your mixing abilities are quite impressive.
Thank you.
I thought we only had the
devil-possessed boy here,
but apparently the girl who used
forbidden magic is here, too.
Luck must be on our side.
So this is Nero.
Look at those horns... She's clearly a devil.
They're proof that she used forbidden magic.
Now, let us capture them.
Stop!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow! Let go!
How can he be so strong?!
I'm losing consciousness...
Let go of Nero!
Asta...
What are you doing?!
Get away from Asta and Nero!
Sealing Magic: Inverse Release!
My body... Crap! I'm gonna di...
Let's hurry and take them.
Water Creation Magic: Sea Dragon's...
Plant Magic: The Flower on the Roadside!
Water—
Sand Magic: Sandscreen!
Let's go!
You're not getting away!
It seems really noisy outside...
Asta! Nero!
She's fast!
Water Creation Magic: Sea Dragon's Waterball!
Crap!
Let's give up for now.
Yes.
I a-apologize...
Transparency Magic:
Share the Same Fate!
Hold it! Who are you?!
We are the Devil Banishers.
We wish for the demise of the devil.
You're not getting away! Give Nero back!
I can't sense their mana.
Nero!
Asta!
How could they do that to little children?
Wh-What's going on?
It's terrible! Marie was...
What?!
Asta, wake up!
Asta!
Asta, don't die!
Make one of your stupid faces and laugh! Asta!
Next time on Black Clover,
Page 143: "The Tilted Scale."
Page 143
The Tilted Scale
They took Nero and Marie...
Just what are they after?!