The Clover Kingdom.
In this kingdom where magic is everything,
there is one boy who can't use magic.
His name is Asta.
He puts in blood, sweat, and tears
in hopes of becoming the Wizard King.
But there are also those in the kingdom
who possess at least a little bit of mana,
yet can barely use any magic at all.
The very few out of the population,
those who live in the shadows...
They are also trying to survive.
Run away!
Mommy!
Someone help me!
On that night in the Clover Kingdom
when chaos reigned due to the
reincarnation of the elves...
Dear! Mother! Hang in there!
Dazu, who lived in a town called Tiulyu,
lost her husband and mother-in-law.
Along with another resident of
Tiulyu named Bow, she decided
to confront Kabwe,
a member of the Magic Parliament.
Kabwe hated devils immensely,
and the fact that
Asta, Nero, and Marie, who were supposed
to be sentenced for being devil-possessed,
had their trial delayed by Damnatio made
Kabwe resent the situation even more.
They eventually took action.
They assumed the title "Devil Banishers"
and kidnapped Marie from the church in Nean.
You're not getting away again,
servant of the devil.
But I'm not a servant of the devil...
We must return the scale that's tilted
toward darkness back to the light.
Let's go!
Someone... Save me!
Big Brother! Big Brother!
Around the same time,
Asta and Nero were put to sleep so
they could be taken away, but...
Let go of Nero!
Asta...
What are you doing?!
Get away from Asta and Nero!
Sealing Magic: Inverse Release!
My body... Crap! I'm gonna di...
Let's hurry and take them.
Water Creation Magic: Sea Dragon's...
Plant Magic: The Flower on the Roadside!
Water—
Let's go!
Asta! Nero!
She's fast!
Sea Dragon's Waterball!
Noelle stopped them.
But in the end, Nero was still taken.
And Asta....
Hold it! Who are you?!
We are the Devil Banishers.
We wish for the demise of the devil.
You're not getting away! Give Nero back!
Asta!
Wake up!
The Tilted Scale
I see you made it safely.
How did things go?
We had no problems.
Where's Asta?
We apologize.
Someone got in the way.
I see.
But by now, he should be...
in a deep sleep.
How is Asta? He's still alive, isn't he?!
Don't worry, he's alive.
Then why won't he open his eyes?
Even if he's alive, what if he's under some
spell that will keep him asleep forever?
Don't worry. Asta's not
asleep because of a spell.
Huh?
I see. The reason Asta's still asleep is...
E-Excuse me!
What possessed you to bring
me here all of a sudden?
Asta?!
So the kid's still asleep?
What do you mean, he's not
asleep because of a spell?
You're not gonna suggest it's some
sleeping potion, are you, you quack?
That's exactly it.
It's quite surprising, really.
I don't know who did it, but to think
someone could make one this powerful...
Why would anyone have a sleeping potion?
That, I can't answer.
If he just continues to rest for a while,
he should wake up on his own.
Thank goodness.
So since they put him to sleep, they weren't
planning to kill him right off the bat.
First, let's see what exactly happened to Asta.
A Town in the Common Realm, Nean
Damn it, you old hag! This is the third time!
The third time?
That's how many times Marie's
been put in danger!
First was when these assholes took her!
Then it was the trial, and now this!
The third time's the charm!
Now I'm gonna kill you!
Gauche! You shouldn't be
so rough with the elderly!
You can shut your mouth!
This isn't even about seniority
anymore! You're just rude!
Even though this happened while I was gone,
I have nothing to say in my defense.
But isn't there something
more important you need to do
before you try to strangle an old lady?
Where's Marie?!
Hey, you! What the hell happened to Marie?!
Y-You're...
Tell me or I'll kill you!
S-Some masked guys calling themselves
the Devil Banishers took Marie...
Who the hell are they?!
I-I have no idea! But they
said something weird...
Quit wasting my time and spit it out!
I think it was, "We must return
the scale that's tilted
toward darkness back to the light."
Scale?!
What is this?
Poison?
Your mixing abilities are quite impressive.
Thank you.
Talk about some creepy-ass masks.
My body... Crap! I'm gonna di...
That's it.
Well, they sure fell for a lame-ass trick.
Thinking back,
their spells weren't that powerful.
Maybe they did that so the other
Black Bulls wouldn't sense their mana.
That's probably why Henry
didn't wake up, too.
Come on, Yami! Knock that off!
Not only did these assholes attack
my hideout while I was gone,
they took one of my squad members, too.
I don't know who the hell they are,
but they sure wanted to test my patience.
Wh-What's that sound?
Chairman Damnatio, what was that sound?
Does no one in the Black Bulls
know how to use a door?
Where's Marie?
Marie? Did something happen to your sister?
Don't give me that!
I know you took her again!
You must be joking.
You're really gonna act like you don't know?
I'm not acting, but...
Considering everything you
just did, you must be judged.
You two should move back.
Yes, sir.
This is what he did last time.
Scale Magic: Scale Regulate.
You were imprisoned once.
Looks like I'll have to send
you back to that life.
Just try it, you bastard!
Mirror Magic: Reflect Ray!
Chairman Damnatio!
Mirror Magic: Real Double!
He created a clone of himself with a mirror?
Too bad for you! I saw your
stupid magic at the trial.
Don't think we'll fall for that again.
It appears you've underestimated me.
On your knees!
Wh-What the hell?!
Seize them.
Y-Yes, sir!
Looks like you've been taking
good care of my squad once again.
Look, I know how much you hate him,
but isn't this kinda out of the blue?
Also, who gave you permission
to use my wheels?
Wheels...
Do you know how much mana I had to
waste to come here because of that?
Didn't he just say it was easy as pie earlier?
Why did you do this?
Because mole-chin over there took Marie again!
Enough.
Then who the hell did it?!
I know those masked bastards said,
"We must return the scale that's tilted
toward darkness back to the light."
That's exactly the kind of bullshit you'd say!
Did you just say "masked bastards"?
And what if I did?!
You did, didn't you?
I didn't see... I didn't see them myself, but...
What?! It wasn't just Marie?!
We managed to get the kid back, but Nero was...
So it was you!
I cannot fathom how you
came to that conclusion.
First Marie, then Asta and Nero...
They're the three that you put on trial!
You were just trying to take
them out by force this time!
Hell, I don't even care what
you do to Asta and Nero!
Uh, hello?!
Give Marie back!
Marx, show them my memories.
Very well.
Once my innocence is proven, you will
pay dearly for your insolence toward me.
There's no memory that suggests
he knew about the kidnapping.
It appears my innocence has been proven.
Not only did you do all of this,
but you accused me of kidnapping.
You will be taking responsibility for that.
Fine. Do whatever you want with me.
But it's gonna have to wait until I save Marie.
I don't believe that was part of our deal.
Hold it.
That guy you were arguing
with doesn't seem to be here.
Is he so careless that he wouldn't
even show up after all this ruckus?
Lord Julius.
What's the matter?
Sorry to butt in when things are so crazy,
but there's something I'd like
Yami and the others to see.
Now's not the time...
He should be there at any moment.
Begging your pardon.
Nozel!
The signal
is from the bracelet-type
communication magic item
that we used to track Asta's
whereabouts at all times.
There currently seems to be a signal from
the town of Tiulyu in the Common Realm.
Which means...
Someone took it off of him?
The only ones who know about the bracelet
are the few who were present back then.
And the only one I can think of who
could actually get it off is Nero.
She's probably trying to use the
bracelet to let us know where she is.
Then there's a good chance
Marie's in that town, too. Fin—
Finral, let's go!
I'm sorry, but I've never been to Tiulyu.
Tch. Then I guess we're gonna
have to use our brooms.
Captain!
I'll be going, too.
My best friend's little sister
is basically my little sister.
What?! Who are you calling
your little sister?!
Please wait! This may be a trap.
Shut up, you stupid mushroom!
Mush—?!
I don't care if it's a damn trap.
It's the only clue we have!
Gauche's right. We're going.
Wait.
I'm not done talking to that criminal over there.
What?!
Read the room, you asshole!
While we're wasting time here,
my squad members are—
Yami...
I ordered the Black Bulls to
keep an eye on Nero, did I not?
And?
The Devil Banishers, was it?
I'll need you to get her back from that
group and continue watching over her.
So I'd like you to postpone
your judgment until then.
What do you say, Damnatio?
Understood.
Well, I'm counting on you, Yami.
Right.
Oh, one more thing.
You're still not done?
I know you probably don't feel great
since one of your own has been kidnapped.
But this is different from the trial.
Depending on what you do, you may be
putting your squad members in danger.
I know that.
Well, let's go, dumbasses.
Right.
I'll go, too.
Wha?
Nozel?
Nozel, why are you helping us this much?
I'd rather not lose any of the forces needed
to eliminate the devil over
something like this. That is all.
You're just worried about your
little sister, aren't ya?
Stop trying to act all cool, Mr. Hubris.
Say another word and you'll
regret it, foreigner.
Didn't you just say something about
not wanting to lose any of our forces?
That must be it.
Tiulyu Town
This town...
The Eye of the Midnight Sun must
have come through here, too.
Wait for me, Marie!
This is...
What's up?
Oh, is this another magic item that
blocks mana tracking, like this one?
I doubt we'll have to worry about anyone
tracking us out here, but just in case.
It appears they're doing what
they can to block the signal.
Did they find the bracelet?
They might have. Either way,
we should be cautious.
I don't think we had to
land this far away, though.
Are you stupid?
What?!
It's not just Marie and Nero over there.
Their kidnappers are with them, too.
What do you think will happen
if we just suddenly show up?
Gauche...
Yes?
You got a picture of your sister?
What do you plan to do with it?!
Don't get any weird ideas!
We need it so we can ask around!
True...
You better give them back when you're done!
Right...
You never know what's gonna happen.
Always watch your back.
Don't go into the town alone.
Looks like the G-G Duo's back!
I don't remember teaming up with you.
There's no need to be embarrassed.
Let's go, Noelle.
Right!
So that leaves me with...
You got a problem with me?
A-Absolutely not.
It seems mostly untouched.
There are only so many forces we can
send to help with their restoration.
Looks like the damage here
was pretty heavy, and yet...
Yami...
Yeah... I wonder how many
more graves popped up
after the Eye of the Midnight Sun attacked.
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Devil Banishers
Devil Banishers.
We're gonna get Nero and
Marie back no matter what!
From those guys...
Uh, I think they were called...
Devil Tooth-Pullers!
Banishers.
Devil Stabbers!
Devil Fourth-Hitters!
Banishers.
Devil Night Train Passengers!
Devil Newspaper Reporters!
Banishers!
Devil Publishers!
Axed
For the love of... Banishers!
Devil Banishers!
I'm telling y—Hey, you got it.
Though I despise the devil,
this country needs Asta's help.
Next time on Black Clover, Page 144:
"Those Who Wish for the Devil's Demise."
Page 144
Those Who Wish for the Devil's Demise
Someone is trying to disturb
the balance we have in place.