The Clover Kingdom.
In this kingdom where magic is everything,
there is one boy who can't use magic.
His name is Asta.
He puts in blood, sweat, and tears
in hopes of becoming the Wizard King.
But there are also those in the kingdom
who possess at least a little bit of mana,
yet can barely use any magic at all.
The very few out of the population,
those who live in the shadows...
They are also trying to survive.
Those Who Wish for the Devil's Demise
I-Is that a no?
Wh-What did you say? I couldn't hear you.
Are you sure I'm good enough?
Of course! Dazu, I...
I want you to be my wife.
You're so hardworking, Dazu.
Mother.
You don't even use magic,
but you still manage to do just
as much work as the rest of us.
Yami...
Yeah... I wonder how many
more graves popped up
after the Eye of the Midnight Sun attacked.
H-Hey there, miss...
There's something we'd like to ask you.
What's that?
Have you seen this girl before?
Also, did you happen to see a really cute
girl with horns growing out of her head?
Horns? What do you mean?
Then...
Maybe you've heard something
about a group of people who
hate devils getting together?
Is there anyone who doesn't hate the devil?
You're talking about what caused
the tragedy here recently, right?
Yeah.
You're Magic Knights, aren't you?
My husband and his mother died that day.
Why didn't you come to help us?
We were stretched too thin ourselves.
The whole kingdom was a mess...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry we couldn't protect your family.
If you'll excuse me.
That silver hair and cross...
They must be from the Silva family.
What are royals doing here?
Hey, don't stare so much.
Hey, I have a question.
Have you seen this girl?
Huh? I, uh...
She's really cute.
We're looking for her and another
girl with horns on her head.
If you've seen them, tell me.
What do you mean by horns?
So you haven't seen them? Okay, then.
R-Right...
Hey, I have a question for you.
Huh?
Have you seen this girl?
No, I haven't. Please excuse me.
Take a closer look!
Sorry, I'm a bit busy.
My house was destroyed,
and I have to rebuild it.
I just have so much to do.
Wait!
Don't chase them.
Nozel...
The people of this town...
They're not making it obvious,
but many of them hold a grudge
against the Magic Knights
and resent how the kingdom has handled things.
I can't blame them.
When this town was in danger,
we couldn't do anything for them.
You're right...
We won't be able to get any useful
information by being forceful.
But if we don't hurry, Nero and Marie will be...
We are indeed in a hurry, but no
good ever came out of panicking.
If you're a true Magic Knight, you need
to remain calm in these situations.
Right...
Questioning them isn't the only thing
we can do. Let's try something else.
Right!
Marie!
Hey! What are you doing?
You're not Marie...
What are you trying to do to my daughter?
Sorry!
But I'm a bit desperate here!
I have to back him up since he's
my partner in the G-G Duo!
Please forgive us. You can have this, okay?
Stay away from my daughter, you creeps!
Try not to mistake someone
else for Marie again.
Shut your trap!
If I sense it might be Marie, I'm going to act!
Damn it! Marie!
Where are you?! My angel Marie! Answer me!
You can't shout like that!
You called?
The hell?
You just called my name.
And you called me an angel.
No one's ever called me that,
even when I was younger.
What the hell are you yapping
about, you old hag?
Um, what is your name?
My name's Maggie.
We're looking for Marie!
Oh, my. I guess that's different.
So close...
Something must've happened.
Yes.
We can talk down below.
Welcome back, Dazu.
Good work out there.
Thank you.
How long are we going to hide down here?
We should just execute these two already.
There's an even bigger
problem on our hands now.
The Magic Knights are here.
What?
Did they track us?
No, that's not possible.
Master Kabwe's transparency spell
made us disappear flawlessly.
Maybe they planted something...
Transparency Magic: Detection Decoder.
There it is!
This is...
A magic item to keep tabs
on one who is devil-possessed!
What's it doing here?
Curses! How underhanded!
Please wait.
I have an idea.
Hey, did you guys get any information?
The townspeople wouldn't
tell us anything useful.
We tried to find somewhere they'd use as
a hideout, but nothing has turned up.
I'm trying to track mana,
but can't pinpoint a target.
And...
The signal still seems unstable.
On top of that, we don't know when they'll
notice that communication magic item.
We need to find those two
before they find it.
What about you two?
We were talking with an old woman.
She wasn't so bad.
Why the hell did you two even come here?
I'm serious about this!
I'm just doing whatever will find those
assholes who took Marie the fastest!
What's up, Bangs?
They're on the move.
Where?!
Did they let down their defense?
I'm not sure, but this is weird.
I'm sure they realize we're in town.
This could be a diversion.
All right. Gordon and I will
investigate this town a bit more.
You guys can borrow my wheels.
Very well. That'll make
getting back somewhat easier.
Even Captain Nozel's using
me as an errand boy?!
Get on. We're going after them.
That worked like a charm.
This should buy us some time.
Curse those Magic Knights.
During the attack by the
Eye of the Midnight Sun,
many of the Magic Knights
had their bodies taken over
and contributed to the
destruction of this kingdom.
They're absolutely unforgivable!
You're exactly right.
The Magic Knights only defend each other.
We mean nothing to them!
Let's show them the true meaning of justice!
Of course.
We're standing up for the
rights of our fellow citizens,
and to regain peace and
harmony in this kingdom.
Now... In order to exact our justice,
let us execute these two servants
of the devil immediately.
Agreed!
We'll put their corpses on
display and show the world
the Magic Knights' negligence,
arrogance, and deceit!
There's no future in this kingdom for
the Magic Knights who aid the devils!
Exactly! From now on, we will be the ones
who maintain the peace and
tranquility of the Clover Kingdom!
I think we should hold off on the executions.
How can you say that right now?!
I feel exactly the same way as all of you.
I cannot forgive anyone
who sides with the devil.
But if we hang on to those two,
we'll be able to lure out the
devil-possessed boy, Asta.
Wouldn't the masses side more with
Master Kabwe if we disposed
of all three of them at once?
True. If we use them as bait,
the Black Bulls should act.
Asta the Devil-Possessed...
He's who we're really after.
True...
We might as well call Asta a devil himself.
We cannot exact justice until we execute him.
Yes, you're exactly right.
Now, let us figure out a way to capture Asta.
Let me think...
They stopped moving.
There's no one here?
In there.
Marie!
We've come to save you! Answer me!
This is...
They put one over on us.
Then Nero and Marie are...
Damn it!
We'll regroup with Yami and Gordon
and return to the royal capital for now.
We need to rethink our plan.
It'll be okay.
Do you think this will all work out?
Everything's been working out
for us ever since that day.
It's all thanks to you, Bow.
No, it's not.
If I hadn't met you, my life wouldn't
be going anywhere right now.
If I didn't have you,
I would've felt nothing but despair
at everything in this world.
You can do it. Because you're my hope.
I'm sure this will all work
out with you by my side, Bow.
What? Where am I?
Are you awake?
This is a breakroom in the palace.
Owen...
That's right! Nero was...
Hey, wait!
You need to confirm what's going on
before you go runnin' off like that, kid.
Yes, sir!
I managed to rid your body of the drug
they used on you, so you can go now.
Thank you!
So those guys called the Devil
Panickers took Nero and Marie?
The Devil Banishers. You were
almost taken yourself.
You saved me, didn't you?
Thanks a bunch, Noelle!
I-It's not like I was trying to save you.
It's just that those weirdos were
doing something that seemed odd...
But I wasn't able to protect Nero.
That's not your fault! It's because I
wasn't strong enough that Nero was...
There's no point in talking about that now.
Since we got Owen's okay,
you guys head back to the hideout.
No! I'm going out to look for them right now!
Didn't you hear a word we just said?
We don't have any clues right now,
so we have no way of finding them.
That's right!
I'm counting on you.
Where are you going, Yami?
A captain's gotta do his
captainly duties sometimes.
Oh, yeah.
I already warned him myself,
but if Gauche decides to freak out,
use force if necessary to stop him.
I don't care how, as long as
he's still breathing some. Got it?
Okay...
Everyone is here.
The Golden Dawn and Aqua Deer
are securing our borders.
The Coral Peacocks and Purple Orcas
are aiding in the restoration
of high-priority locations.
We can't just abandon those duties right now.
So if we can solve this with everyone
who's here right now, it'd be for the best.
There's something I'd like to say first.
There is a high likelihood that my
subordinates orchestrated this whole thing.
And because of that, I will
offer you any information I can.
Are you all okay with that?
Our top priority right now is to
take back the two who were taken.
We can investigate your
subordinates' involvement later.
Yes, you're right.
Chairman Damnatio, if you would fill us in.
The first is Kabwe Carillon, 38 years old.
He uses transparency magic that allows
him and those around him to disappear.
But unlike the former Captain of the
Purple Orcas, he cannot conceal his mana.
The second is Onoby Sinho, 31 years old.
He uses barrier magic that allows him to
put up a barrier with a radius
about five times his height.
If anyone tries to forcefully destroy
this barrier, it will explode.
The third is Siona Caverly, 29 years old.
She is a paper magic user who
can control any thickness
and length of paper at will.
None of them sound like
they're worth slicing up.
We don't know for sure if they're involved
with the Devil Banishers just yet.
Once we get proof they're involved,
you can slice them up all you want,
but for now, help us figure out how we're
gonna save those girls, Beanpole Monster.
The Black Bull who has been captured
possesses arcane stage magic.
Since she stands a chance against the devil,
she is key in our strategy to fight it.
We cannot lose her.
The other captive is also an
important citizen of this kingdom.
We must get her back unharmed.
Great thing to say, Prickly Queen.
You're way smarter than
a certain beanpole we know.
Shut up.
Yami praised me! Wait, now's not
the time to be happy about that.
Even if it was an ambush, it's hard to believe
that Asta would let someone who's
not a fighter get the best of him.
Well, they used a method he's
never had to deal with before.
They used a sleeping potion on Asta.
Well, that's pretty dirty.
Our kid's trained, so he can dispel
any spells if he's attacked by magic
and smack anyone back if
they physically hit him.
So basically, he's only fought people
face-to-face up until now, so that was fine.
It would appear they have someone
rather intelligent in their ranks.
There is also the fact that they
used that magic item against us.
So those guys call themselves
the Devil Banishers.
They want to get rid of the devil, don't they?
Yes.
So why haven't they offed their captives
already? I'm sure they've had the chance.
If we assume my subordinates are
indeed involved in this matter...
Among the three, Kabwe has an
extremely strong sense of justice,
and after the incident with
the Eye of the Midnight Sun,
he grew to hate the devil even more.
He was quite exasperated
that the execution of the
devil-possessed had been delayed.
Then wouldn't he kill them even quicker?
Why would they bother wasting
time with sleeping potions?
I'm sure they had their reasons.
Like what?
If Kabwe is leading them,
he would much prefer this be an actual
execution rather than an assassination.
I'm sure he will try to take
their lives in front of
the masses in the name of justice.
So that he can gain the approval of the masses
and justify his own brand of justice.
So he fancies himself a revolutionary.
That seems like a rather effective
way to carry out their goal.
Tch. Man, these assholes are a pain.
But going with that assumption, it's very
likely the captives are still alive.
Yeah.
If they actually carried out
a public execution...
I'm sure there are citizens who
would agree with their justice.
Even I have seen those who are unhappy
with this kingdom's governance
ever since the attack by the
Eye of the Midnight Sun.
The wounds from that attack have yet to heal.
People still remember how
fearsome the devil was.
If this keeps going, there might be an
uprising caused by a large group of rebels.
We must prepare for the imminent threat
from outside our kingdom right now,
so we need to do everything
we can to avoid conflict within.
That's just another reason we need
to put an end to their schemes.
If they're going to go through
with this public execution,
they will appear before us.
What's important is what we do then.
Yes. I'd like you all to proceed with caution.
There's still something off about all of this.
It feels like we might be overlooking something.
The City of Lehart
At noon today, we will be executing two of the devil's servants
Execution?! Like hell I'm
ever gonna let that happen!
I'll personally send anyone
who scares Marie to hell!
Next time on Black Clover,
Page 145: "Rescue."
Page 145
Rescue
Your brother's coming for you, my angel!