The Clover Kingdom.
In this kingdom where magic is everything,
there is one boy who can't use magic.
His name is Asta.
He puts in blood, sweat, and tears
in hopes of becoming the Wizard King.
But there are also those in the kingdom
who possess at least a little bit of mana,
yet can barely use any magic at all.
The very few out of the population,
those who live in the shadows...
They are also trying to survive.
Where am I? What am I doing here?
That's right! I—
I see you're awake.
You're... one of Asta and
Big Brother's friends.
Yes.
Though I wish we could escape,
our mana has been sealed.
The magic item I borrowed from Asta to let
people know of our location is gone, too.
Where are we? Who are those people?
The only thing we have in common is that
we were suspected of being servants
of the devil at the trial.
They're probably trying to take
advantage of that somehow.
This is all for the sake of justice.
Indeed, Master Kabwe.
We must rid this world of the devil's
servants who brought destruction
and chaos to this kingdom.
No matter what it takes.
Rescue
The City of Lehart
There are so many people.
The Devil Banishers are the bringers
of justice we've been waiting for!
Bring death to servants of the devil!
Yeah!
Let there be blood!
I can't wait!
This is...
How dare they do that to
my angel?! I'll kill them all!
Damn. Looks like they're having fun.
I-I'm scared...
Nero, Marie, we're here to save you!
We've got a message from Julius, guys.
Looks like all the squads are ready.
It's almost noon,
when the Devil Banishers said
they'd execute them.
We don't know how many
enemies we're dealing with,
and we expect them to use
various drugs as well as magic.
This will probably prove difficult,
but I'd like you to do everything
you can to save the captured.
First, the Silver Eagles
and the Crimson Lion Kings
will help with the rescue and protect
the civilians who have gathered.
The Blue Rose Knights and the Green
Praying Mantises will patrol the square.
And the core squad that will save the
hostages will be the Black Bulls.
You got it. By the way,
there seems to be someone here who
has nothing to do with the plan.
He may be here because he feels some guilt,
considering his subordinates are behind this,
but we can't just have him acting on his own.
The rescue is our primary objective.
Are you willing to go along with our plan?
That was my intention.
But I'd like to confirm something.
If Asta uses the powers of the
devil in front of the masses,
he will only bring more confusion and chaos.
I ask that...
He not use it for this plan, right?
No shit.
Listen up, dumbasses.
Everyone other than the kid and Gauche,
keep an eye on the square like we planned.
The lives of two of our own are
at stake. Don't let your guard down!
Right!
I'm counting on all of you.
As you requested, we are having the other
squads keep an eye on the Noble Realm.
Well, we must consider that
the execution could be
a ruse to distract us while
they wreak havoc elsewhere.
We must make sure this plan is
a success, to ensure this incident
doesn't cause greater panic
among the masses.
Yes. Let's have faith in everyone.
So far, we haven't seen anything unusual.
I hope they're able to rescue them safely.
Since Captain Vangeance is away
keeping an eye on the border,
we aren't able to assist in
the main part of this plan.
But be alert for even the smallest detail!
Right.
Ugh, why are we on patrol duty?
You'd be able to beat up any enemy in a flash!
I'm just here to complete my mission.
Hey, wait for me!
It's almost time! The purveyors
of justice will soon arrive!
We can't count on the Magic Parliament
or the Magic Knights!
Our true saviors are the Devil Banishers!
That's right!
Let justice be served!
Those guys are probably
somewhere in this crowd, too.
How are we supposed to find them, though?
Yeah, they've all lost their minds.
Did they use some kind
of weird drug on them all?
Tch. I can't just sit here!
Captain Yami, let me go down there!
Me, too!
Shut up!
You're gonna ruin the plan
if you go down there!
But we can't just sit here!
You're the cornerstone of this plan, kid.
So just sit and wait your damn turn.
Okay...
There's still no sign of them, but...
It's almost noon.
Sis, I don't see anyone suspicious.
Don't let your guard down.
You've got it, Sis.
It's finally time.
Witch...
If you want your friends to live,
you will do as we say.
Do anything rash, and we will kill your
friends before the public execution.
Walk toward the exit.
I knew this was mentioned,
but I really didn't sense their mana.
It'll be okay. I'm sure the others
will be able to save Nero and Marie.
All right.
Here they come.
To all who despise the devil...
The time to strike in the
name of justice as arrived.
We are the Devil Banishers!
We are the ones who wish for the devil's demise!
Marie!
Nero!
Calm your asses down.
So it does appear that they can prevent
their mana from being detected.
Looks like the only ones using
the items are those three.
Behold this woman's horns!
This is solid proof that she sold her soul
to the devil and used forbidden magic.
How mortifying.
She's the devil herself.
The little girl next to her became a servant
of the devil along with her brother,
who is a former criminal.
We know it's the undeniable truth
that they have harmed many!
Look at that innocent, harmless expression!
Just execute them already!
Let us have our justice!
She should've been executed before!
L-Lord Damnatio, if that
barrier spell explodes,
many civilians will be harmed.
Kabwe... Does your justice involve
risking the lives of innocent people?
That spell is probably the work
of Mole Chin Scales' subordinates.
But we mustn't forget that
there is one possessed by the devil whom
we must hate even more than these two.
His name is...
Asta!
Asta, our greatest desire
is to see you executed!
You are the true cause of this chaos!
We know you're here.
Asta?!
It's just like Mister Yami said.
I saw him in the papers!
That peasant is here?!
Like they'd stop any of this
if Asta did come forward.
If you show yourself and
allow us to detain you,
we will let these two go.
Nero! Marie!
What's the matter, Asta?
Is your life more precious
than your friends' after all?
Of course it is!
You evil servant of the devil!
There's no way Asta would
abandon his friends!
Very well. If you refuse to show yourself...
I'm right here!
Now, come here.
I don't see Vanessa, but we don't
have time to find her right now.
You accursed devil-possessed!
Everyone, he's the one who
messed up this country!
How dare you ruin my family?!
Kill him!
Execute him!
We don't serve the devil!
Shut up, you devil!
Halt.
Give them your grimoire.
Did that ruin your plans?
We know that you hope to undo
the barrier with your anti-magic.
What's the matter?
Hurry up and give it to him!
You're gonna free Nero and Marie, right?
Yes. We already established that.
Then put down your swords
and step away from them.
Very well.
Now, give us your grimoire.
All right.
Wha—
There's...
another Asta?!
We were waiting for you to
look away from the hostages!
Dark Magic: Dark Cloaked Lightless Slash!
Th-That was so scary!
Sleeping potion...
That's not gonna work anymore!
Paper Magic: Dagger-Folding
Early Summer Rain!
Nero! Marie!
Not happening!
There!
Hup.
Sis!
Let's go!
Things are getting interesting.
Save me!
Our comrades will buy us some time.
Transparency Magic: Share the Same Fate!
Nero! Marie!
Hold it!
You're in the way. Move!
Kid, where are ya?!
A drug?
Water Magic: Sea Dragon's Lair!
What's going on? My magic control is...
It's closing in!
Finral! Where's Marie?
Asta went after her.
I was going to chase after them,
but this smoke is affecting
my sight, and my magic is...
The trap spells I set up throughout
the square aren't responding.
Looks like there's something in
this smoke that disrupts mana.
Those dirty little...
Way to go, Mister Yami!
The smoke's no match for him!
Go help evacuate the masses.
On your knees.
Begone!
They're gone...
Where are you taking me?
Nowhere.
Our mission was to get you away from
the square since you have magic
that can change fate in your favor.
I see... But even without changing fate,
I know my friends have rescued the hostages.
I guess I don't have to listen to you anymore.
We know we can't defeat you.
We also know they'll read our
memories if we're captured.
Our job is done.
We're willing to risk our lives for this plan.
No... They just took their own lives.
This plan is that important to them?
I can feel their ki over here.
You're finished.
You followed us without realizing
that we wanted you to come.
Put your grimoire here.
If you resist, these girls will die.
Asta...
Don't worry. I'll save you.
What could you possibly do
without the powers of the devil?
Now, Master Kabwe, let's take
them before the others arrive.
No, we'll take care of them here.
B-But that's not according to plan.
The Magic Knights are far more
powerful than I anticipated.
We were lucky everything went well so far,
but if we want to succeed,
our only chance is now.
B-But...
You coward! Why are you so scared?
Wha—
You'll pay for your insolence!
Y-You bastard!
Nero!
You accursed devil-possessed!
If you dodge, these will hit the little girl!
Paper Magic: Dagger-Folding
Early Summer Rain!
What?
So you must be the Devil Banishers.
Yuno?! What are you doing here?
We just happened to be patrolling
the area and wandered by.
Pure coincidence.
This is slightly outside of our mission,
but Captain Vangeance did say to patrol.
Are you all right, Asta?!
Yeah. But more importantly,
take care of Nero.
How dare you?!
We almost got our hands on Asta!
We can't get caught here.
Give Nero back!
Come any closer and the girl dies.
Uh, wait. You're running away?
You can't be serious.
A devil resides in the
five-leaf-clover grimoire...
We'll be taking this.
Hold it!
Asta...
Damn it!
Asta!
Mimosa, check on Marie.
Right!
They stole his grimoire...
How vile could they be?
You still have magic you can use even
if they take your grimoire, right?
Yuno?
What are you...
Yeah.
Not giving up is my magic!
I'm gonna get Nero and my grimoire back!
Marie!
Don't die, Marie!
It's too soon for you to become a real angel!
Don't leave me behind!
According to Owen, she'll need a
little more time before she wakes up.
So Marie's okay?!
Yes.
I see...
Looks like I owe you again.
Today, it became clear that my subordinates
are involved in this matter.
First, let me apologize for
my lack of supervision.
You said they had a strong sense of justice,
but they took the crowd hostage.
That's nothing more than playing dirty.
Perhaps he's being fooled and
manipulated by the enemy?
Stealing Asta's grimoire could
be someone else's intent, too.
You're here at this meeting now,
but you weren't here earlier, were you?
After you cried and swore your
loyalty to the boss, too.
Sorry, Yami. I'm the one who
asked him to watch the borders.
The worst thing that could happen right now
is for the Spade Kingdom to make a move.
Everyone, please look at this.
Looking through the memories of
the Devil Banishers we captured
tells us that most of them were paid hires.
I apologize for interrupting,
but this is urgent.
What's going on?
W-Well, we received a message from Kabwe.
What?
Kabwe?
Where are you?
They... aren't after the demise of the devil.
They're actually... trying to
gain the powers of the devil.
What?
They are those who worship the devil...
The Devil Believers!
Thank goodness you're
all right, my angel Marie!
But this isn't over!
Next time on Black Clover, Page 146:
"Those Who Worship the Devil."
Page 146
Those Who Worship the Devil
I won't be satisfied until
I beat the crap out of them!