Um... Pardon me.
You made all these? That's amazing!
It's really not a big deal.
No, really. You're amazing, Bow!
Thank you, Dazu.
That's about all the magic I have.
You really are amazing, Bow!
Thanks for having me over.
It was a pleasure.
Well, see you...
Right...
Um...
If you wouldn't mind...
May I come over again?
Would you come over again?
Yes.
There we go. All that's left is...
Could you take over for a moment?
And to finish it off... a pinch
of moguro leaf powder.
Slower, gentler... Okay?
All right...
There we go.
Now they won't get chapped so easily.
Thank you, Bow.
Here.
I'll do it, too.
There you go.
Thank you, Dazu.
What happened?
They did this. They asked
to see my catalyst magic.
They only wanted to see me fail and laugh at me.
He almost looked worried
and asked, "Are you okay?"
But I know he was laughing on the inside.
They're all like that. They're all the same.
But you're different!
And so are you.
Ow...
Endure it. It'll get better soon enough.
Thank you.
It's fine.
Are you all right?
Yes.
I always thought I was alone.
But I'm not alone.
I lived in a world where the sun didn't shine.
We were weak and fleeting...
But we definitely existed.
Becoming the Light That Shines Through the Darkness
Breed Mountain
Ugh, you're late!
Wait, you mean our backup is...
I was basically the fastest one to get here.
Thanks!
But damn...
Who knew there were this many of them now?
Heya, Devil Believers.
Why don't we have a little chat?
Chat?
There's nothing to talk about.
Aw, don't be like that.
Is that a Magic Knights Squad captain?
Does he want to capture us?
But we're right at the border.
N-No! I don't want to get caught!
I'm going to the Spade Kingdom!
Yeah!
Let's go!
You won't catch us!
Let's all go to the Spade Kingdom!
Hey, now... We didn't come to nab all of—
We should hurry, too.
Yes.
Come on!
Ow...
Noelle!
Nero!
Hold it!
It's no use.
But...
No matter. We still have the five-leaf grimoire.
As long as we still have this...
Captain Yami!
Hold out your hands.
Our hands?
Mister Yami, shouldn't we stop them?
No need to hurry.
See? Here they come.
Looks like two pretty little
birdies have arrived.
Huh?
Captain Fuegoleon!
And the pleasantly plump spatial door guy!
Nozel!
Looks like we made it in time.
Devil Believers...
We would like all of you to listen to us!
Why would we listen to Magic Knights?
Everyone, send all of your mana to me!
Concentrate!
To Dazu!
Looks like they're not going
to listen. That's not surprising.
I'm sure they feel nothing but distrust for us.
What?
Come on, now...
Her catalyst magic most likely affects
the mana in the surrounding area, too.
And we're right next to a strong magic region.
That must've summoned a
magic beast from there.
Thanks for the explanation, bud.
So...
Now what?
I had the power to summon that monster.
If I have that much power...
Dazu!
Flame Magic: Exploding Fireball!
You okay?!
Y-Yes...
Sealing Magic: Closed Sorrow.
My wounds...
They weren't after the grimoire?
They came to save us?
Flame Magic: Ignis Columna!
Mercury Magic: Silver Bullets!
Dark Magic: Dark Cloaked Lightless Slash!
Mercury Magic: Silver Shining Regal Spear!
Flame Spirit Magic: Salamander's Breath!
Dark Magic: Dark Cloaked Black Blade!
Well, that's that.
Th-They're so strong...
So these are...
...the Magic Knights?
Even though... I collected
mana from so many of them...
It's over...
And we came so far.
You saw how strong they are.
We can't escape.
What kind of punishment will we get?
Guys...
I think you've got the wrong idea here.
We didn't come here to apprehend you.
We just came to talk to you.
Talk?
Roger-dodger-roger!
Hey, that's... Wait...
Is he the Golden...
...Hero, William...
...Vangeance?!
Those who live in the shadows...
Heya, "Hero."
Thanks for coming out this far.
I'll do anything for this kingdom.
That is my atonement.
But you know...
Did you have to show up
with Mister No Fun Scales?
Arcane stage girl.
I'm glad you're safe.
We don't intend to punish you.
It appears that you're heading
toward the Spade Kingdom,
but you haven't crossed the border yet,
which means you haven't
committed a crime yet.
But...
If we just asked you to go home
from here, I'm sure you'd refuse.
We Magic Knights understand your situation.
So please, could you give us a bit of time?
We will try to get rid of your doubts.
But...
We can't trust them.
Why would they care how we feel?
They're all royalty and nobles...
That's not—
Well, as you can see,
we do have some royal and noble
elites in the Magic Knights,
but it's not as if we're all like that.
I mean, my squad has a former convict,
someone who got kicked out of their home,
a loner, a guy who was disowned by his family,
someone who's been alone for a really long time,
and we've even got some peasants.
Also, I'm a foreigner.
When I first drifted to this kingdom,
I couldn't speak your language
and was totally ostracized.
So I get where you guys are coming from.
What pushed you over the edge
are your differences and the
discrimination you've faced.
We must apologize for how powerless
we've been to help you thus far.
Nozel...
I swear upon the House of Vermillion...
I will do everything I can to rid this world
of these differences and discrimination.
Please go back to your homes and wait
for the day we fulfill our promise.
We will shine the light known
as hope upon the darkness.
Lord Vangeance...
Your face...
I am the same as you.
I have faced discrimination
because of this face.
But the current Wizard King,
Julius Novachrono,
did not care how I looked and took me in.
He accepted me for who I was.
He gave me a place to belong.
Lord Julius saved me.
And now, it's our turn.
We will create a place for you to stay.
A place where the sun shines.
So please, once... Just once...
I ask that you believe in us.
The Magic Knights...
If they're saying that they'll support us...
Maybe just once...
Yeah, just once...
Let's believe in them.
Yeah.
Now, then.
Dazu Tayak, Bow Nocde, and other
leaders of the Devil Believers.
You are a separate matter.
You kidnapped two girls.
Instigated a riot in the royal capital.
And...
Kabwe Carillon, Onoby Sinho,
and Siona Caverly of the Magic Parliament.
You are suspected of killing those three.
Well, you heard him.
You must be judged.
You have committed severe crimes.
If we're just going to get
arrested and be punished...
Then I'll blow you all away!
Don't waste your time.
But we came so far...
Dazu...
Dazu.
Who said anything about arresting you?
Arrest you and punish you?
How naïve.
I told you. I'm going to judge you.
Therefore, you are hereby...
exiled from this kingdom.
Roger-dodger-roger!
Leave the Clover Kingdom immediately.
Dazu...
We will decide
where we go.
No one can decide our path for us.
Do as you please.
Does that mean...
Asta...
That's my...
H-Hey!
I'm going to be the Wizard King someday.
And as the Wizard King,
I want to create a free kingdom
where everyone can understand
each other and laugh together.
I promise you, so please...
No matter where you go, even if it's from afar,
please keep an eye on us.
I wish...
I could've been like you.
I'm sorry. Please tell that little girl, Marie, as well.
We have no grimoire and no hostages.
We are the only ones left.
The chances of us getting through
the strong magic region and making
it to the Spade Kingdom are...
But even so, I'm...
Let's go.
Right.
Yes.
We will go. We will leave
the Clover Kingdom. But...
If this kingdom is unable to change...
Someone else will take our place.
They'll appear from the shadows, over and over.
Bow...
Dazu...
Returning the scales that
have tipped toward darkness
back to the light.
Isn't that right, Kabwe?
All of the scales in this kingdom shall be...
Let's go.
Yes.
I have committed a sin.
Many sins.
I killed my husband and his mother.
They were scum.
On the inside, they were laughing
and looking down on me.
But they never said anything to suggest
that or let it show on their faces.
So I could've continued
pretending not to know.
But...
Dear! Mother! Hang in there!
H-Hurry and help us...
Hurry up, you stupid...
Good-for-nothing wench.
Dazu...
You two can just...
Die.
I don't regret letting those two die.
Because that's what they deserved.
The burn scar that he gave
me should fade over time.
But the scars on my heart from
enduring their ridicule for so long
will never go away.
Above all, even after they died,
the vengeful flames that burn in my heart
can never be extinguished.
I... We...
will make it to the Spade
Kingdom, no matter what.
So that we can obtain the powers of the devil.
This kingdom is still embroiled in chaos.
The threat of the devil
draws near from the outside.
Next time on Black Clover, Page 149:
"Two Things We Need to Find."
Page 149
Two Things We Need to Find
It's always darkest before the dawn...
Isn't that right, my prince?