The Clover Kingdom.
In this kingdom where magic is everything,
there is one boy who can't use magic.
His name is Asta.
He puts in blood, sweat, and tears
in hopes of becoming the Wizard King.
But there are also those in the kingdom
who possess at least a little bit of mana,
yet can barely use any magic at all.
The very few out of the population,
those who live in the shadows...
They are also trying to survive.
My prince, I've brought your tea.
It's completely cold by now.
Secré? How long have you been there?
How long do you think?
Sorry, I didn't see you.
It doesn't bother me.
This happens all the time.
Take a look at this.
"First, a magic item that
stores and splits mana."
So what's this one do?
It's a magic item that increases mana!
Like the elves' magic stones, basically.
Ah...
There aren't many of them,
but this kingdom does have people
who weren't blessed with mana.
But once this is complete, we should
be able to resolve their concerns.
Huh?
Yes, and this should end the
discrimination that currently exists.
But there are a few problems
I need to take care of first.
Ah, it makes my head hurt...
My prince thought about the future
of this kingdom more than anyone else.
But...
The burn scar that he gave
me should fade over time.
But the scars on my heart from
enduring their ridicule for so long
will never go away.
Above all, even after they died,
the vengeful flames that burn in my heart
can never be extinguished.
I...
will make it to the Spade
Kingdom, no matter what.
So that we can obtain the powers of the devil.
The reason she wanted the devil's powers
and caused this whole incident
was because she was born with very
little mana and suffered discrimination.
Maybe this kingdom hasn't changed
that much in the past 500 years.
Two Things We Need to Find
I'm sure you can guess why
I summoned you all here today.
I wanted to ask you some questions regarding
the incident with the Devil Believers.
Ask us anything.
Right, kid?
Sure?!
All right, then, let's get started. First...
Could you tell me what
you talked about that day
with one of the leaders of the
Devil Believers, Dazu Tayak?
The difference in mana... Those blessed
with abundant mana and those who aren't.
There's no doubt that the gap between
those two is what caused this incident.
Discrimination is something
we must get rid of at any cost.
Is there something up with Nero?
Oh, it's nothing.
Pardon me.
Lord Julius, we just received
a message from Queen Loropechika
of the Heart Kingdom.
Loropechika
Huh?
So she's the Queen of the Heart Kingdom.
You three...
We just happened to be
summoned by the Wizard King.
I see.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
You must be the Captain of
the Black Bulls, Yami Sukehiro.
Hey, nice to meet you.
I guess she really does know about me.
You may have gathered why
I'm contacting you today.
As I mentioned to you previously,
we were preparing for you to train with
our elite guard, the Spirit Guardians,
and those preparations are now complete.
Are you okay, Loropechika?
What just happened?!
Did something happen to the queen?
What, though?!
Maybe Megicula's curse suddenly advanced?
No!
Finral!
Huh? But...
We'll take care of all the paperwork.
We're counting on you.
Right!
Asta, sorry, but do you
mind if she stays behind?
Huh?
I'm fine with that.
Asta!
I can't keep this open for
long over such a distance...
Hurry!
Okay, I'm off!
It'll probably be easier to speak
with you if you're not in that form.
Could you come with me
to the basement library?
There's something I'd like you to see.
Marx, I expect you to fill out
all the paperwork required
for them to enter the Heart Kingdom.
Huh? Er, yes, of course.
All right, let's go.
Wait, why are we outside the palace?
I think... the queen is generating
a force field made of mana,
so we can't enter the palace.
Spirit Guardian
Gaja
You lot...
I don't know what you're doing here,
but this is clearly unlawful
entry to our kingdom,
unless you can prove otherwise.
W-W-W-Wait!
Our Wizard King will eventually contact you.
Yes... What?
Forms have been submitted from
the Clover Kingdom to allow
entry into our kingdom?
Very well.
Pardon my rudeness.
Allow me to lead you to the queen.
Welcome, everyone.
She seems to be dressed pretty rough
compared to last time...
Even if her clothes are different,
they can't hide her beauty!
She is truly a goddess who has
descended upon this land!
Finral! You're supposed to change, remember?!
By the way, what brings you here today?
Oh, right!
It doesn't look like her curse is acting up...
Is there something about my curse?
Oh, for goodness' sake, Loropechika.
So that's the Water Spirit.
You had a stomachache because
the things you ate for lunch
didn't agree with each other?
I told her not to eat hard bacon
and red spinach together.
But that part of her is adorable, too.
If you will excuse me...
Thanks.
Guess I'll head back, too.
I've got something to do.
Head back? But how?
How do you think?
I'm gonna die...
But thank goodness it wasn't your curse.
As I was trying to tell you earlier,
the preparations for your
training are complete.
And so...
Huh?
What's wrong?
My glasses are missing!
Your glasses?
Wait, you just noticed?!
Wow, her eyesight is...
...shockingly bad?!
Come on, now, Loropechika.
That was your last pair.
I end up stepping on them,
kicking them, dropping them,
H-Huh?
sitting on them... I basically
break my glasses all the time.
And they're custom-made.
In that case, I'll help you find them!
Oh, don't worry. I have an
idea as to where they are.
Huh?
This is...
She's gathering information from all around?
This is only one part of it,
but it should be enough for now.
She's usually watching
over the whole kingdom.
The whole kingdom...
Oh, there they are!
I knew it was Mugi!
Mugi?
Wait, then is that creature—
It's alive?!
Oh, I forgot to introduce you.
This is the thick-pelted beaver,
Big Mugi. She's Mugi's mother.
Mugi comes here often with Big Mugi.
Or you might say they just waltz right in.
Why in the world does she look so smug?
Sh-She's so cute!
The only problem is they're
quite the troublemakers,
and they take my things
without permission sometimes.
All right!
I'll head on over and get your
glasses back from this Mugi!
Huh? But it's okay...
You're gonna be training us soon!
This is nothing!
Oh, fine...
I'm exhausted, so I'm gonna pass.
But wait... If I make a good
impression on the queen...
Wait, no... That's not it, Finral.
This is just another trial to break my curse!
Leave getting your glasses back to us!
Let's go, Asta!
All right, we're off!
So that's the thick-pelted beavers' lodge...
There they are!
Leave it to me!
Spatial Magic: Fallen Angel Gate!
As well as... Fallen Angel's Wingbeat!
Way to go, Finral!
Easy-peasy!
Oh, no! You can't hold them like that!
Are you okay?!
What are you doing?!
You're not getting away!
Perhaps Mugi is finally
getting its just deserts.
Really?
No, I can't!
That thing is seriously pissing me off.
That's just another reason they're so cute.
Looks like it's my turn.
What the heck is he doing?
Huh? He's fishing, isn't he?
Well, that much is obvious!
You'll be giving those back.
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
So that must be
the ki that's commonly used
in the Land of the Sun.
So that's how...
That must be how he found you, even though
I was concealing you and your mana.
Yes.
It doesn't matter if he has anti-magic
or if he's at the arcane stage.
He's going to become stronger.
Let's trade.
Way to go, Asta!
Thank you so much.
Now I can see all of your
faces... clearly... a-again?
Oh, Loropechika...
What?!
Loropechika, is your hand okay? Are you hurt?
I-I'm fine...
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry! What have I done?
Are your eyes actually bad?
Huh?
You could see us just fine
the last time we met.
You see, when Loropechika
is in her royal gown,
she's using Mana Zone, so she
can detect what's around her.
It has nothing to do with
if she can see or not.
You wouldn't need glasses if you
just did that regularly, would you?
My mana isn't infinite.
I want to avoid using up too much of it,
just in case something happens.
Especially considering Loropechika has
a Mana Zone barrier up all around
the Heart Kingdom at all times.
I have returned, Your Majesty.
Oh, perfect timing.
I apologize for keeping you waiting.
It's fine.
Is that...
I went to retrieve the new ones.
Then are all those...
There can never be enough.
Then everything we just went through was...
I'm very sorry. I tried to stop you, but...
This is all your fault.
My fault?!
Oh, yeah. I guess I'm the one
who said we'd get them back.
But I thank you from the bottom of my
heart for doing all of that for me.
Please rely on us whenever you're in need!
Damn it, Finral, no!
Now, let us get back on the topic at hand.
The reason the preparations for
your training took so long...
Um...
Yes?
We're over here.
Oh, I'm terribly sorry about that.
The reason the preparations for
your training took so long...
is so that the Spirit Guardians
could meet you in top form.
But there is also a limit to how
many the Spirit Guardians can train.
All right! I'm getting fired up!
No one said you were going to train yet.
What?!
No, since they're both at the arcane stage,
we need Asta and Nero to participate.
Nero, too?
Wait, the arcane stage? Does that mean
the Wizard King and Captain Yami, too?
I'm certain those two don't need our training.
And it appears that your captain
has already figured out how to
get to an even higher plane.
Yami has?
When?
As embarrassing as this is, I've lost the key.
From what I've heard, your magic
allows you to open and close things?
Would you mind opening that for me?
I wonder what he wants to show me.
Sealing Magic: Inverse Release.
That's...
Your real name is Secré, right?
"Secré is going to love this!"
was scribbled onto this page.
My prince!
There aren't many of them,
but this kingdom does have people
who weren't blessed with mana.
But once this is complete, we should
be able to resolve their concerns.
Yes, and this should end the
discrimination that currently exists.
But back then, they probably lacked
the technique to create this magic item,
so it was never completed.
I know.
But I've sent a request to the
Magic Item Research Lab at the
Magic Knights' headquarters
to have it made according to this blueprint.
If this had already been completed...
People like the Devil Believers'
leader, Dazu Tayak,
and those who follow her
may have never come to exist.
Those blessed by magic
and those who aren't...
In order to end the
discrimination between them,
this is one of the things most
necessary to the Clover Kingdom.
Is something wrong?
N-No...
We're back!
Today was so exhausting...
Welcome back.
Thanks.
What did you and the Wizard King talk about?
Nothing really.
Did something good happen, Nero?
Huh?
You look happy.
She's right.
You've been looking pretty down lately,
but today is different.
She has?!
You all look pretty happy yourselves.
Well, of course we do!
We're finally going to be training
with the Spirit Guardians!
Of course, you're coming with us, Nero.
I see.
Let's do our best!
All right.
My prince, your will has
definitely been carried on.
Julius Novachrono...
He thinks about the future of the
Clover Kingdom just as much as you did.
My prince, I will become stronger
so that I can protect this kingdom.
Stronger... I have to get stronger.
Or I can't protect this kingdom!
I can't fight!
Next time on Black Clover, Page 150:
"The Maidens' Challenge."
Page 150
The Maidens' Challenge
Grey and Captain Charlotte of the
Blue Rose Knights are working hard, too!