The Clover Kingdom.
In this kingdom where magic is everything,
there is one boy who can't use magic.
His name is Asta.
With guts and hard work,
he made it into the Magic Knights,
and he never gave up,
despite how much he got hurt.
He continues to diligently aim for the top!
Even if you are a peasant,
or even if you're poor...
Anyone in this world can still shine!
He's working hard to prove that,
and to become the Wizard King!
We need to reassure them that the Magic
Knights have the strength to protect them,
and raise the morale of the captains
and Magic Knights, too.
So that we can face the impending threat
of the Spade Kingdom and the devil.
Um... If I may, what exactly
are you planning to do?
I'm going to have the
captains fight each other.
Ahem...
We will now commence
a team battle between
Magic Knights Squad Captains!
Captain of the Purple Orcas
Kaiser Granvorka
Captain of the Silver Eagles
Nozel Silva
Captain of the Black Bulls
Yami Sukehiro
Captain of the Green Praying Mantises
Jack the Ripper
Captain of the Crimson Lion Kings
Fuegoleon Vermillion
Captain of the Blue Rose Knights
Charlotte Roselei
Captain of the Golden Dawn
William Vangeance
Captain of the Coral Peacocks
Dorothy Unsworth
Ooh!
Begin!
Clash! The Battle of the
Magic Knights Squad Captains
Citizens of the Clover Kingdom!
Allow your beloved king to
explain the rules personally!
The time limit is 30 minutes!
The team that destroys
the enemy team's crystal
while protecting theirs will be the winner!
This match between the captains
is being broadcast throughout
the entire kingdom!
A Village Out in the Boonies: Hage
Behold as the Magic Knights Squad Captains
Saussy Village
that I personally spilled blood,
sweat, and tears to train
battle it out before your very eyes!
Also,
due to unforeseen circumstances, the
Captain of the Aqua Deer, Rill Boismortier,
will not be participating in the match.
Master Rill, those melancholy sighs
are a sign that you're in love,
and the first step into adulthood!
Miss... Who are you? Where are you now?
Thanks, Marx.
Everyone in the kingdom
is able to watch this match
because of your communication magic.
I'm glad to hear it...
How long do I have to wear this disguise?
Ah, Julius! Do not force yourself too much.
Because this is a prime opportunity
for me to gain the favor of the citizens
without Julius getting in the way!
Oh, what's wrong? Are you not feeling well?
We should probably figure something
else out for Owen's sake, too.
How are you feeling?
How are you feeling right now?
World Tree Magic: Magic Tree Descends!
Do not touch the World Tree Magic!
You're starting off with that?
Severing Magic: Death Scythe!
Not bad, Beanpole Monster.
Dark Magic: Dark Cloaked—
You're mine!
I guess this was never going to be simple.
Indeed.
Then we'll just have to follow our plan.
Understood.
I know we talked about doing a joint
training session with the Black Bulls,
but to think I'd end up
having to fight Yami...
No, don't think about that now.
Keep calm! Keep calm!
Let's do our best, Charlotte!
O-Of course!
I don't remember the last
time I had so much fun.
You're not getting away!
Something, something, moth to the flame...
Hold it!
You accursed foreigner and former commoner...
Let us strengthen our defense of our crystal.
Where ya hidin'?
Where do you think you're going,
Beanpole Monster?
Huh? Don't order me around.
This sure is a prime spot to get attacked.
Who cares if it's a trap or not?
It won't matter if we slice them all up!
Mercury Magic: Rain of Silver.
You should know that this spell is
not powerful enough to defeat me!
And you should know as well...
that I wouldn't run away without a plan.
In that case...
I shall burn you and your
meddlesome plan to ash!
Sir Nozel, I shall assist you.
When we previously fought, despite having
vortex magic amplified by the elf's mana,
I was no match for Sir Fuegoleon.
I will now get my revenge!
Hmph.
I have a plan. Follow my lead.
I'm getting used to being
the king's attendant.
After the amazing things I've done,
I'm sure the citizens are all wondering,
"Who's that really hot guy
next to the king?" For sure!
Swoon.
Sekke, if by any chance the captains' spells
come this way, protect me with your life.
Bah-ha?!
Yeah, right! That ain't bah-happening!
You two seem to be pretty
good at poking and prodding
while keeping your distance!
Dark Magic: Black Hole!
This is...
Dark Magic: Dark Cloaked Lightless Slash!
Severing Magic: Death Scythe: Lunatic Slash!
Mercury Creation Magic:
Silver Star of Execution!
Sorry about that. You guys were hiding
in the forest, and we sorta leveled it.
That's quite all right.
As long as we made you use up some magic.
Hold it!
Yoo-hoo!
Yami!
Beautiful!
Our captain lured Captain Yami into
the dream world... How amazing!
But alas, the communication magic
doesn't extend into the dream world.
Sadly, we and the rest of the citizens
will not be able to see this
beautiful battle take place!
Ah...
Being so beautiful is such a burden...
Welcome to Dream Magic: Glamour World!
Sit back and relax until
the time limit is up,
Yami dear.
I've heard from my squad
that if you fall asleep here,
you won't be able to go back outside.
And whatever you think up appears here.
It sure does!
In that case...
Outdoor bath!
Sushi on a boat!
Daiginjo sake!
Stuff I can't imagine isn't
going to show up here.
Aw, you really got my hopes up, too.
In that case...
Exit!
The little elf that took over my body
had a rough time playing the
word association game before.
I've made sure I won't make the same mistake.
Guess that just means I'm gonna
have to face you head-on.
That's more like it.
Then...
How about this?
Dark Cloaked...
...Lightless Slash!
Howdy doody!
I'm the great Captain of
the Black Bulls, Yami! Yar!
Is that how I sound in her damn head?
The foreigner's mana disappeared.
He must've been captured by the dream magic.
He won't be back out for a while.
We need to avoid any more setbacks.
We will take care of him right here and now!
Leave this to me!
In most cases, I would have the
upper hand against mercury magic.
But because he's constantly using
an immense amount of mana,
this cage is instantly repaired.
Though I'd like to take
down the spellcasters,
they're both outside the vortex magic.
An excellent strategy!
Brother!
Thanks to the combination of wide-range
silver magic and vortex magic,
they have the advantage
against Captain Fuegoleon.
So this is what it looks
like when captains fight...
No...
My brother's just getting warmed up!
What is he going to do with all those flames?
He can't be...
Though the flames won't
reach us, the heat will...
But what is he...
How hot is he planning to...
Where did Sir Fuegoleon go?
He used Salamander as a decoy
to get by our mana detection.
I'm not done yet!
Howdy doody...
I mean, we all know a copy
could never beat the original.
Nay! You are still within the caster's spell!
The best thing about copies is
you can just keep making them!
It doesn't matter how many
fakes you send after... me...
Aw... shit.
Dark Cloaked... Dark Cloaked... Dark
Cloaked... Dark Cloaked... Dark Cloaked...
...Lightless Slash!
Kaiser!
It's weak, but I sense Sir Jack's mana!
Things are grim...
If we can hit him with even
a single magical attack,
we still have a chance.
So you still have enough
strength to keep struggling.
Mercury Magic: Silver Shining Regal Spear!
I cannot hold out much longer!
After all that talk...
Is this all you've got, you former commoner?
Well done, Yami dear!
You're tougher than I thought!
But you're probably nearing your limit now.
My limit, eh?
Guess you've still got a lot
to learn about me...
Little Miss Pointy Hat.
I'll show you the spell I used back then...
when I truly surpassed my limits!
Are you still functional?
Don't compare me to the small fry!
We'll have no other chances.
We're ending this now.
Who do you think you're ordering
around, Mr. Sparkle Pants?
Now!
Not happening.
As a royal who protects the masses,
and as the Captain of the Silver Eagles,
I cannot let myself lose so pathetically!
I'm sure you're watching, my squad!
There is nothing the flames
of the Crimson Lion Kings
cannot incinerate!
Ooh!
I'm a Magic Knights Squad Captain, too!
I have to get strong enough that I can
trap even a devil in my dream world!
Y'all are the image of the past me,
who Miss Pointy Hat imagined me to be.
But I've already...
grown beyond that!
Mana Zone...
Dark Cloaked...
Dimension Slash ~ Equinox!
Wow, that was such a fantastic battle!
I can't believe I got to see an
exchange of magic like that!
Especially that last one!
To think that Yami's Dimension Slash ended
up slicing through both teams' crystals!
You made us do all that, and it's a draw?
All because you were too busy
playing around in a dream!
Those fools are beyond saving.
That's because you guys had Golden Weird
Mask Guy sucking up all of your damn mana!
I'm surprised they have the strength to
keep arguing after going all-out like that.
What? You want a piece of me, meathead?
Aw... Yami dear wouldn't
let up in Glamour World,
What? Come at me!
so I didn't get to be on the broadcast at all.
Y-Yami dear?! What happened
between these two?!
It was amazing! To think your magic
still had so many possibilities!
I'm almost certain he just wanted
to see the captains use their magic.
You did great too, Marx!
I'm glad the whole kingdom got to see
this battle between the captains.
And I'm sure the citizens are
relieved to know they have
amazing Magic Knights such as
yourselves protecting this kingdom.
And I'm sure after seeing
all of you captains... no,
Grand Magic Knights in action,
your squad members' image of you will change.
The battle against the Spade Kingdom
and the devil is drawing near.
Use this battle to propel you and your
Magic Knights to even greater heights!
Yes, sir!
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Yami and Yami
Yami and Yami.
A-Ahem... Yami, it seems that dream
magic gave you quite a bit of trouble.
What exactly were you doing in there?
Oh, that.
Another me showed up,
and he was stupidly strong.
Another Yami, you say?!
You've got the Sexy Yami.
And the Wild Yami.
Which do you prefer?
Huh?
The days pass... Time continues to flow.
Even I cannot turn back time.
Tomorrow will always come.
Next time on Black Clover,
Page 152: "To Tomorrow!"
Page 152
To Tomorrow!
This kingdom has those who
will carry it into tomorrow.