The Clover Kingdom.
In this kingdom where magic is everything,
there is one boy who can't use magic.
His name is Asta.
With guts and hard work,
he made it into the Magic Knights,
and he never gave up,
despite how much he got hurt.
He continues to diligently aim for the top!
Even if you are a peasant,
or even if you're poor...
Anyone in this world can still shine!
He's working hard to prove that,
and to become the Wizard King!
To Tomorrow!
The Magic Knights Squads.
Nine squads of Magic Knights
who specialize in combat,
all in direct service to the Wizard King.
They are an army of heroes who dedicate
their lives to protecting their kingdom.
It is said that a Magic Knights Squad Captain
possesses the strength of a hundred mages.
The Wizard King and the Magic Knights Squads
are the idols of the Clover Kingdom.
These squad captains
faced each other in battle!
It was a mock tournament held
by Julius, the Wizard King,
meant to strengthen the fighting
spirit of the Magic Knights Squads.
Dark Magic: Dark Cloaked—
Yoo-hoo!
Welcome to Dream Magic: Glamour World!
Guess that just means I'm gonna
have to face you head-on.
Dark Cloaked...
...Lightless Slash!
Mercury Magic: Silver Shining Regal Spear!
Are you still functional?
Don't compare me to the small fry!
We'll have no other chances.
We're ending this now.
Who do you think you're ordering
around, Mr. Sparkle Pants?
Now!
Not happening.
I shall burn you and your
meddlesome plan to ash!
As a royal who protects the masses,
and as the Captain of the Silver Eagles,
I cannot let myself lose so pathetically!
I'm sure you're watching, my squad!
There is nothing the flames
of the Crimson Lion Kings
cannot incinerate!
I'll show you the spell I used back then...
when I truly surpassed my limits!
Mana Zone...
Dark Cloaked...
Dimension Slash ~ Equinox!
Asta and the other Magic Knights renewed
their promise to protect the Clover Kingdom
and its people from the threat of
the Spade Kingdom and the devil,
and to become much, much stronger.
Water Creation Magic: Sea Dragon's Roar!
In September, the Magic Knights trained daily
to prepare for the upcoming battle
with the Spade Kingdom and the devil.
After seeing the captains fight,
Asta and Noelle felt even more motivated,
and continued their own training as
they awaited the day they would train
with the Heart Kingdom's Spirit Guardians.
Asta! Noelle!
Hey, let's go.
Yes, sir!
It's already time?
I get to go out with my friends.
My heart leaps with joy.
I can't help but smile.
Sure thing!
Clover Kingdom
Castle Town Kikka
Looks like the town has mostly recovered
from the Eye of the Midnight Sun's attack.
Captain Yami, thank you for
bringing us along with you!
I just brought you along because you
wouldn't shut up about wanting to come.
I wanted to go back to my roots!
It's already been a year.
It feels so long, yet somehow,
it feels like it passed in the blink of an eye.
On this day, the annual Magic Knights
Entrance Exam was being held in the coliseum.
Good luck on the Entrance Exam!
You're the Clover Kingdom's stars of hope!
The kingdom's future is in your hands!
Partially because of all the chaos caused by
the Eye of the Midnight Sun's attack,
there were fewer applicants than in years prior.
Listen up! Whatever you do, don't interfere.
Right!
That's obvious.
Look, Noelle! That was us a year ago!
Someone out of that crowd
might end up being our junior.
Miss Noelle!
I wonder if they'll call
me something like that.
That wouldn't be so bad.
Asta! Above you!
Huh?
Ack! What the heck's with these birds?!
Wait, are these the
anti-birds I've heard about?
What? The ones that peck at you
if you don't have much mana?
Hey! Get away from me!
Get away from me!
Get off me!
What the heck was that?
How little mana do you have if
a swarm that big pecks at you?
I guess someone always has it worse.
What the heck is Stupidsta doing?
Noelle.
Nozel.
You came.
Yes. Stupids—
Asta invited me.
He thought we may be able to go
back to our roots as Magic Knights
in order to prepare for our upcoming battle.
So it's already been a year.
Okay!
What are you doing?
Oh, I'm... um...
I told you. There's no need for royalty
to take the same exam as the peasants.
But...
Your destination has already been decided.
Do not take unnecessary action.
Yes, Brother Nozel.
Your existence itself is unnecessary.
I understand now, though.
That was all my brother's kindness.
He just didn't want me to go to the battlefield.
What is it?
N-Nothing. I was just...
At first, I couldn't help but wonder
why I got put in the Black Bulls.
But now, I can truly say that I'm grateful
that you put me with the Black Bulls.
I now have precious friends
and a precious family.
I was able to share experiences
I wouldn't trade for the world.
You've grown, Noelle.
Thank you very much!
And you have the potential to grow even more.
You will probably become even stronger.
Yes... Just like Mother.
I said get away from me!
Ugh!
The Magic Knights Squad Captains...
Th-They have such presence.
I am the Captain of the Golden Dawn,
William Vangeance.
I will be conducting the Magic
Knights Entrance Exam.
First, I would like to commend you all for
participating in this exam to protect
this kingdom and its people after the
attack by the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
The hero, Lord Vangeance...
...is praising us?
And I want you to know this.
Even if you do not pass, that is not the end.
Anyone can retry as many times as they'd like.
Now, then...
Magic Tree Descends!
Let us now begin the
Magic Knights Entrance Exam!
Wow, this takes me back!
Remember how you couldn't fly
at all back then, Stupidsta?
You were watching me?
Well, you stuck out like a sore thumb.
Of course I noticed you.
Not only could you not fly,
but you had no mana at all,
so I thought you were going to fail for sure.
But then...
You're funny, kid.
Join my squad.
Huh?
I'm telling you that I'll let
you join the Black Bulls.
Captain Yami acknowledged you. And then...
Even if you got hurt and battered,
you never gave up.
No matter how many times you fell,
you always, always got back up again.
Right here, right now...
I'll surpass my limits!
You were able to overcome any obstacle.
You truly are amazing.
Wha?
O-Only a little bit, though!
Thanks, Noelle!
You're pretty amazing yourself!
You have an insane amount of mana,
and you keep learning how to use
one new spell after another.
That water armor's super cool, too!
That's not water armor.
That's my Valkyrie Armor.
Yeah, exactly. That water armor!
You're super amazing!
I'm not that impressive.
We went through so many hardships.
Yeah.
And I'm sure there are many more hardships
we can't even imagine awaiting us.
But we have the captains
and a bunch of our friends!
And new strength!
We're going to protect the
people no matter what!
By combining our strengths!
Let's become stronger.
Much, much stronger.
Say, Yuno. What's so fun about this?
Oh, you're just so cool!
Hey, wait, Stupidsta. Where are you going?
Hey, Yuno!
Gah, it's him again.
You're here too, Yuno?
Don't just wander off without
saying anything, you silent stud.
Shrug.
Did you just say "shrug" at me?!
You seriously just spoke a sound effect?!
He's just so cool.
Yeah, right! He's not cool at all!
He's just trying to act cool!
What do you mean, trying?
Yuno doesn't have to try to
be cool. He is cool, right?
Though I guess since you're here,
you felt the same way I did.
The same?
We both swore that we'd
become the Wizard King!
You?!
Not just me!
I'll... never cry again.
Maybe I... no...
Yuno?
I will...
I'll become the Wizard King, too!
I'll get stronger, and protect
you and everyone else!
I'm gonna make everyone happier!
So we can have nicer things!
Let's see who can become the Wizard King!
Though I'm going to be the one who wins.
Say what?! I'm gonna win!
No, me.
Me!
So...
Were you able to go back
to your roots or whatever?
Yes! Thank you so much!
I see.
I'm feeling more motivated, too.
I'm going to become even stronger
and make even more friends.
I'm going to become stronger, too!
So I can make the Black Bulls
the best Magic Knights Squad ever!
And so I can defeat this curse
and win Miss Finnes's trust.
Let's all do our best!
So, Captain, did you recruit anyone new?
Do I have a junior now?
Well, there was someone interesting, but...
But?!
Another squad swiped them.
What?!
Which means you two are at
the bottom for another year.
What?!
Come on, let's go home.
I knew I'd find you here.
Hey there, Marx. What a coincidence.
You left the castle.
There's nothing coincidental about it.
Let's hurry back. Your work
just continues to pile up.
I know.
But...
But?
Young people are joining the
Magic Knights Squads to work hard
to protect the people and this kingdom.
Just seeing them seems to give me courage.
Yes, you're right. They give
us hope for the future.
Yes.
All right, let's head back.
Marx, do you like grilled purple snake?
What are you talking about?
If you do, I thought I'd catch
one and grill it up for you.
There's no need for that.
Aw... Asta would be more
than happy to eat it.
Yuno.
There's something I want to give you.
What is it?
My pendant... But how?
A man named Revchi brought it.
He did?
Apparently, it was among
the treasures that he and Gueldre
took from the Shadow Palace.
He was probably afraid of what
you'd do to him if you ever found out.
This magic stone belongs to you.
Yes.
To think it'd come back to me because
of him. You can't be serious.
Good for you, Yuno.
Today marks exactly a year.
You've helped me out so much.
Thank you.
I expect great things from you.
Well, everyone is waiting. Let's go.
All right, let's do this.
More training?! Let's do it!
The hell are you talking about?
We're having a party.
A party?
We're celebrating the first
anniversary since you two joined.
A lot is happening right now,
but it's the least we can do.
Magna and the others
should be back soon, too.
Thanks!
I guess I'll let you celebrate, for my sake.
All right! Forget about fighting
just for tonight, and eat and drink!
Right!
Let's have fun tonight.
Let's talk friendship until morning.
We're back!
We're back, Charmy.
I've gotten stronger since then.
But...
...it's not enough.
I'm going to rise even higher
and become the Wizard King.
and become the Wizard King!
It's been a year since the kid and
Noelle joined the Black Bulls.
Time sure does fly.
Next time on Black Clover,
Page 153: "The Chosen Ones."
Page 153
The Chosen Ones
If you want to get even stronger,
what else are you gonna do?