The Clover Kingdom.
In this kingdom where magic is everything,
there is one boy who can't use magic.
His name is Asta.
With guts and hard work,
he made it into the Magic Knights,
and he never gave up,
despite how much he got hurt.
He continues to diligently aim for the top!
Even if you are a peasant,
or even if you're poor...
Anyone in this world can still shine!
He's working hard to prove that,
and to become the Wizard King!
I've been informed that the recovery
efforts in even the hardest-hit
parts of the Forsaken Realm are now underway.
Things are finally looking brighter as a whole.
Yes. And to make this peace an eternal
one rather than a fleeting one,
we must remain strong.
It's nearly time.
You have the captains' meeting as well
as a special decoration ceremony.
You're going to have a busy day.
Indeed.
The Chosen Ones
Our topic today is who will participate
in the Heart Kingdom's training.
Our promise with the Heart Kingdom's
queen... In other words,
the battle with the Spade Kingdom,
is drawing nearer as we speak.
I know that every squad is
working hard to get stronger,
but we just received word
from the Heart Kingdom that
preparations for training are done.
Our training is finally in its final stage.
There are five Spirit Guardians
who will help us train,
and there is a limited number
that each of them can train.
So I'd like all of you to nominate
members of your squad.
Now, who would like to get us started?
From my squad, I'm choosing Asta and Nero,
though they were already
chosen by the Heart Kingdom.
Asta, who uses anti-magic,
and Nero, who uses forbidden magic,
are already at the arcane stage.
We know from our previous
battle that their powers will be
our trump card in defeating the devil.
I hope they can make those powers
their own even more through training.
I'm also going to be sending Finral,
Luck, and Noelle from my squad.
What's this? Are you worried?
No matter how tough you act, you're such
a softie when it comes to your sister.
Apparently Luck and Noelle both
pair well with their magic.
Well, the Heart Kingdom does have a
Spirit Guardian who controls lightning,
and their queen controls
the Water Spirit, Undine.
Since Luck controls lightning magic
and Noelle controls water magic,
it should be perfect.
And I'm not surprised that Luck is super
excited, since he's always rarin' to go,
but even Noelle's super motivated right now.
Well, they are up against Megicula,
who killed their mother.
And as for Finral...
Well, he's handy to have around.
If a reliable supporter
like him is able to level up,
our strength as a whole should rise.
He may also provide hints
to a new way of fighting.
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about.
So from the Black Bulls, we have
Asta, Nero, Noelle Silva,
Luck Voltia, and Finral Roulacase,
making five members.
That's quite a few.
Nothing wrong with having
so many guys with potential.
They're who I'm gonna go with.
I nominate Mimosa Vermillion
from the Golden Dawn.
We're up against the devil-possessed.
I'm sure we will face some
cruel, ruthless battles.
The cornerstone of these battles
will be recovery mages.
She is a royal who also possesses
substantial natural talent,
and stretching her potential
is sure to benefit our kingdom.
I see. Is Mimosa your only nominee?
I hear that the Wind Spirit Guardian
will also be training our nominees.
Yuno declined.
I assume he has his reasons.
Please nominate Magic Knights
from other squads, too.
I nominate Leopold Vermillion
from the Crimson Lion Kings.
Leo's ambition is high, and he
asked our older sister, Mereoleona,
to train him at the volcano
in the strong magic region.
I can clearly imagine what kind
of hell that must've been.
No one can beat Leopold's hard
work and ambition in my squad,
but there is hesitation in him.
I am hoping he can light a new flame
by training in another kingdom
and burn away his hesitation.
Once he is able to do that,
he will be essential in the
battle against the Spade Kingdom,
but he will also become a true lion king
capable of protecting this kingdom!
I see.
I look forward to seeing how he grows.
What about the other squads?
Anyone from the Blue Rose Knights?
I'd like to confirm something first.
Is it possible for a captain to participate?
I see no problem with it.
I personally think someone who was possessed by an elf, such as yourself,
could produce some interesting results.
The feeling of the mana from when my body
was possessed by an elf still remains.
That red rose mana was far superior to mine.
I cannot be picky in how I become stronger
for the battle against the devil.
I need to experience something
similar again, no matter what!
Wait, no! That's not what
I meant by "experience"!
Hmm?
So the only nominee from the
Blue Rose Knights is the captain?
Yes.
Any others?
This is a rather hard decision, but I
believe younger candidates are favorable.
I agree. And I am very aware
of how to train myself.
I don't mind going if I can
slice up the Heart Kingdom.
Yeah, no. You're not going.
This training will probably be grueling.
But there will be knowledge and new
discoveries they won't find here,
and a new world may open up to those who go.
I'd like you all to use that to your advantage.
My... My own...
They're all my food!
I'd like you to train hard every
day and grow ever vigilant.
Training...
Training means protein...
This is for the protein!
You all have wonderful potential,
so I'd like to see you grow.
Growing bigger...
This is for the fat!
La!
This is for the vitamins!
This is for the fiber!
This is for the collagen!
Me, me, me, me, me, me, me!
Goodness, aren't you full of energy?
What got into you all of a sudden?
I nominate myself from the Aqua Deer!
I'm going to train, become stronger,
and become a man that nice lady will notice!
I think we actually have enough now,
but is there anyone else?
The Silver Eagles will do everything they can
to bolster their skills so that they
can face the Spade Kingdom.
As will my squad.
We're also doing things our own way!
Then do we agree on the nominees mentioned?
Aye.
Good. I look forward to seeing
the fruits of your labor.
Yes, sir.
This concludes the Magic
Knights Squad Captains' meeting.
Whew, we're finally done.
See ya.
And where do you think you're going?
The special decoration ceremony
is just about to start.
Seriously? I have to go to that?
But I've got my wheels parked outside.
It's not like anyone from
my squad got picked.
We were told that every captain should
be in attendance for this ceremony.
What? Why?
Well, you see...
The king will be participating this time.
Seriously?
Bah-ha... All the captains are here.
They're so intense-ha.
So they've made all the captains attend
because I am present. Excellent.
Seriously, this is too close.
He's going to find out pretty soon.
Captain Jack!
Please...
bring me back...
to the squad.
The hell's his problem?
Talk about annoying.
How about I slice you open?!
It looks like everyone's here.
Let us begin.
We will now begin our special decoration
ceremony for the Magic Knights
who fought bravely against
the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
Because the Wizard King's throat
is not completely healed,
I will be conducting this ceremony.
First...
With 21 stars acquired, we have
Sol Marron from the Blue Rose Knights.
You have been promoted to
5th Class Senior Magic Knight.
Thanks to your calm and brave decisions,
you got the gravely injured
Wizard King to a safe place.
Please continue using that judgment
and drive in the battlefield.
Oho! Impressive. She moved
up three ranks at once.
She saved the Wizard King's life.
This promotion seems quite fitting.
I wasn't actually calm at all back then.
Not to mention, the guy who saved Sis
was the Captain of the Black Bulls.
Next time, I'm gonna protect Sis
without the help of any man!
Hey, uh... one of yours
seems to be glaring at me.
Is that my problem?
She's staring at Yami?
Wait, no, Sol! Don't tell
me you like Yami, too!
Sis is staring at me passionately!
I'll do my best to live
up to your expectations!
With 23 stars acquired,
we have Mimosa Vermillion
from the Golden Dawn.
You have been promoted to
2nd Class Intermediate Magic Knight.
In the battle at the Shadow Palace,
you showed humanity and effectively
did your job as a recovery mage.
We look forward to you saving
many more lives in the future.
I think people realize how important
recovery magic is because of Mimosa.
I will live up to this honor that
I just received and do my best
in the battle against the Spade Kingdom.
With 18 stars acquired,
we have Leopold Vermillion
from the Crimson Lion Kings.
You have been promoted to
4th Class Senior Magic Knight.
When the previous and
new captains were absent,
you inspired the other squad members and
did everything in your power to stop
your vice captain, who had
been possessed by an elf.
Please continue to use your character to
raise everyone's morale on the battlefield
and lead us to victory.
So Leopold has also gone up three ranks.
I would like to decline!
Back then, if my brother hadn't shown up,
my whole squad would have been annihilated.
I did everything in my power,
but I was completely powerless.
Everyone tried to protect me,
even if it cost them their lives.
I'm just...
I'm just a weakling, and I do
not deserve this recognition!
You fool!
Do you not understand why everyone
tried so hard to protect you?
Is it not because they
were moved by your bravery,
and because they saw hope
in your very existence?
They entrusted you with the future
of the Crimson Lion Kings.
This award includes
the very determination, resolve,
and hope of the Crimson Lion Kings!
Resolve and hope?
I, Leopold Vermillion,
will live up to this recognition,
do everything I can to protect
my squad from any enemy,
and become a Lion King who
can lead everyone to victory!
Yuno from the Golden Dawn.
Yes, sir.
You have earned 77 stars.
Holy wow!
Wait, how many stars did the
Aqua Deer have last time?
Yuno of the Golden Dawn,
you have been promoted to
1st Class Senior Magic Knight.
What?!
Bah-ha?!
A 1st Class Senior Magic Knight?!
This peasant?!
With your tremendous amount of mana,
you were able to deal a fatal blow to
the devil, who was the root of all this evil.
We look forward to great things from you.
Yes, sir.
He's now the same rank as
our vice captain, Langris.
He suddenly jumped to the rank right
under the Magic Knights Squad Captains.
I don't really get it, but you did good, right?
Way to go, Yuno!
To celebrate, let's go on a dat—
1st Class Senior Magic Knight...
I guess I got a little closer.
These four members...
Hold it!
Well, this definitely sounds like
it's gonna be a pain in the ass.
Silence, Yami. Despite how
he is, he's still our king.
You just lowkey dragged said king.
The one who shined the brightest in
this battle hasn't been recognized!
The hero who protected the most
important person in this kingdom!
Him! Sekke Bronzazza!
Bah-ha?!
Not only did all of you leave me,
your king, unattended,
but some of you fools had
the nerve to attack me!
Really?
Who knows?
Sekke is the true hero!
The epitome of Magic Knights!
During that fierce battle, he dodged
the enemy's attacks and came to me!
There's no doubt that he deserves the
most recognition out of anyone here!
* Some facts may have been skewed.
I-I just happened to show up-ha...
With my authority as king, I give Sekke...
the title of 1st Class Senior Magic Knight!
F-First Class Senior Magic Knight?!
What the bah-ha?!
If that peasant gets to be a
1st Class Senior Magic Knight,
I'm going to promote Sekke
to that rank, too!
Bah-ha... Bah-ha... Bah-ha?!
Th-This is, uh...
Their disapproval is super obvious-ha!
I'm gonna get killed, bah-ha!
I-I have just been promoted to
1st Class Senior Magic Knight!
I, Sekke Bronzazza,
will fight any enemy, win,
and take pride in protecting
the Clover Kingdom, bah-ha!
So please spare my life.
W-Will that be all, Your Majesty?
Indeed! All of you should follow Sekke's
example and remember to prioritize me!
Do you understand?!
I-I've been saved.
As I was saying,
other than the present five,
we will be promoting everyone who
participated in this battle one rank.
I see. So that's why they
had all captains attend.
They wouldn't usually have us all show
up just because the king is here.
Such care for the squad members
coming from the Wizard King...
I thank you.
All of the Magic Knights who risked their
lives in this battle will be rewarded.
If the current fuss over the Magic
Parliament trial hadn't been going on,
there were squads that would've
seen many promotions.
Though we will not be able
to promote them at this time,
we have decided to give
them special recognition.
Captain of the Black Bulls, Yami Sukehiro.
What? I get something?
Please keep the problems to a minimum,
and continue to show results
with your teamwork.
What? I don't get money?
Well, thanks anyway.
This concludes the
special decoration ceremony.
Lastly, I would like to read a
message from the Wizard King.
"Our kingdom is slowly recovering from
the attack by the Eye of the Midnight Sun,
but the threat of the Spade Kingdom
is just around the corner.
I expect nothing but the best from
those who have just been promoted.
I hope that those who did not receive
new titles will continue to train hard,
come together as Magic Knights,
and protect this kingdom and its people."
Yes, sir.
We're back!
Come and get me!
Damn it! Quit running away!
Looks like you can't keep up with me at all!
Hey! Welcome back, Captain Yami and Finral!
Damn, you're noisy.
Go train outside.
Hey, Luck!
Huh?
You're mine!
You're going to the Heart Kingdom.
Really?!
So it's finally been decided?!
From our squad, we've got you and Nero,
then Finral, Luck, and Noelle.
Finral, too?!
Yeah...
I get to go all-out in the Heart Kingdom!
Sure. Go crazy, kid.
Please...
Please let me go, too!
I can't just sit here if he's gonna go!
I'll get even stronger than him!
Look, this was already decided
at the captains' meeting.
Sorry.
Please! Let me go!
He's always running ahead of me.
But I'm a true man,
and I can't be left behind again!
Even if you tell me not
to go, I'm going to go!
With your mana, you're not gonna be able
to keep up unless you're prepared to die.
You up to that?
Yes, sir!
Who the hell cares about
how much mana you have?!
I'll surpass the limits of a peasant!
Fine. I'll try asking Julius.
Just remember this.
What's important here isn't where you train.
It's how you train.
Got it?
Yes, sir!
You did it, Magna!
Yeah, it wouldn't be fun if
I just kept getting stronger.
Yeah! You bet your ass I'm gonna catch up!
In that case, Finral, Magna, and Luck!
Let's all do our best training
in the Heart Kingdom!
Yeah!
Look at you, climbing up
that ladder all at once.
You're just so cool!
I guess you'll become the
Wizard King in no time!
You can't be serious. It's not that easy.
But someday...
Someday, for sure...
I'm going to follow my own path
to become the Wizard King.
Next time on Black Clover, Page 154:
"Vice Captain Langris Vaude."
Page 154
Vice Captain Langris Vaude
If you're going to come at me,
you can't hold back, or you'll get hurt.