The Clover Kingdom.
In this kingdom where magic is everything,
there is one boy who can't use magic.
His name is Asta.
With guts and hard work,
he made it into the Magic Knights,
and he never gave up,
despite how much he got hurt.
He continues to diligently aim for the top!
Even if you are a peasant,
or even if you're poor...
Anyone in this world can still shine!
He's working hard to prove that,
and to become the Wizard King!
We can finally train in the Heart Kingdom!
Now that I've sworn I'd be worthy of
being the head of the House of Vaude
and of Miss Finnes,
If I don't become stronger now,
it'll all be a lie.
So the Spirit Guardians won't break
even if I go all-out, right?
I can't wait!
Hell yeah! I'm definitely gonna get stronger!
Well, you can get stronger, but I'm
still gonna get even stronger than you!
The hell'd you say?!
To avenge my mother...
To destroy the devil Megicula...
I'm going to become stronger!
The 5 Spirit Guardians
Guys, you're already here?
Asta!
I've been waiting for you, my rival!
Training in another kingdom...
Yami should've come, too.
Asta, Yuno gave me a message for you.
Oh? What'd he say?
Just simply, "I'm going to become
stronger with the Golden Dawn."
What's that supposed to mean? He'd obviously
get stronger if he trained over here.
Nah, he'd get stronger
no matter where he was.
I can't lose!
It appears that you're all here.
Yes. Thank you for having us, Gaja.
Then allow me to lead you in.
There are many of you I am
meeting for the first time.
Welcome to the Heart Kingdom.
Normally, I would be holding a
feast to welcome all of you here,
and it pains me deeply that
this is the best I can do,
but considering the circumstances...
Is something the matter?
I do beg your pardon for bringing
this up, but the one on your lap...
It's Charmy.
Yeah, that much is obvious.
But what's she doing here?
Wherever there are delicious noms,
I shall also be there!
What the hell?
Honestly, this is the problem
with the Black Bulls.
But it does appear that
Queen Loropechika is okay with it.
If the queen is allowing it,
there shouldn't be a problem.
It seems the queen here is very generous.
Is this actually what you'd call generous?
It's a pleasure to have you all here,
citizens of the Clover Kingdom.
We'll be in your care for a while.
We thank you for your kindness!
Then let us go into a bit more
detail about your training.
First, the Spade Kingdom has
already taken control of most of
the bases in the Diamond Kingdom,
and their invasion has halted for the moment.
Which means that our kingdom, as well as
the Clover Kingdom,
may be targeted at any time.
And because of that,
all of you will be undergoing rigorous
training to ensure rapid growth.
Bring it on!
We also wish to become more
powerful as soon as possible.
I will now introduce the Spirit Guardians
who will be mentoring you.
The Spirit Guardian of Earth
Sarado
The Spirit Guardian of Earth, Sarado.
Pleased to meet you!
The Spirit Guardian of Plants, Potrof.
The Spirit Guardian of Plants
Potrof
Let us learn together!
The Spirit Guardian of Fire
Floga
The Spirit Guardian of Fire, Floga.
I have high hopes for you!
The Spirit Guardian of Wind
Smurik
The Spirit Guardian of Wind, Smurik.
Hey, they seem pretty intense.
This seems fun! Who do I get to fight first?!
Mimosa and Charlotte, please
train with Sarado first.
Understood.
Very well.
Leave it to me!
Finral, please learn from Smurik.
Yes, sir!
Rill, Potrof shall be your mentor.
Yeah, sure thing!
I'll be waiting for you in the forest!
Leopold and Magna will be under Floga's care.
I hope you'll train me to the fullest!
You both seem really determined!
I can't wait to meet you in person!
Luck, I will be training you myself.
As long as we get to put our lives
on the line, I don't care who it is.
What about me? Who's gonna be training me?
You do not have any mana whatsoever.
We may be Spirit Guardians, but we
cannot make mana grow from nothing.
Huh?! Then why the heck did I come here?!
But you are one of the mages
at the arcane stage, who could
possibly defeat the devil.
I would like you to spar with me
so I can gauge your strength.
We will figure out the details after that.
Spar with you? Okay, got it!
As for the other mage at
the arcane stage, Nero...
I will be training her myself.
The queen will be training Nero personally?
I look forward to working with you, Nero.
And as for Noelle,
Undine and I will be training you.
Let's do our best.
Yes, all right.
This covers the assignments for the training.
Hang on a second!
What is it, Magna?
Is there any way I can continue going
at it with Luck and train under you?
Very well.
Hell yeah!
Aw, sure. But do you think you'll
be able to keep up with me?
Of course I can!
The rest of you, as well, are not bound
permanently to the assignments I have chosen.
Once your mana grows a bit, please move
on to a different Spirit Guardian.
That will help you learn as much as possible.
Now then, everyone, I look forward to
working with all of you for a while.
Right!
Magna uses flame magic,
and Luck uses lightning magic.
If natural magic attributes work better
with the Heart Kingdom's techniques,
then these two are perfect, aren't they?
Essentially, yes.
First, I will show you how to make
mana words with natural mana.
The hell is that?!
Without this, you cannot
create this technique.
By creating a technique using mana words,
you can add simple orders to spells.
For example...
Please dodge.
Like this?
Just like that, it means
we are able to give it
orders like "chase him" or "become bigger."
That's awesome!
Huh...
All right! Let's do this!
Plants grow from the earth.
In order to strengthen plant magic,
you start with the earth.
I somewhat understand what you're saying...
So you're telling us to understand the earth.
It's probably quicker to show
you than try to explain it.
So this is the Heart Kingdom's technique.
Though our magic attributes are different,
we're in the same boat when it
comes to understanding nature.
If you can master this, your magic
will instantly power up!
That's rather surprising. One of my
subordinates uses similar magic,
but yours is much faster and more powerful.
From the looks of it, you all
just rely on your own mana,
and can't use natural mana at all.
So you're telling us to become able to do that.
And how do we do that?
You just gather it, like "swoosh," from
a huge area, and bam, you're all set.
Um, could you be more specific, please?
You just sense mana, like, "ding, ding, ding."
Once you feel it, you've just
gotta go whoosh and swoosh.
Then we can talk about technique.
That's far too vague...
He seems a bit different.
The wind that comes down
from the mountains,
the wind that rises from the ocean...
All the wind passes through this valley.
I see. So that's why the
wind is so strong here.
I was looking forward to the arrival
of the boy chosen by the Wind Spirit.
Oh, you mean Asta's rival.
But you came to me instead. I'm sure
there must be a deep meaning behind that.
I mean, I think Gaja decided that, but...
Now, what will you do?
Is this training?
Has our training already begun?
Whether this is training or not, the wind
that blows between us does not change.
Isn't that right?
I can't seem to figure this
guy out. Is he really okay?
Spatial magic's main purpose
is to support your friends.
Isn't that what you think?
Yes... and?
Then if someone targets you, do you
just expect your friends to save you?
Does that truly make you a supporter?
What you must do is not
necessarily just one thing.
Crap!
Well, what now?
Please continue!
Very well. Anywhere the wind blows.
What a beautiful day!
A perfect day for training.
I look forward to working with you, Floga!
First, let's see your magic.
About 80% of your power is enough.
Flame Magic: Spiral Flames!
Nice. If this is what you can do at 80%,
you've got a fair bit of potential.
No, this is nowhere near enough.
I must learn much more
and become even stronger.
I don't want this chance to go to waste.
Agreed.
I realize I may come off
as rude when I say this,
but I'd like to see your powers.
Mine?
I want to see with my own eyes
whether I can learn anything from you.
Ah, so that's what you mean.
Well, in that case...
I think that about does it.
I apologize for doubting your strength.
Don't worry about it.
It was so intense... I want to
make that intensity my own!
Your potential is far greater than mine.
Once you learn how to use natural mana,
it won't be that difficult
for you to do what I just did.
You're on the right track.
But it's not easy getting
full control of natural mana.
I look forward to working with you, Floga!
You've gotta push harder, Magna!
Your magic is far too weak, after all.
What?!
You're around the fifth stage.
To use these techniques in battle,
you need to be third stage or higher.
What the heck is this? It's super fun!
It appears that he has a knack for this.
Guess I'm just gonna get
stronger on my own, then.
Magna...
Just leave him alone, Asta.
If he can't get any stronger,
it just means that's all he's worth.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
As I stated earlier, I'm going
to measure your strength.
Please come at me with everything you have.
I get to fight someone who's almost
on a par with the Wizard King!
Let's have a good match!
I think this is a good spot.
So what are we going to do for training?
We're going to bask in the natural mana.
Plants and animals...
The earth, water, wind, sunlight...
This place is rich with life,
so it's also overflowing with mana.
Now that you mention it,
I think I can feel that.
And don't ever forget that feeling.
You need mana words to create the
techniques we use in the Heart Kingdom.
You'll be able to use mana words as you please
once you become one with natural mana.
Wow!
I can feel something welling up inside me
after seeing you use your magic like this.
Then why not try using mana
words as your heart desires?
It probably won't go perfectly as
planned at first, but that's fine.
All right.
Er, that's not quite right.
You need to use mana words—
I feel the need to create
welling up within me!
Uh... I see that you're an excellent painter,
so why not try writing mana words?
Mana words... like this.
Like this?
My painting!
Unbelievable.
You were able to write that many mana
words after seeing them just once...
Rill, keep that up.
No, don't go painting again!
Thanks for your help. I think this painting
is going to be even better for it.
Oh, for crying out loud!
Hey, you're from the Black Bulls...
Aren't you Queen Loropechika's pet...
er, I mean, guest?
Weren't you enjoying a
meal back at the palace?
Well, I ate all the food there,
so I came here in search for new foods, la.
You're telling me you've depleted
all of the palace's reserves?
Yup.
Well, since you came all the
way to the Heart Kingdom,
why not learn the Heart Kingdom's techniques?
Well, right now, I just want to eat
as many delicious noms as I can.
Oh, don't be like that. See, look.
These are mana words.
They're really convenient to be able to use.
Ah! Looks like we have
another genius on our hands!
But it's not complete just yet.
Listen well. You use mana
words and natural mana to...
I think there's even more delicious
fruit further in the forest.
If we go further into the forest,
I'm sure I'll find some scenery
that'll spark my inspiration!
I'm begging you two, please listen to me.
Now, let's have you train us,
Loropechika and Undine.
Of course. But first,
I have a request for you two.
Please save me.
As things stand, this curse will kill me.
Before that happens...
We know. We'll defeat the
devil before that happens.
That's why we're all here to train.
The four of us here will strike
down the devil Megicula.
Could you explain what you mean?
Of course, we will need
everyone else's help in order
to stop the invasion from the Spade Kingdom.
But Megicula... The one that
Megicula possesses, the mage Vanica...
We don't stand a chance
against that one unless Undine and I,
as well as the two of you, join forces.
And you know how this Vanica fights.
That's why you're saying that.
My duty is to fight alongside
Loropechika, as well as protect her.
But the two of us were no match for Vanica.
It's my fault that Loropechika has to
deal with the fear of impending death.
No, it's not your fault, Undine.
Those possessed by the devil cannot
be defeated by ordinary means.
So you're saying if you have
Nero and me with you,
we'll be able to win using
unconventional means.
We can't be certain just yet.
But I've come to the conclusion that
if the four of us work together,
we may come closest to that result.
Please... help us so that
we can save Loropechika.
Nero's arcane stage...
Noelle's combative spirit
and fighting style...
If you two grow along with Undine and me,
we should be able to defeat Vanica,
as well as Megicula, who possesses her.
I'll believe you.
Nero, you're doing this, too.
Thank you.
You don't need to thank us.
I have my own reasons for wanting to
defeat Megicula with my own hands.
Very well. Then let us begin.
All right! Come at me from wherever!
You've got the right idea.
But if you can't figure out your
opponent's powers, there's no point.
This isn't good. At this rate,
I won't be able to support my friends!
Keep zooming at me!
Keep using those mana words!
Then you'll eventually get the hang of it!
This time, I'll get you!
The power to nullify magic is unrivaled.
But your vision is so narrow that you can't
use your powers to their full potential.
Not yet!
Solely relying on how tough
you are in your fighting style
will not keep working forever.
To use those powers to their full potential,
it's only logical that you use
them to back up your friends.
Please let me try again!
I guess you won't be satisfied with that.
Yeah, they're working me
to the bone from day one.
Not just me. All of us!
So, are you seeing any progress?
It looks like everyone else has already
learned the Heart Kingdom's techniques,
so I think it's unlikely that we won't get
stronger if we keep this up every day.
Oh? Well, keep up the good work.
Yes, sir!
Looks like they're all trying
to surpass their limits.
So I guess I need to work a bit harder, too.
Everyone's gone out training, so the
Black Bulls' hideout is super quiet.
Next time on Black Clover,
Page 156: "Awakening Powers."
Page 156
Awakening Powers
Guess I should push harder, too.
And no, I don't mean in the bathroom.