The Clover Kingdom.
In this kingdom where magic is everything,
there is one boy who can't use magic.
His name is Asta.
With guts and hard work,
he made it into the Magic Knights,
and he never gave up,
despite how much he got hurt.
He continues to diligently aim for the top!
Even if you are a peasant,
or even if you're poor...
Anyone in this world can still shine!
He's working hard to prove that,
and to become the Wizard King!
In order to learn the Mana Method
and acquire new powers,
Asta and the others train their
hardest in the Heart Kingdom.
This time, I'll get you!
The power to nullify magic is unrivaled.
But your vision is so narrow that you can't
use your powers to their full potential.
Not yet!
And this man was making his move, too.
Looks like they're all trying
to surpass their limits.
So I guess I need to work a bit harder, too.
Awakening Powers
Lightning Magic: Tenjiolia.
I've been sparring with him for days now,
and I still can't get a hit in!
If I wasn't holding back,
you'd be in far worse shape.
The extremely rare power known as anti-magic,
physical strength that you've trained
to your limit, and your friends
are what have led you to victory thus far.
But the enemy we're about
to face is far too powerful.
If you cannot defeat me on your own,
you will not be able to defeat the devil.
Please let me have another try!
Is it his unwavering willpower that
has strengthened him to this point?
No, it's not just him.
Some of the mages who came
from the Clover Kingdom
have already started creating
techniques of their own.
Faster... I need to be faster.
I need to be stronger!
Leopold...
I know I should be able to do more... More!
Those were great moves, Leo.
You're able to use the
Mana Method faster now, too.
It's just...
Hmm, how do I put this?
Every now and then, you seem to
waver a bit when you're fighting.
It feels like something's making you hesitate.
Is there a reason why?
I have an older brother and
an older sister that I look up to.
Their strength is burned into
my eyes. I cannot unsee it.
The stronger I become,
the more I realize how much higher
up my brother and sister are.
Stand up.
Lions should never look so pitiful.
The more powerful I get, the more
out of reach they seem to become.
No matter how hard I try, I can't help
but think that they're stronger than me.
Flame Magic: Calidos Brachium!
Man, it's hot.
Heya, Sisgoleon.
Who are you calling Sisgoleon, you fool?
Did you come for a dip in the hot springs, too?
Why not go defeat one of the magical
beasts around here while you're at it?
Jeez, were you fighting so you
could enjoy a nice, long bath?
You sure are violent, aren't ya?
Hah. I couldn't even call this a warmup.
I'm sure you couldn't.
So in that case...
How about fighting me?
Oh? What brought this on?
Yeah, about that.
In that last battle with the devil,
I was able to use the Mana Zone
or whatever it's called.
But I still don't really get it,
and I think I could take it a bit further,
so I wanted to give it a try.
Give it a try? With me?
Well, you're more experienced
with Mana Zone, aren't you?
Help a newbie out, will ya?
Very well. I was just thinking
I hadn't had enough.
But are you sure about this?
Before you even get to try,
your body might not even hold up!
Yikes. Not only is she ready,
she's ready to kill me.
Yeah, I'm going home. Sorry to bug you.
I guess that's not gonna work, is it?
Looks like you're ready
to be devoured by a lion.
Then again, if you don't come at me like that,
I won't be able to surpass my limits, either.
As you wish, I'll burn you to a crisp!
Black Meteorite!
Is he tracking my mana?
In that case...
Ow...
If I can figure out how your technique works,
I can figure out many ways to deal with it.
Would you like to continue fighting until
you cannot use your anti-magic anymore?
What the heck am I supposed to do?
How do I get my anti-magic to reach him?
Mana and anti-magic...
They are fundamentally different,
but the power to create
and the power to nullify
are similar in that they
are both a form of power.
Which means the way to use them
shouldn't be that different, either.
The basic technique in using the Mana Method
is to feel the flow of mana.
Which means the thing you
need to do right now...
...is to feel the flow of anti-magic!
She's faster than my ki can track.
Is that all you've got?
You can't win if you just keep running away!
How the hell is she so fast?!
But if that's also
thanks to Mana Zone,
I should be able to do it, too!
Too slow!
Here, get an up-close feel for what
you can really do with Mana Zone!
Well... what to do?
Hot! Hot!
I guess I should've expected
that from the Mana Zone expert.
She's definitely something else.
I guess you're as crazy as ever,
you violent lioness.
There's no fun in catching weak prey.
Try struggling more!
If we're just fighting with speed,
I'm definitely at a disadvantage.
Dark Magic: Dark Cloaked Black Blade!
Black Divider!
He disappeared?!
So you're trying to make your
blade longer to reach me.
But you're too slow.
Even if I can sense him with
my ki, I can't keep up.
As long as I use the Mana Method
to increase my speed,
I'll have no problem dodging.
The mages of the Heart Kingdom
borrow power from natural mana.
Depending on the level of their Mana Method,
they will have unlimited use of their mana.
Which means that so long as your attacks
don't reach me, my mana is limitless.
If I keep using up my anti-magic,
I'm going to lose.
What was that?
This is pathetic.
Before the devil has a chance to end you,
I wouldn't mind giving you
your last rites here and now.
I'm already grateful that you're
helping me out with my training.
There's no need for you to do that, too.
I guess I can't even get in the
ring with you unless I can use
that superhuman walking-through-the-air bit.
Think... I need to figure out
an attack that can reach him,
but one that's fast enough so he can't dodge!
I've now seen the powers of the Demon-Slayer
Sword and the Demon-Destroyer Sword.
Does that sword have some
special power, too?
That's right. The Demon-Dweller Sword...
It must have some power
that I haven't drawn out yet.
That reminds me. Back then,
I was able to unleash the mana
that I borrowed from Noelle.
I might be able to do the same
thing with my anti-magic!
It appears as though
you've found your answer.
I'd like another try, please!
Very well.
I won't be holding back
as much on this attack.
If you can hit me even once,
I will declare you the winner.
I'd prefer if you didn't hold back at all!
If you're not going to
make a move, then I will!
And now, I'm gonna kick the air!
Lions hurl even their young
into bottomless valleys.
I'll have no problem hurling you into the lava!
Are you seriously chasing me right now?!
But, I mean... Sisgoleon's right.
If I lose here...
I'm not gonna stand a chance against a devil!
Oh?
Guess we're finally on equal ground.
Equal ground? What are you babbling about?
I'm just saying we're in
the same position now!
You're a babe who just learned
how to walk! Know your place!
I've gotta do something
about that superhuman punch.
Just like when I borrowed
Noelle's mana last time...
I need to infuse the Demon-Dweller
Sword with my anti-magic!
Now, as you wish, I will
show you my true strength.
I just need to keep increasing
my speed with Mana Zone,
and not give her a chance to use magic!
I see. Looks like you can
use Mana Zone somewhat now.
I guess there's no reason for
me to hold back any longer.
You actually thought you were
holding back? Seriously?
I'll now thank you for
showing me a good time.
Try not to die from it.
Can I actually stop all of that?
Well, I'm gonna have to!
Don't doubt that you can do this!
You're just gonna have to!
Right here, right now...
I'm gonna surpass my limits!
Mana Zone: Dark Magic: Black Hole!
This is...
Is he nullifying my mana?
Dark Magic: Dark Cloaked Lightless Slash!
There!
Well done.
Heck yeah! I got a hit in!
Things are finally getting interesting!
I'll turn you into ash and
enjoy a nice, long bath!
Nah, I got the gist of it, so I'm gonna go.
What? Are you scared?
Anyway, see ya.
Well, that's no fun.
If you'll now begin your reports. Potrof?
Rill and Charmy are getting the
hang of using the Mana Method.
They're geniuses, to be honest.
The best thing I can do is
help bring out their potential
and prepare their meals.
Huh... Charlotte and Mimosa are amazing, too.
They're fighting like, "kaboom,"
and getting better like, "fabam"!
If we're talking about
how much they've grown,
I'd say Noelle and Nero have grown the most.
Of course, they are being trained by the
Queen of the Heart Kingdom
and the Water Spirit,
so of course they're going to get stronger.
Looks like you're proud of your students.
Smurik, how is Finral doing?
For the time being, let the wind guide us
and help us nurture the storm within him.
You can never just get to the point, can you?
Did you say something?
I couldn't hear you over
the whispers of the wind.
N-Now, now...
Floga, how about you?
It appears that Leo is
doubting his own strength.
Why not concentrate on your strengths?
My... strengths?
You may not be the most talented,
but you're patient and don't give up.
Your technique is getting
more powerful every day.
You have the strength to endure.
You're you, remember, Leo?
The strength... to endure?
I want to draw out potential
that he hasn't realized yet.
That's my idea.
Yes, I'm counting on you.
How's Asta doing?
Since he wields anti-magic, he is
our trump card against the devil.
It appears as though he's becoming
stronger in his own way.
We don't have much more time.
Please focus everything
you have on this training.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Let us defeat the Spade
Kingdom and the devil.
Spade Kingdom Garrison
There are so many of them.
Their preparations for the invasion are almost
complete. We don't have much more time.
That's...
Rejoice! You will contribute to
the prosperity of the Spade Kingdom!
Hey, where are we going?
Shh! Quiet!
Come on, now! Get up!
We can't go out there right now, Ralph.
I know.
If we can get through that strong
magic region, and even one of us
can reach the Clover Kingdom...
That's the little hope we have left.
We'll just have to hang on to that!
Let's go!
Hello, foolish rebels.
Your friend told us all about you...
in exchange for their
precious daughter's life.
Let's make a break for it!
I'll move up the ranks if
I bring back your head!
It's that simple.
Ralph?!
Ralph!
What are you—
We leave you with our mana.
Please, Ralph...
For him...
You must follow in your father's footsteps...
You're not getting away!
Go!
I promise I'll get there!
I'll get to them...
Just beyond this cliff
is a strong magic region.
Will I be able to get through?
No...
I can't let their sacrifice go to waste.
I am my father's son!
I will see this through!
There he is!
Get him!
I cannot be defeated here.
Lord Yuno!
Did we do it?
I'm not sure.
But even if he's still alive,
that's a strong magic region.
It won't be long before he perishes.
Yeah.
Foolish Resistance. Serves them right.
Let's head back.
We're too close to the strong magic region.
Who knows what will happen
if we hang around too long?
Yeah.
Spade Castle
The son of the former commander of
the Mage Defense Force's 1st Division?
Yes. According to what another
one of the rebel scum told us,
apparently his name is Ralph.
His name appears in—
It doesn't matter.
A single fly isn't going to
bring any harm to our plans.
Who am I, you ask? I guess I wouldn't
mind telling you a little about me.
Next time on Black Clover,
Page 157: "Five-Leaf Clover."
Page 157
Five-Leaf Clover
Within the clover's fifth leaf resides a devil.