And in the clover's fifth leaf resides...
a devil.
What Asta, who was born without magic,
gained from the five-leaf grimoire was
the power of anti-magic,
which nullifies any magic.
Meanwhile, the Dark Triad
of the Spade Kingdom
also possessed the powers of
the devils from the underworld,
and began invading the other kingdoms.
Asta continued to fight
while believing in himself,
along with his friends...
to protect this world!
At last, the battle against the devil
and the Spade Kingdom began.
Asta and the others spent six months
training in the Heart Kingdom.
They then rescued some citizens
of the Spade Kingdom
and succeeded in taking
over one of their bases.
Meanwhile, back in Hage Village,
where Asta and Yuno grew up,
the wheels of fate were beginning to turn.
O-Oh, no!
Lord Yuno...
Quiet Lakes and Forest Shadows
Where are Nash and the others?
I sent them off to school.
I'm sure this would make
some of the kids nervous.
Yes.
How is he doing?
He's still asleep.
I used a recovery spell,
but his wounds are deep.
Maybe he ran into some bandits in the forest.
Depending on the situation, we may
have to contact the Magic Knights.
Yes.
Who could he be?
Good work, everyone.
Thanks to you, we were able to make
one of the Spade Kingdom's bases,
the town of Tolon, our own.
I hear that all the citizens of the
Spade Kingdom who were captured
in the mobile fortress are recovering.
Thank you very much.
Are you sure you wanted us to come back?
You could've just had your
forces proceed from there.
Stage two guys weren't enough.
I wanna fight someone stronger.
We're dealing with devils here.
We can't just go barging into the unknown.
We have to rest and recover.
Will the town be all right
in terms of its defense?
You can leave that to us.
I asked Noelle to take one of
my clones to the town of Tolon.
Through that clone, I've set up the same
barrier there that the Heart Kingdom has.
Because I have the devil's curse within me,
I can sense the devil's magic immediately.
Let's continue to gain more territory and
corner the devil in the Spade Kingdom.
Yeah!
Honestly... You sure are making that
sound much easier than it's going to be.
That's all for today.
Please keep up the good work.
But with Loropechika's powers,
we might just be able to do it.
This queen is insane.
I still haven't had enough yet.
Hey, Gaja. Play with me again today.
The Spirit Guardian of Fire who trained me,
Floga, is extremely powerful,
but I'd love to know how
powerful you are, too.
I'd also love to spar with you.
Ooh! Me, too!
All of you just returned from battle,
so please get some rest.
No, I'm totally fine!
You don't need to worry about me!
Then let's have a bloodbath together!
I'm getting fired up!
Ooh, this sounds like fun.
I'd like to join in, too.
You know you can't do that,
Loropechika! What are you saying?!
I'm fi—
Loropechika!
Everyone seems well.
Honestly, they're all so stupid.
I got all dirty in the strong magic region,
so I'm going to take a bath.
I shall join you, Noelle.
You're going too, Loropechika.
You're a queen, so you need to enjoy
an elegant bath, not a bloodbath.
All right...
Oh, I just happen to know
the best place for a bath.
The cuties from the Clover Kingdom are
going to take a bath with the beautiful
queen of the Heart Kingdom...
No, don't, Finral!
Don't you dare get excited over any
woman other than Miss Finnes!
Resist!
Finral, make up any weird
fantasies and I'll kill you.
Noelle! I'm doing everything
I can to resist right now!
Th-There's trouble!
In the Polnfrume Forest...
A wild Charmy has appeared!
If we don't do something,
she'll eat up all the fruits in the forest!
Again?
Wait, again?
Well, you see, it appears Miz Charmy really took
a liking to the food in the Heart Kingdom.
And she's been causing trouble everywhere.
In one of the forests, she took
over a group of monkeys
La...
and had them bring her bananas.
And in another forest, she fought
a bear over some super rare apples.
La...
Well, the fruits in the Heart
Kingdom are indeed delicious.
It must be the pure water here.
Good grief. We should go fetch her
before she causes any more trouble.
I'll go! I'm sure you're pretty tired
from moving all those people around,
so you should get some rest, Finral.
I think you moved around
way more than I did, Asta.
But I don't use any magic, so I'm fine!
I'm talking about your stamina, actually...
Well, good luck.
We're counting on you.
Yes, ma'am!
Demon-Slayer!
I'm going to control my anti-magic...
and fly!
The kid without magic who
couldn't fly on a broom...
He's turned into an impressive guy.
How lovely.
This is a secret spring that's been
passed down through the generations
of the royal family of the Heart Kingdom.
Oh, my. I'm so honored that
you've brought us here.
I sense some very pure mana.
Elmora Lake has some of the finest
water in all of the Heart Kingdom.
If you bathe in these waters,
your skin will be nice and smooth.
Let's go in.
Indeed.
Finally, I feel so much better.
It's so nice and cold.
Oops! I forgot to take these off.
Oh, Loropechika...
By the way, I've been meaning
to ask you girls this for a while...
Which one of you is dating Asta?
What?!
Ooh, are we talking about relationships?
I'd love to know myself!
W-We're not dating him!
A-Asta is a very lovely gentleman
who's very kind and reliable,
but now is not the time for that.
Then how about when the battle
with the Spade Kingdom ends?
What?
Well, you obviously don't seem to mind.
Oh, but the one who always
seems to be with him is Nero.
Is that because you two are dating?!
His head is nice to perch on.
Is that all it is?
Yes.
So you're only interested
in the top of his head.
I-I see.
Nero's saying that now,
but what if they become closer as
they spend more time together?
So what about you, Noelle?
I'd never date S-S-S-Stupidsta!
Oh, I see.
I see.
Wh-What about you, Loropechika?
Y-Yes. Are you seeing Gaja?
Huh? Me and Gaja? Yeah, no.
Really? But you're always together.
You'd make a lovely couple.
That'll never happen.
I'm sure Gaja feels the same.
Poor Gaja. I'd never tell him that, though.
This is fun!
No wonder you're the leader
of the Spirit Guardians.
Your strength knows no bounds.
Because you both managed to
grow so surprisingly quickly,
this is excellent training for me, too.
I must also become stronger, just like them.
I will protect the Heart Kingdom,
even if it costs my life.
I'm so happy that everyone from
the Clover Kingdom is so nice.
I didn't know what I would do if you
all turned out to be scary people.
That's our line.
I know it was to check our magic stages,
but you just suddenly attacked us.
Sorry about that.
We're very grateful that the
Queen of the Heart Kingdom
is someone as lovely as you, Loropechika.
Mimosa...
And everyone in the Heart Kingdom
has been so kind to us.
Yes.
Well, we're all going to
face the devil together.
I'm glad you're someone we can trust.
Th-Though it's a shame you're so clumsy.
Hey.
Thank you very much.
Despite appearances, I am trying
my best to be a proper queen
in front of the citizens
of the Heart Kingdom.
Though I'm not good at it.
So I'm happy to have some friends
I can be so honest with.
I'm so happy we became friends.
You're so cute, Loropechika.
Oh, come on. Now you're making me blush.
We feel the same as you, Loropechika.
It's so great flying through the sky!
The passing breeze!
The sweet, fruity scent!
Hm? Sweet scent?
She must be there!
Miz Charmy!
Hey, Asta.
Want some noms?
Holy crap, she gained weight!
Just how much did you eat?!
It's all because the fruit in the
Heart Kingdom is so nummy.
You shouldn't eat any more, Miz Charmy!
La? You tryin' to stop me, Asta?
Well, yeah! You've obviously
eaten too much—
Listen up, Asta.
We don't eat to live.
We live to eat!
What?!
So...
People who get in the way of good eatin'
will get run over by sheep and die.
Uh, what?
Miz Charmy?!
What's going on?
Hey, that's...
That's Charmy's sheep!
Charmy's out of control!
Charmy...
Golden Dawn Headquarters
Vice Captain, do you have a moment?
I'm about to go on a mission.
Is this urgent?
Well... we've received a message
from a church in Hage Village,
out in the boonies.
Tell me at once.
That's Charmy's sheep!
Charmy's gone wild!
Cotton! It's using cotton to gather food!
It's headed this way!
She's attacking with all
the hungry forest animals!
At this rate, all of the food in the
forest is going to be gobbled up!
I...
I may have created a monster.
The Mana Method basically makes recipes...
and the dishes they create are magic!
That means I must eat in order
to learn the Mana Method, la!
I didn't really understand her logic,
but I decided to support her.
Charmy is a genius Magic Knight.
The best thing I could do for her would
be to make her talent shine even more.
But she fell in love with all
the food in the Heart Kingdom,
and she ended up at the top
of the forest's food chain.
It's my duty to stop her!
Plant Magic: Evergreen Vida Valtoria.
I can't stop it! They're just
going through. In that case...
Wow!
Way to go, Sir Potrof!
W-We're finished!
Oh, dear.
I thought I was going to suffocate!
Are you all right, Asta?
Potrof! Thank you!
At this rate, everyone's dinners
are going to be stolen, too!
Will you help me out, Asta?
Right back at you!
Fruits are truly the best.
They're delicious, healthy, and mostly water,
so you never gain weight.
So you still haven't given up, Master.
But once the flames of my hunger have
been lit, not even you can stop them!
Then I'll just have to
stop you once and for all!
La?
All right!
What?!
That's not fair!
Then I'll just have to cut it
somewhere that can't be avoided!
'Scuse me for a bit!
What the heck?! I keep cutting,
but there's no end!
Oh, crap!
Even Asta doesn't stand a chance...
Does this mean all we can do is
watch as she devours everything?
Leave this to me, Potrof!
Rill!
Charmy... we trained together.
As your friend, I cannot allow
your rampage to continue!
Picture Magic: Invasion of Heat-Infused Ice!
You saved me, Rill!
I see! We can attack it if it's frozen!
Let's go, Asta!
Yeah!
La!
They defeated the Charmy!
Thank you!
Goodness, my students caused a mess...
Though I am happy with how much they've grown.
La...
Charmy, overeating is bad for you.
Sorry. It's just that the Heart Kingdom's
fruits are so yummy
that I couldn't help myself.
You totally saved me back there, Rill.
You got even more insane than before!
Well, training in the Heart Kingdom
has been super fun.
And whenever I think of a certain someone,
my inspiration and need
to create just won't stop.
A certain someone?
The goddess who saved me when
I was possessed by the elf.
She's my soulmate!
I want to become a powerful man worthy
of her... and a powerful captain.
That goddess...
is totally Miz Charmy, Rill!
Huh?
What are you talking about, Asta?
They're totally different. She wasn't this fat.
Yeah, I know that, but...
And what are you talking about, Rill?
I'm not that fat.
I'm pleasantly plump.
Obviously, the most popular body type.
You're still eating! Can't you
do anything besides eat?!
How rude, Asta! Of course I think of
something besides eating sometimes.
Something besides eating...
I wonder how Yuno is doing.
We're almost to Hage Village.
This place is always so dull.
We're finally alone, but it
doesn't feel like a date at all.
I don't know what they need to tell you,
but we're finally going on a date afterward.
Yuno, are you listening?
Hey, Yuno!
Bell, shut up.
Yuno!
Sister.
Welcome home. Sorry, I know you must be busy.
Yeah! Yuno's super busy!
I'm fine. Did something happen?
Well... why don't you come in first?
You're the spitting image of Lord Ciel.
And that necklace... There's no doubt about it!
Who the heck is this old guy?
Apparently, he's from the Spade Kingdom.
Guess we need to kick his butt, then!
I am not your enemy!
The Spade Kingdom was originally
a peaceful kingdom.
Despite how bitterly cold it got,
the people lived happily under the
rule of the House of Grinberryall...
until the Dark Triad appeared,
exiled the Grinberryalls,
and ruled over the people with fear.
Lord Yuno...
You are our hope. You belong
to the House of Grinberryall.
Meaning...
You are the Prince of the Spade Kingdom!
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
The Ultimate Canvas
The Ultimate Canvas.
I just can't draw her enough!
Ah, my goddess!
Munchy, munchy, munchy,
munchy, munchy, munchy...
Rill, you don't want to draw
this version of Miz Charmy?
I'm too busy trying to get every detail
of the goddess's beauty perfect right now.
This canvas is so soft and smooth.
It's as though I'm painting on a cloud!
This may just become my ultimate masterpiece!
R-Rill, that's—
And done! My ideal goddess has descended!
Wait a minute...
Just how wrapped up were you in your work?!
Ack, please don't eat any more, Charmy!
You're going to stretch my goddess out!
La? Rill, those who get in
the way of others' meals...
Please! No more, Miz Charmy!
You can't be serious.
You can't be serious about me being
the Prince of the Spade Kingdom.
But I am serious.
Next time on Black Clover, Page 160:
"The Messenger from the Spade Kingdom."
Page 160
The Messenger From the Spade Kingdom
I'm serious.