And in the clover's fifth leaf resides...
a devil.
What Asta, who was born without magic,
gained from the five-leaf grimoire was
the power of anti-magic,
which nullifies any magic.
Meanwhile, the Dark Triad
of the Spade Kingdom
also possessed the powers of
the devils from the underworld,
and began invading the other kingdoms.
Asta continued to fight
while believing in himself,
along with his friends...
to protect this world!
When Yuno returned to his
home village of Hage,
he encountered a man named
Ralph from the Spade Kingdom.
Lord Yuno...
You are our hope. You belong
to the House of Grinberryall.
Meaning...
You are the Prince of the Spade Kingdom!
Ralph showed Yuno his history.
At that moment, he received word that the
Golden Dawn headquarters was under attack.
Even so, I'm Yuno of the Clover Kingdom.
The ones who attacked were
mages from the Spade Kingdom,
Gaderois and Foyal...
We are the elite among those deemed
suitable to be bestowed
powers by the Dark Triad.
We, the Dark Disciples, are all stage zero.
...as well as the devil-possessed
Zenon of the Dark Triad.
And Zenon's goal was...
World Tree Magic: Magic Warding Ash!
So that's world tree magic.
To benefit the Spade Kingdom,
I'll be taking you.
Bone Magic: Eternal Fangs.
When he returned to the Golden Dawn's
headquarters, he saw...
Everyone!
...an unbelievable tragedy.
What do you think you're doing...
to my comrades?!
Zenon's Power
There were many members of the
Golden Dawn who looked down on you
for being a peasant.
They despised you and were
jealous of your powers.
That includes myself, too.
Why in the world would you have
to defend the likes of them?
Because they're my comrades.
I don't need a reason to know that
my comrades are important to me.
I'm sorry.
Then let's all go get something
to eat after we're done reporting.
Yuno, wait!
Yuno...
We're also inviting you... rather,
this invitation was specifically for you, Yuno.
Huh? No, I...
Hamon knows a number of places around
the royal capital that serve delicious food.
Let's just invite the whole
gang and have a blast!
Hey!
Becoming the vice captain after just
eighteen months on the squad?
Who the hell do you think you are?
Yeah, seriously.
Thanks.
You little brat.
Take that, and that! Well?
You give up? You give up?
Yuno's actually smiling lately.
Yup.
A smile suits you much better.
Hey! I'm the only one allowed to stare
at Yuno's happy yet bashful face!
Take that, and that.
Hey, what are you doing?
Now, now, calm down. No fighting.
Why, you!
I'm sure we killed about half of them.
And the other half's following right behind.
They died fighting a really strong enemy,
so they should be honored!
Wind Spirit Magic: Spirit Storm!
Oh? So you've been chosen
by the Wind Spirit, eh?
That's great!
My stone magic that's been
enhanced by the devil's powers
is way harder than iron or steel!
No wind is even gonna scratch it!
Mana Zone: Spirit's Hushed Dance.
This guy is attacking me while
protecting those who are about to die.
The arcane stage captain should
be fighting Lord Zenon right now.
Who knew that anyone other than
captains could be a zero stage?
Things are definitely getting interesting!
I'm Gaderois! Who're you?
I have no reason to tell someone like you...
my name!
Aw, guess you don't like me much.
Don't be like that. Let's be friends...
and kill each other!
Why did you attack this place?
Huh? I don't know the details.
But the Dark Triad is in need
of some arcane stage mage.
I don't care as long as I get
to go wild with my magic!
Arcane stage?!
The Dark Triad is the best.
They killed our last king,
a peace-loving fool,
and gave those of us who wanted
to fight even more powers.
The last king was an idiot.
The strong are always right!
The strong are free to do whatever they want!
When you hurt or kill people...
What kind of emotions do you feel?
Huh?! I feel insanely excited and
awesomely refreshed, of course!
That's why I can't give this up!
That's why you're so strong, too, isn't it?!
There's no way...
I'm anything like you, scum!
Wind Spirit Creation Magic:
Spirit of Zephyr!
Not bad!
But your magic still isn't
enough to defeat me!
It's all clear to me now.
Things get messed up in this world
because people like you exist.
No matter how much time passes,
the curse persists.
The hell are you rambling abou—
He's instantly undoing my stone magic?
Whether I'm a mage from the Clover Kingdom
or the Prince of the Spade
Kingdom... It doesn't matter.
I'll cut right through you!
The range on this spell is insane.
I have no idea where the enemy is.
You know...
Your magic is pretty hard.
Steel Magic: Blazing Spiral Lance!
Too bad.
Your magic is just hard. It can't hit me.
Let's go a little stronger
this time, shall we?
I'm a zero stage. I'm a genius
chosen by the Dark Triad.
Even if there was a whole army of
you scrubs, you couldn't beat me!
How in the world are they so much stronger?
He's not even the leader, and his magic
is equal to a Magic Knights Squad Captain.
What's going on with the
mages from the Spade Kingdom?
Everyone's mana is...
I need to do something,
or we're going to be wiped out!
But I can't even tell where the enemy is.
Useless North isn't responding to his magic,
and this is as big as Another Atlas can get.
Some of the elves' magic
still remains within us.
I'm sure some of you would rather disavow it,
since it was used to attack the kingdom.
But now, we can take that tremendous power
and use it as an amazing force
to protect the Clover Kingdom.
After about six months of training,
though I'm still not as powerful as an elf,
I made this power mine.
But the enemy's magic is just too powerful!
Your magic's been destroyed,
as well as your body.
Just give up.
You seem smart enough to understand.
You have no chance.
My will...
has not been broken!
Then just die already, you piece of trash.
Klaus!
Yuno!
He blew away my mist.
He's a natural enemy.
But...
Mist Creation Magic: Sealing Spectral Hands.
The damage from that last fight...
You seem a bit tired.
I knew it. No matter how many of you
there are, you're all just going to die.
I know where you are now, thanks to Yuno!
I'll move myself and Another Atlas,
and rip away your illusionary armor!
You utter trash...
How... can he still move with
his body in that state?
Whenever I have to face someone
with such natural gifts, I think...
Despite how much I may train, I still
might not be able to surpass them.
But now, as a Magic Knight...
I'm going to continue to break through!
Why can I still move?
Because I train regularly.
Letoile!
Yuno! Er, I mean, Vice Captain Yuno.
Thank you for your help.
Team Leader Klaus...
You hardly need to address me that way now.
You're a true vice captain now.
You can stop calling me
"vice captain." It's creepy.
I'm going to be honest. Who cares?
Well, I care!
Yuno's the vice captain!
That's basically almost captain!
So who pushed Yuno to the top?
It's all thanks to me, of course. Who else?
I'm the best partner there is.
Right, Yuno?
Vice captain and captain
are completely different.
Oh, you're just so modest.
Owie.
This mana...
Captain Vangeance...
Impossible...
Who in the world is he?!
Oh, some of you are still alive.
You're...
So Gaderois and Foyal were defeated.
They were only at 40%.
I guess there was no point in bringing
them when they couldn't surpass 50%.
Yuno!
Quickly! Use Spirit Dive!
He's bad news.
There's no time to even dodge!
He's just...
He's too powerful!
Oh?
Klaus...
You bastard!
I can't even cut through
him with Spirit of Zephyr?!
No, he's...
regenerating at incredible speed!
So you're stage zero. Then let me show you...
just a bit of my devil powers.
55%.
It's not that you're weak.
It's just that I'm far superior.
This is all...
for the glory of the Spade Kingdom.
I-It can't be!
Prince Yuno!
Yuno... No! I don't want to leave you!
Prince Yuno...
No...
You're...
But you're supposed to...
What?
This is...
Yuno's squad...
His squad captain's magic.
Y-Yuno!
Thank goodness!
Bell...
Yuno!
I'm... alive?
Lord Vangeance's world tree magic...
He was already quite injured himself.
But he cast a spell this vast for us?
Where's Captain Vangeance?
Was he taken by that man?
Lord Vangeance...
What about the others?
Shiren...
Oh, Shiren...
No...
Hamon...
He was able to save those
on the verge of death...
But even Captain Vangeance's magic
couldn't save those who were already dead.
Half of our squad... is dead.
If only...
If only I had been stronger...
This is but the prologue.
Once our goal is realized,
you will be overwhelmed with despair.
Next time on Black Clover, Page 162:
"The Great War Breaks Out."
Page 162
The Great War Breaks Out