And in the clover's fifth leaf resides...
a devil.
What Asta, who was born without magic,
gained from the five-leaf grimoire was
the power of anti-magic,
which nullifies any magic.
Meanwhile, the Dark Triad
of the Spade Kingdom
also possessed the powers of
the devils from the underworld,
and began invading the other kingdoms.
Asta continued to fight
while believing in himself,
along with his friends...
to protect this world!
Zenon, one of the members of the
Dark Triad from the Spade Kingdom,
attacked the Golden Dawn's headquarters
along with some of the Dark Disciples.
What do you think you're doing...
to my comrades?!
Yuno let his rage explode after
seeing his comrades injured,
and he defeated the Dark Disciples.
55%.
It's not that you're weak.
It's just that I'm far superior.
It looked as though Yuno had died,
but thanks to the spell Vangeance
left behind, the Budding of Yggdrasil,
he came back to life.
The Great War Breaks Out
Humans are evil creatures.
Rage,
fear,
hatred,
revenge,
and destruction...
The true nature of humans is evil.
And we have grown bored of this world.
Now, then...
I guess I should get going, as well.
I can't wait to see what
kind of human he is...
Arcane stage... Yami Sukehiro.
This is awesome!
Aw, I wonder how Loropechika
and her friends are doing.
I hope they're super energetic!
They'd be even more fun to destroy then.
So yummy...
The Heart Kingdom's food is so yummy.
So cute... Charmy's so cute.
Oh, dear. It looks like one troublemaker
took a liking to another.
Hey, Loropechika!
No more spoiling Charmy.
She's about to burst.
Don't you worry.
Charmy's cute no matter what shape she's in.
I will always be a glutton no matter
what shape I'm in, and nothing more.
I'm not exactly sure why she
came to the Heart Kingdom.
Honestly...
Our battle with the Spade Kingdom's
going to happen any day now.
I'm ready to go anytime.
As am I!
We have conquered all of the towns
along the Spade Kingdom's border,
so we now have a foothold.
But we must keep in step.
That's also why Rill and Charlotte
have returned to the Clover
Kingdom for a captains' meeting.
But it's also difficult trying
to hold in these raging emotions.
Wanna fight me, then? I haven't
gotten to fight you for real yet.
Indeed, you're right!
While we're at it, let us include
Asta and have a three-way battle!
Asta's not here, though.
What?!
Training's calmed down for now, so he wanted
to take some gifts back to our hideout.
He went back home with Finral for now.
It's better to relax
before the battle begins.
Why don't you all have
something to eat, as well?
This is all mine, by the way.
The rest of you, please eat something else.
Apparently every last
morsel here is for Charmy.
I told you to stop spoiling her!
Undine!
Yes.
What's wrong, Loropechika?
We're under attack.
In total...
There are six in various locations
throughout the kingdom.
When did they...
They got through the Mana
Zone barrier with ease.
We've told all of the Spirit Guardians
the locations of the enemies
through Undine's clones.
They've gone to defend immediately.
But...
All six have the devil's power,
and they're all stage zero.
Even the Spirit Guardians may
have trouble against them.
Depending on how this goes,
I may need to ask for your help.
Loropechika!
This extraordinary magic...
It belongs to the Dark Triad's Vanica,
the devil-possessed who hosts Megicula.
Megicula...
Nice!
Dark Disciple
Robero Ringert
From the looks of it, we've probably
killed about a hundred of them.
Lady Vanica, we should—
Not yet.
The more filth we kill in this kingdom,
the more serious Loropechika will get.
That makes things way more fun!
As you wish, Lady Vanica...
Please... step on me more!
Gross.
The neutral zone between the Clover
Kingdom and the Spade Kingdom.
The Black Bulls' hideout was placed
here as a front line of defense.
Hey, guys!
I've brought gifts!
Well, aren't you thoughtful
after being gone for so long?
There are no good drinking
snacks anywhere around here.
W-W-Welcome home!
More importantly, I lack Marie essence.
Yeah, I can't really do anything about that.
Hey, the captains' meeting
should be done soon.
Guess I'd better go pick up Yami.
Must be rough always going back and forth.
Thanks for everything you do, Finral.
Yeah, I'm freakin' exhausted.
It's pretty far, so I'm gonna make a few
stops along the way. It'll take a while.
Roger!
See you guys later.
How do you think Gordon's doing
with his curse magic studies?
How the hell would I know?
I just know that I'm never
going near that house again.
This is hard.
You can do it, son.
I believe in you.
Gordon, I've brought your dinner.
This is...
This is the same sandwich you made
me when we went on our first date!
This takes me back to the good old days.
You were eighteen. I was seventeen.
It was destiny.
Tell me more about how
you met, Mama, Papa.
Of course.
I'm just going to concentrate on my studies.
Is Henry resting?
Apparently, he's lacking mana.
A good number of us aren't here
because of training and such.
And since Charmy's gone right now,
we have no way of eating
mana recovery food.
Charmy's totally hooked on the
food in the Heart Kingdom.
I guess Charmy's just
Charmy wherever she goes.
By the way, where's Magna?
Oh, Magna...
Just when I thought he was
back from the Heart Kingdom,
he went off somewhere with Zora.
Maybe they get along since
they both look so mean.
Every...one...
Henry?
The hell?
Did something happen?
The hideout is... floating!
It looks like Yami Sukehiro
isn't home right now.
I guess I'll play with all of
you while I await his return.
An attack from the Spade Kingdom?!
He's the one making the hideout float?
By himself?
Rouge!
Oh?
Here... we... go!
Recombination Magic: The Raging Black Bull.
Well, he looks threatening enough.
Guess I don't need to hold back!
Large Reflect Refrain!
Mana Rocket Punch!
Insolence.
Gravity Magic: Presence of the Demon King.
What the hell kind of magic is that?!
The trees in the area are breaking in half!
If we didn't have Rouge,
we'd end up like that, too.
Ah, you're still in your original shapes
despite being hit by my spell.
Apparently, one of you has magic
that can manipulate natural laws.
To think there was another besides
Yami Sukehiro at the arcane stage.
Excellent.
You're gonna have to deal with me!
Well, aren't you a lively one?
Let's see how much you're
able to entertain me.
Black Slash!
Gravity Magic: Presence of the Demon King.
He negated my magic and then attacked.
Not bad.
Magic that interferes with natural laws...
I didn't expect it to be enough
to overturn death.
You must be that cat's owner.
You two, get behind Rouge!
Fight me!
Asta!
His magic... Not only is it powerful,
but its range is too vast.
On top of using magic that
interferes with natural laws,
you are absolutely beautiful.
Stunning, really.
You are worthy of Dante of the Dark Triad.
The Dark Triad? From the Spade Kingdom?!
So he's the one ruling
over the Spade Kingdom?
You there. Be my woman.
What?!
The hell? You can't be serious!
Oh, I am very serious.
So you're the evil boss, huh?!
Well, that was quite the surprise.
To think there was a devil-possessed
in the Clover Kingdom, too.
Black Divider!
Black Meteorite!
I can't hit him!
He dodged an anti-magic spell
made to track mana... and so easily.
What do we do?
If he's able to dodge,
we just gotta keep attacking
until he can't dodge anymore!
How nice of him to show up here for us.
If we defeat him here, this whole
pain-in-the-ass ordeal will be over.
Asta!
Gauche!
Look... at me!
Mirror Magic: Mirror Brigade!
Mirror Meteorites!
Take this!
With that much anti-magic going
around, and all at super speed,
he has no way to block or dodge them!
50%.
That's impossible!
He warped space?!
What just...
Let us talk for a while.
Though we have different ranks,
we are both possessed by devils.
I'm sure we can see eye to eye.
We're nothing alike!
All those terrible things you're
doing to your own people...
I'll never see eye to eye with you!
I have no idea what you're talking about,
but if you're speaking ill of me,
I will take it as a compliment.
Animals have no malice.
It is the supreme emotion
that only humans have.
I'm sure you're very
familiar with it yourself.
Rage, hatred,
revenge, and destruction...
The power of malice.
When you unleash those feelings of malice,
you are the most human.
Evil is humanity's true form.
You're wrong!
Even I have times when
I'm filled with bad thoughts.
Sometimes that even makes me more powerful!
But I have a strong heart that allows
me to control that and use it for good!
That's what it means to be human!
It appears that you're a rather
unique devil-possessed.
As long as I'm here, I won't
let any of my friends die!
Honestly...
You are my woman.
That means you can't use
that power for anyone else,
you bad little girl.
60%.
No... I trained and worked
so hard to increase my mana,
and it was all expended in an instant.
This isn't good. I don't have enough mana
to move the Black Bull... any longer...
I can't... move...
We're being pinned down from every direction!
I have to do something...
Gravity Magic: Evil God's Pressure Craft.
You leave me no choice.
I'll awaken your true feelings for you.
Don't...
Stop...
Stop!
Gauche!
My beloved... son...
Now that's what truly makes you...
human!
Asta's attack managed to erase that
guy's magic in this whole area.
Now, then... Let's see how you do.
Attacks like that will never reach me.
I wanted to chat a bit, but it appears
you're too busy losing yourself.
Who might that devil be,
Lucifero?
I do not know. If there are any high-ranking
devils in this world right now,
it would probably be Zagred,
who left the underworld.
But it doesn't appear to be him.
A makeshift power like
being able to erase magic
is probably the work of a low-ranking
nothing with only trifling mana.
So that means he's no match for us,
the ones possessed by
the highest-ranking devils...
The Dark Triad!
What in the world is this battle?!
Asta... Are his devil powers going berserk?
But right now, we have no
choice but to rely on Asta.
This isn't good. He won't last long.
Nero, who can seal wounds, isn't here.
Even if she was, this might be too...
Gauche...
I couldn't...
I couldn't do anything...
My transformation magic...
is absolutely useless!
I'm impressed that you can still
do all this in that state.
I guess I'll finish you now.
Goodness. You're still not giving up.
Anything you do is futile.
He managed to predict...
where I'd show up?
How dare you...
mark me?
Please don't die, Gauche!
After all, you're my...
Your what?
I-I'm so embarrassed!
Next time on Black Clover, Page 163:
"Dante VS The Captain of the Black Bulls."
Page 162
What is he, now?
I'm so embarrassed!