And in the clover's fifth leaf resides...
a devil.
What Asta, who was born without magic,
gained from the five-leaf grimoire was
the power of anti-magic,
which nullifies any magic.
Meanwhile, the Dark Triad
of the Spade Kingdom
also possessed the powers of
the devils from the underworld,
and began invading the other kingdoms.
Asta continued to fight
while believing in himself,
along with his friends...
to protect this world!
Undine!
Yes.
The Dark Disciples, who had the devils'
powers bestowed upon them,
attacked the Heart Kingdom.
Leading this attack was
a member of the Dark Triad,
Vanica, who was possessed by Megicula.
Meanwhile, in the neutral zone between
the Clover Kingdom and Spade Kingdom,
where the Black Bulls had
relocated their base,
they were attacked by another member
of the Dark Triad, Dante.
An attack from the Spade Kingdom?!
Rouge!
They momentarily escaped peril
thanks to Vanessa's magic,
and Asta fought back with his anti-magic,
but they were no match for
Dante's gravity magic.
You leave me no choice.
I'll awaken your true feelings for you.
Stop!
Gauche!
Gauche was dealt a mortal blow.
Asta went berserk, losing himself
to rage and hatred.
He was finally able to land
a strike on Dante!
How dare you...
mark me?
I didn't want to taint my hands
with worldly matters...
But you leave me no choice.
Gravity Magic:
Heavy Infighting.
I definitely feel like beating you to a pulp
with my own fists right now.
Gauche... Gauche...
I...
Dante VS The Captain
of the Black Bulls
How dare you show yourself in front
of me like that, you ugly child?!
For heaven's sake.
My daughters are so beautiful,
but you have to be so plain and gloomy!
You made Mother mad again?
Hurry up and do the cleaning,
laundry, and dishes!
Sister...
And you're covered in soot,
you filthy creature.
I guess that goes perfectly with
your name. Grey, covered in soot!
It really does suit her well.
Isn't it perfect? You can hide how
embarrassing you look, you ugly girl.
Wonderful! You should be
covered in soot all the time.
Look, Mother!
My, what a beautiful spell!
It suits you both perfectly.
N-Next year, I can also...
I-I'm so sorry! I'm sorry!
What are you peeking in for, you ugly girl?
You must be jealous of our beautiful magic.
Because an ugly girl like you could
never dream of having such magic.
A laggard like you could never use
any magic that's worthwhile, anyway.
Just stick to your chores, understand?
Y-Yes, ma'am.
I have nothing,
and I'm always getting yelled
at for being a laggard...
But if I work really hard,
maybe my stepmother and stepsisters will...
It seems you've been sneaking around
practicing and not doing your chores.
Did you finally learn a decent spell?
It's been five years since you
got your grimoire, hasn't it?
I'm sure even a loser like you must
be able to do something by now.
Go on, show us.
I'm sure it's going to be as
shabby as you are, though.
Now I can finally...
How dare you?!
We're the only ones who received
these beautiful faces from Mother!
Hurry up and turn back!
Wait... I just learned how to
do it, so I can't really...
You laggard! You stupid, ugly girl!
We'll kill you!
I finally learned this spell,
but I knew my magic couldn't...
I don't know what they'll
do to me if I go back home.
But could someone like me possibly
live out here on my own?
Oh?
Well, well, if it isn't one of the
young ladies from the Whiteley family.
Are you all alone today?
Do you have anything you can spare
for poor, lowly bandits like us?
I-I don't have any money.
I don't have anything I can give you.
Well, you've got on some nice clothes.
Why don't we go ahead and take you?
There's nothing...
Grab her!
I can do...
Are you okay, miss?
U-Um... Thank you very mu—
Don't get the wrong idea.
I only saved you because Marie asked me to.
You're such a nice little girl, Marie!
You're truly an angel! An angel
descended from the heavens!
My little angel Marie!
Thank you for saving her, Big Brother.
I'd do anything for you, Marie.
Oh, there are siblings who
are actually that close.
How nice. I wish I had...
Hey.
What are you doing here, anyway?
Huh? Well, I...
You should probably go home.
Did you run away from home?
If you ran away half-heartedly, go back home.
If you don't have the resolve to
get what you want on your own,
you're not gonna survive
in this rotten world.
I'm pretty sure Gauche never realized it.
I had nothing in this world,
but he gave me the light
I needed to live strong.
I did my best to survive, and...
You're hilarious! Come join my squad!
How long are you going to stand there?
Come over here and have a drink with me.
Come on, you say something, too.
What? I'm too busy burning the
vision of Marie into my eyeballs.
For crying out loud... You're only
ever interested in your sister.
Of course I am! She's an angel!
Yeah, yeah...
She's an angel, isn't she?!
...I was able to see you again!
It might be overboard for
me to call this fate.
But you're the one who led me here.
You gave me a place to belong.
I don't want to lose a
single one of my friends!
You gave me a reason to live.
And...
It doesn't matter what form
you take. You're always Grey.
I found friends I could truly trust like family.
I want to save Gauche!
And...
It's embarrassing, but I want
you to look at me more!
And see how much stronger I've become!
Grey?!
She sealed his wound?
She can do that with
her transformation magic?
What is this magic?
Grey, you...
Asta!
Magnificent!
To think there was another arcane stage.
Your powers are wasted here.
Both of you...
should be my women.
Hey!
Keep your filthy mitts off my squad.
Captain!
I see.
So you're Yami Sukehiro.
You seem like one of those devil-possessed
from the Spade Kingdom.
But I don't give a shit about that.
I don't care who you are. I'm gonna kill you.
Excellent malice, but you
need to know your place.
Gravity Magic: Presence of the Demon King.
I can't control my spatial magic—
Oh? So you refuse to grovel. Impressive.
I've learned a bunch of new
things these past six months.
Guess I'll try some of them out.
Mana Zone and Black Hole...
Dark Magic: Black Moon.
Magic of mine that's within his
territory is being erased.
You go over to the rest of them.
Y-Yes, sir!
So this is dark magic.
Well, then...
I'll send this boulder flying at super speed
and crush you with the inertia.
Dark Magic: Dark Cloaked Dimension Slash!
He cut through space?
Impressive. I'd expect nothing less
from an arcane stage that we seek.
Gravity Magic: Heavy Infighting Gladiator!
He's fast.
I'm using Mana Zone and reading
his ki to predict his moves.
It's not as much as Julius, but...
He's using his gravity to control
the speed of his sword strikes.
Splendid, Yami Sukehiro.
You seem to know a lot about me.
What the hell are you, a stalker?
Indeed! You're the one I'm after.
What?! I gotta say I'm not exactly happy
to be in demand with a guy like you.
You're a key that connects this
world with the underworld.
The underworld?
The hell are you even
talking about, stalker?!
But unfortunately, it appears that Yami
Sukehiro is a rather vulgar and shabby man.
Say that again, jackass!
How did a man like yourself acquire
so many individuals with unique magic?
This is the first time I've
been jealous of a human.
Thank you for this new malice.
But those arcane stage
ladies will now be mine.
From now on, they will serve me and my ends!
Captain!
Arcane stage? Serve your ends?
The hell are you talking about?
I only brought them in because I liked them.
Mana Zone: Condense...
Dark Cloaked Iai Slash.
Ain't no way in hell I'm gonna let
a creep like you have any of them.
The enemy's attacking! Run!
The queen's water will save us!
Over here!
Hurry!
N-No...
Those who have been bestowed powers
by the devil-possessed are this strong?
I'll go.
Gaja!
If the Spirit Guardians don't stand a chance,
no one else in the Heart
Kingdom could possibly...
We need to stop Luck and the
others who went to back them up!
Loropechika!
I'm sure they'll be fine.
So you concentrate on
protecting your kingdom.
For both protecting the Heart Kingdom
and attacking the Spade Kingdom,
Loropechika is absolutely essential.
We will protect you!
No matter how strong the enemy is, I won't
let us get away with losing, everyone!
That was one of the Spirit Guardians who are
some of the most powerful in this kingdom?
I'm so disappointed. But what can you do?
After all, I'm... Lady Vanica's favorite!
I'm a Dark Disciple with
50% of the devil's power...
The Great Svenkin!
Dark Disciple
Svenkin Gatard
Now, time for some cleaning up.
Oh?
Well, look at the cutie who just arrived.
You're not from this kingdom, are you?
Then you're probably better off staying put.
Don't wanna.
I like you.
Well, your speed, at least!
Lightning Magic: Thunderbolt Destruction!
My skin magic lets me be
as tough or soft as I want.
I change the constitution of my skin
depending on my opponent's
magic to nullify its effects.
My body is the ultimate spear and shield!
It doesn't matter what you—
I just told you, it's useless!
I'm way into the zero stage,
while you're first stage at most.
You get it, don't you?
You have no chance at winning.
You should just use that
speed of yours to run away.
Why would I run away from such a fun fight?
Ah, so you're actually a dummy.
So why are you attacking the Heart Kingdom?
Why, for Lady Vanica, of course!
No woman is as powerful and beautiful as her.
She is my ideal and my idol!
Huh... So that's reason enough
for you to hurt people.
That's reason enough?
Then why in the world do you put
your life on the line for others?
Just look at how beat-up you are.
You're pretty selfish,
squashing people's happiness like that.
Do whatever you want!
And I'll do what I want!
Then I'll do what I want to and protect them.
Because...
I'm a Magic Knight!
Hey.
Show me how to do the true
lightning magic that you use.
As the name suggests, it is a spell
that produces a real lightning bolt.
Despite being a Spirit Guardian,
it took me two years to learn it.
Aw, and it seemed pretty fun, too.
I am an expert at discharge
spells, so it works out.
What you're good at is equip spells.
You can instantly form arrays
near your hands and feet.
Use that to your advantage and
create your own powerful spell.
Just being fast won't be enough to defeat me.
Your magic won't work on me,
and you're already busted up.
Why not give up?
Seriously...
I'm telling you it won't work.
My skin detects your mana and
instantly auto-initiates.
He got rid of a piece of armor.
Well, that was a clever thing to do.
In that case, I'll show you
how clever I can be, too.
Skin Magic: Skin Fort!
Magic Shells for all!
I need to be... faster.
You're a tough one.
I'm sure your mana won't
hold out for much longer.
I'll make sure to take good care of you
when you run out of mana and can't move.
Even... faster.
What? He only scratched me,
and I took this much damage?!
Does that mean his speed is getting faster
than my skin's ability to sense mana?
In that case...
I'm just going to give
myself rock-hard defense!
Now you won't be able to hurt me at all!
More...
What in the world is this eerie feeling?
This is impossible.
And more...
My skin magic nullifies your magic!
Faster!
There's no way it'll work against m—
True Lightning Magic: Ceranos!
He went... through me?
But that's... impossible.
He turned himself into a
spear of actual lighting?
Thanks! That was a lot of fun!
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Today's the Day
Today's the Day.
Marie...
Today's the day...
I'm going to thank him for
what he did back then.
Hey.
Today's the day...
Isn't Marie the cutest?
She's so adorable it hurts, right?
Today's the day...
Isn't she cute?
I've seen them do that often lately.
What are they even doing?
Isn't she cute?
Today's the day...
Nice communication.
Yay, that was so much fun!
I wonder what the rest are up to.
If they waste too much time,
I'm gonna defeat them all myself.
Next time on Black Clover, Page 164:
"Battlefield: Heart Kingdom."
Page 164
Battlefield: Heart Kingdom
Isn't it exciting when your enemy's strong?