And in the clover's fifth leaf resides...
a devil.
What Asta, who was born without magic,
gained from the five-leaf grimoire was
the power of anti-magic,
which nullifies any magic.
Meanwhile, the Dark Triad
of the Spade Kingdom
also possessed the powers of
the devils from the underworld,
and began invading the other kingdoms.
Asta continued to fight
while believing in himself,
along with his friends...
to protect this world!
Just being fast won't be enough to defeat me.
Skin Magic: Skin Fort!
True Lightning Magic: Ceranos!
One of the Dark Disciples, Svenkin,
who attacked the Heart Kingdom with Vanica,
was defeated by Luck after a fierce battle.
Meanwhile, the Black Bulls' hideout
was under attack by Dante.
Stop!
Gauche!
Grey was able to save Gauche, who was
mortally injured, with unknown magic.
Grey?!
She sealed his wound?
She can do that with
her transformation magic?
What is this magic?
Asta was enraged after seeing his friends
get hurt, and his devil powers went berserk.
But his attacks still didn't work on Dante.
Magnificent!
To think there was another arcane stage.
Dante tried to take Vanessa and Grey,
who were both also arcane stage mages.
But then Yami arrived.
Hey!
Keep your filthy mitts off my squad.
But Yami was the one Dante was truly after!
He believes the key to connect this
world with the underworld is Yami.
Arcane stage? Serve your ends?
The hell are you talking about?
I only brought them in because I liked them.
Mana Zone: Condense...
Dark Cloaked Iai Slash.
Ain't no way in hell I'm gonna let
a creep like you have any of them.
Battlefield: Heart Kingdom
Kill...
Kill... I'll kill them! They will pay...
Kill... Kill...
What...
Kill...
What the heck happened?
My body won't move.
Wait! Gauche!
I can sense Gauche's ki.
He's alive! Thank goodness!
That Spade bastard...
While using Mana Zone with
condensed mana, my iai blade...
will never miss.
I never imagined anyone would
make me use this magic.
What the hell is that magic?
This power is completely different
from the magic he was using earlier!
What's going on?
Envy, rage, hatred... I can't get enough.
Splendid, Yami Sukehiro!
I was bored... of absolutely everything.
There wasn't a single thing...
the could satisfy my malice.
It's just starting. We've only
just begun, Yami Sukehiro.
You will open up an even
more wonderful world.
Yeah, just stop. You're creepy as hell,
Mr. Psycho Hipster Goatee.
You said something about me
being the key to the underworld,
but I dunno what you're talking about.
I don't have any mysterious powers like that.
The thing that connects this
world with the underworld is...
a magic channel called the Tree of Qliphoth.
And to create that Tree of Qliphoth,
we need dark magic and world
tree magic at the arcane stage.
Yes...
That means you, Yami Sukehiro,
and William Vangeance.
This guy knows about William, too.
And what happens once this world
connects with the underworld?
Devils will pour into this world.
Once this world is filled with devils...
It will be overcome with
every possible malice.
Oh, what a delight.
Wouldn't you agree, Yami Sukehiro?
Yeah...
Guess I'm gonna have to
take you out here and now!
If anyone dares to harm this
kingdom's nature or food,
I, Charmy, will never let that stand!
O flames...
Shine beautifully upon me and my hair.
Oh, no... The Polnfrume Forest...
We're finished!
The Spirit Guardian's been defeated.
Sir Potrof shielded us...
You're truly blessed.
You get to engrave
Dark Disciple
Halbet Chevour
the beauty of the Dark Disciple
Halbet Chevour into your eyes before you die.
What do you think you're doing?
Oh?
It seems an unsightly fatty has arrived.
Sir Potrof! Charmy is here!
Charmy...
Charmy!
Hey, Charmy. Did you sneak
away from training again?
Want to take a break and have some food?
You have an amazing talent!
Let's do our best together!
You won't get away with this.
It's Charmy's sheep!
Save us, Charmy!
I guess your magic is as slow as you are.
Oh, dear. Perhaps this is
what they call "affinity"...
Our spells are going
right through each other.
But there's one very decisive difference.
My magic is able to protect me...
But your magic cannot protect you.
Not only is my hair absolutely
beautiful thanks to the devil's powers,
it's also the strongest!
Charmy!
You're so pleasantly plump, you'll have
no chance of escaping my attacks.
Consuming food is idiotic.
All you need for beauty is nutrition.
There's no way you can beat me with my
beauty, strength, and proper nutrition.
I'm done looking at an unsightly fatty.
Let my beauty embrace you as you die!
Hey.
You need to shut your mouth. Didn't I tell you?
You won't get away with this.
Hey.
You need to shut your mouth. Didn't I tell you?
You won't get away with this.
What?
She doesn't even have devil powers.
What in the world is this magic?
Food Magic: Glutton's Banquet.
Well, isn't she an agile one?
In that case...
I'll just have to cook her.
What are you doing?!
The Mana Method is my kitchen.
And when I cook there...
Any dish becomes delicious, so the
wolf won't be such a picky eater!
It appears as though I created a monster.
How dare you do this to
someone as beautiful as me?!
Lookin' good.
I'll just... help myself!
La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la...
True beauty and strength come
from a well-balanced diet!
Thanks, Charmy!
You gobbled her right up!
The Fire Spirit Guardian, Sir Floga,
has also been defeated.
I can't believe he couldn't
defeat them, either.
What is with that attack, anyway?
There's no way to dodge that!
There's no way that Clover
Kingdom boy can win.
Where did they—
Well, he's tough.
My attack didn't even pierce his body.
But I wonder how long you'll hold up.
Your mana just keeps draining away.
Dark Disciple
Sivoir Snyle
You're just going to get punched to
death by me, the Dark Disciple Sivoir.
You cannot escape my
Eye Magic: Catoblepas's Evil Eye.
The countless eyes floating in the
air can not only see where you are,
but can identify your mana
and stamina, too.
I can even predict your next move from where
you're looking and how your muscles move!
When I use those eyes to lock on to you
and shoot my magic shells made
from my condensed mana...
They'll never miss!
Damn it...
Floga...
Why not concentrate on your strengths?
My... strengths?
You have the strength to endure.
You're you, remember, Leo?
Sharpen your senses!
There you are!
Flame Magic: Profound Spiral Flames!
You dumbass. I can easily dodge that attack.
You may be using the Heart Kingdom's arrays
or whatever, but there's still no point.
His attack this time took
longer than the others.
That's because he dodged my attack.
You can move closer all you want.
I'll just have to go farther away.
The enemy is moving, but just as I thought,
the distance between us hasn't changed.
He's keeping as much distance
from me as possible
while staying in his attack range.
I've never been injured or
experienced pain during a battle.
There's no way an attack from a
simpleton like you will ever hit me.
Endure...
I'm not going down until I defeat him!
Just die already. Man, you don't
know when to give up.
It's true. I may not have as much
talent as my brother and sister.
But with those two in front of me,
I've endured and let my inner flames blaze!
There's no way you're gonna win
if you're just enduring, dumbass.
Let's end this.
What?
This is...
What is this giant array?
When did he...
I endured and took my time making it.
All while you couldn't
keep your eyes off of me.
I have to get out of this array!
True Flame Magic:
Crimson Eruption!
Wow...
I've never seen an array so big.
It's hot, hot, hot! I don't like pain!
I've never even gotten scratched before!
How dare you?! How dare you?!
Thanks to all your yowling,
I know exactly where you are now!
How dare you say that after all
the innocent people you hurt?!
S-Stop...
If you aren't prepared to get hurt,
stay off the battlefield!
You won't have your way, Dark Disciple!
Wow!
You're amazing, Sir Gaja!
I hate to admit it, but you're
definitely on another level,
even among the Spirit Guardians, Gaja.
I somehow made it in time.
I need to get everyone to safety and
return to Queen Loropechika immediately.
They've defeated all of the Dark Disciples.
Excellent work, everyone.
Hmph. That's the least they could do.
Thank goodness! Great job, everyone!
My water can't reach where the
enemies were, so I'm grateful.
It doesn't matter how powerful
their opponents are.
The Magic Knights of the Clover Kingdom
evolve when they're in battle.
I sense the mana of some luscious girls!
We knew you would show up.
So we were ready for you!
Plant Magic: Magic Cannon Flower!
You're disgusting!
That was a splendid attack, Mimosa!
It's all thanks to the mana you sent me.
Yoo-hoo!
Such ominous mana...
It's just been so long since I've
seen you, so I came to play!
My widdle Loropechika!
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
The Strength to Endure
The Strength to Endure.
Are you almost at the end
of your rope, Miz Charmy?
I'm still totally fine, la.
You don't need to push yourself, either, Leo.
Nay! Floga has shown me
the strength to endure,
and I shall use it to defeat you, my rival.
It's hot!
W-Water!
Y-You can hop out anytime, Miz Charmy!
A-A-Asta, you're turning blue.
Leo, you don't do well with the cold, do you?
The strength... to endure!
My, but they're lively.
Vanica, I will not let you
have your way any longer.
I now have friends I can depend on!
Next time on Black Clover,
Page 165: "Water Crusade."
Page 165
Water Crusade
Today is the day we end this!