And in the clover's fifth leaf resides...
a devil.
What Asta, who was born without magic,
gained from the five-leaf grimoire was
the power of anti-magic,
which nullifies any magic.
Meanwhile, the Dark Triad
of the Spade Kingdom
also possessed the powers of
the devils from the underworld,
and began invading the other kingdoms.
Asta continued to fight
while believing in himself,
along with his friends...
to protect this world!
The thing that connects this
world with the underworld is...
a magic channel called the Tree of Qliphoth.
Dante said that creating the Tree of Qliphoth
required world tree magic and dark magic.
Guess I'm gonna have to
take you out here and now!
Meanwhile, in the Heart Kingdom,
the battle against Vanica's
Dark Disciples continued.
True Lightning Magic: Ceranos!
First, Luck defeated Svenkin,
who uses skin magic.
And next...
Food Magic: Glutton's Banquet.
I'll just... help myself!
Charmy powered up her food magic
with the Mana Method
and brought down Halbet, who used hair magic.
True beauty and strength come
from a well-balanced diet!
What is this giant array?
I endured and took my time making it.
True Flame Magic:
Crimson Eruption!
Leopold, who had obtained true flame
magic through the Mana Method,
defeated Sivoir, who used eye magic.
If you aren't prepared to get hurt,
stay off the battlefield!
The Spirit Guardian Gaja took care
of Hischer, who used nail magic.
You won't have your way, Dark Disciple!
Plant Magic: Magic Cannon Flower!
You're disgusting!
Robero, who used tongue magic,
appeared before Queen Loropechika,
and fell at the hands of Mimosa, but...
Yoo-hoo!
My widdle Loropechika!
Man, I'm bored.
The three members of the Dark Triad
are also out right now, aren't they?
Yeah. By the way, did you hear?
There might be a spy from
the Clover Kingdom here.
Oh, please! No one would be that stupid.
Guess you're right.
You there.
What are you doing in Lord Dante's room?
Ah, you must be the spy.
Let's have a nice, long chat.
They disappeared?
Where did...
Water Crusade
My widdle Loropechika!
You grunts next to her don't
need to be so guarded, either.
I only cursed you last time
because Megicula asked me to,
but we're going to have so much fun today!
She's the devil-possessed
who hosts Megicula...
Vanica of the Dark Triad.
The one who killed my mother!
Why did you attack the Heart Kingdom
if I'm the one you're after?
Why did you target the places
where my people were?
Well, I thought if I did that,
you'd be even more willing to fight me!
How dare she?!
We've defeated all of your minions!
You're the only one left! I hope
you're prepared to deal with us!
What?
You've defeated them all, you say?
Man, that felt great.
No... He should've been
rendered unconscious.
Ah, Lady Vanica, I am so grateful.
Thanks to you, I was able
to feel good so many ti—
Could you shut up?
Hurry up and take care of all the pests
who aren't my widdle Loropechika.
Lady Vanica, please, stomp on me some more.
You see? Thanks to the curse I put on them,
they just won't die, no matter
how many times you kill them!
Where do you think you're going?
What?
We've only just begun trampling
this kingdom. Long live Lady Vanica!
Dark Disciple
Hischer Ongg
All the other enemies...
Behold the power of love!
All hail Lady Vanica!
How dare you... How dare you
inflict pain and injury on me?!
I was chosen by Lady Vanica!
How dare you put someone as beautiful
as me through something so disgraceful?!
I'll wreck everything with the eternal
beauty that Lady Vanica gave me!
Looks like they're all still yapping.
Bring it on!
I told you, you will not have your way.
But if you don't defeat me, they're just
going to keep coming back to life...
Until they exterminate every
last person in this kingdom.
Do you feel like playing with
me now, my widdle Loropechika?
Let's go, Loropechika.
Yes.
Noelle! Let us fight, too!
Right!
Water Creation Magic: Valkyrie Armor!
We will defeat you!
Water Creation Magic: Sea Dragon's Roar!
Blood Magic: Red Beast.
What was that snake
supposed to be? An attack?
Don't worry. I'll play with you girlies.
I snuck some magic-controlling
weed seeds into that last attack.
I can't move...
But neither can you!
Mimosa!
Leave this frog to me. You two
take care of that devil-possessed!
Both of your magic powers
are the best, Lady Vanica!
Blood magic and curse-warding magic...
Just like Loropechika said, she's...
Uh, Loropechika?
Loropechika!
Ah! Yesh?!
S-Sorry, I was checking something.
Checking something? It looked
like you were just spacing out.
More importantly, the Spade Kingdom...
Oh, right.
Each member of the Dark Triad uses
two different magical attributes.
Their own, and the one their devil has.
Vanica and Megicula...
I've fought them once before, so I will
come up with a strategy against them.
Let us train toward that.
Excellent, my widdle Loropechika!
I wonder if Dante and Zenon
are also having fun right now.
But I definitely get to have the most fun!
It's widdle Loropechika,
and I get to kill her if I want!
Loropechika has me. That won't be happening.
World tree magic and dark
magic sound fun and all...
But having to drag them back
sounds like such a pain!
Dark magic?
What do you mean, drag them back?
What are the other two members
of the Dark Triad doing?
What? Why should I have to tell you?
World tree magic... Dark magic...
The Queen of the Heart Kingdom
inherits the previous queens' powers,
which includes their knowledge and experiences.
This is where that colossal
amount of information
gets realized in Loropechika's mind.
This place is why she is called
the "All-Knowing Priestess."
That's... awful.
Loropechika!
They're...
If we let the Dark Triad have their way,
the door connecting the underworld where
the devils live to this world will open,
killing more than 90% of
the people on this continent,
and the world will cease to be!
What?!
That's... awful.
Loropechika!
They're...
If we let the Dark Triad have their way,
the door connecting the underworld where
the devils live to this world will open,
killing more than 90% of
the people on this continent,
and the world will cease to be!
What?!
How could you do something so awful?
People are going to die, too!
I want my blood to seethe with all of the
blood of the strong people left behind!
I have no interest in the
weak who're going to die.
But who cares about the future?
Let's enjoy the pres—
Indeed, we cannot let
these people roam free!
That's why we will defeat
you right here and now!
The fate of the world is in our hands.
Mana Zone plus Mana Method...
Water Spirit Magic...
Ludic Sanctuary!
This water cuts the power
of your blood magic in half
and powers up Noelle's magic!
Harder! Even harder!
What...
The lighter your armor, the more
you can become one with the water!
That will also assist you in becoming
one with the water and moving faster!
Valkyrie Armor ~ Mermaid Form!
I won't let you have your way any longer!
Nice!
Aw, there was someone who could
team up with widdle Loropechika.
This is going to be even more fun, then!
Don't croak too fast, okay?
Devil Power: 50%!
She has this much power even
when it's difficult for blood
to harden within my magic.
As I expected... a normal attack
won't be enough to defeat her!
Noelle!
Nice! I'm getting even more fired up!
51%!
She only went up one percent,
and her power is insanely stronger!
I guess you only think about
satisfying your desires.
52%!
Is that how you killed my mother...
Acier Silva of the Clover Kingdom?!
53%!
Who's that? I have no interest in the past,
so let's just enjoy this moment!
Just give up and let me lick you.
We're never going to die because
of Lady Vanica's magic.
We trained really hard so we
wouldn't lose to the likes of you!
Not just for the world...
Or to avenge my mother...
You're truly magnificent, Loropechika.
We've gotten so much stronger.
Y-Yes. I guess maybe you had
something to do with that.
But of course! Loropechika is amazing!
Oh, no. I'm not that... I'm just...
Just so you know, humility is
going to sound fake right now.
My mana and magic are both passed
down from all the other queens.
Well, your mana is amazing to begin with.
It can't be inherited just by anyone.
Since I'm so clumsy and silly,
I wonder if I'm worthy of being
the Queen of the Heart Kingdom.
When I previously fought against Vanica,
who is possessed by Megicula,
I was frightened.
And because of that, I was cursed.
I am unfit to be the queen.
When I'm before you, I forget about
my status as queen, and I can be honest.
I wonder why.
Saying this probably makes me even
more unfit to be queen, but...
I'm...
so afraid of dying.
I don't want to die!
I have so much to think about
as the queen of this kingdom!
But I... I...
Oh, I'm sorry. A queen shouldn't
cry so much in front of others.
Seriously, what are you even talking about?
It's totally fine if you cry.
Especially in front of friends.
Exactly.
Noelle... Mimosa...
How in the world did you just trip?!
We...
are going to win, no matter what!
For our truly kind...
...friend!
65%!
66%! 67%!
Nice! Okay, here I go! I'm gonna do it!
I'm going to give it my all!
70%!
Noelle!
That's what we were waiting for!
We'll have Vanica use all of the
devil's power she can right now.
We'll have her increase how much
blood she sheds from her blood magic
and make her use up her mana.
That way, she will use the devil's power.
We should be able to go
head-to-head with her.
And when she uses up all of
the devil's power that she can,
we'll use our trump card.
That will be you,
our mage of the arcane stage...
Nero!
Nero's arcane stage...
Noelle's combative spirit
and fighting style...
If you two grow along with Undine and me,
we should be able to defeat Vanica,
as well as Megicula, who possesses her.
Nero, you're doing this, too.
I'm going to seal that devil's
power you're so proud of!
Mana Method: Sealing Magic ~ Eternal Prison!
I won't let scum like you take
the world or Loropechika!
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
What the Queen of the
Heart Kingdom Inherited
Heart Kingdom Inherited.
The Queen of the Heart Kingdom
inherits the previous queens' powers,
which includes their knowledge and experiences.
This is where that colossal
amount of information
gets realized in Loropechika's mind.
This isn't it.
This isn't it, either.
It's not this, either.
Or this. Or this.
Ugh, dang it!
Why were all the previous
Queens of the Heart Kingdom
unable to sort anything in order?!
That goes for you, too.
Sniffle, sniffle...
No matter how powerful the enemy is...
No matter how cornered we are,
we'll never give up.
We'll continue to surpass our limits.
That's what the Black Bulls do.
Next time on Black Clover,
Page 166: "Captain: Yami Sukehiro."
Page 166
Captain: Yami Sukehiro