And in the clover's fifth leaf resides...
a devil.
What Asta, who was born without magic,
gained from the five-leaf grimoire was
the power of anti-magic,
which nullifies any magic.
Meanwhile, the Dark Triad
of the Spade Kingdom
also possessed the powers of
the devils from the underworld,
and began invading the other kingdoms.
Asta continued to fight
while believing in himself,
along with his friends...
to protect this world!
We will defeat you!
The fate of the world is in our hands.
Valkyrie Armor ~ Mermaid Form!
Loropechika and Noelle used the strategy
they came up with to fight Vanica.
And...
Nice! Okay, here I go! I'm gonna do it!
I'm going to give it my all!
70%!
Noelle!
That's what we were waiting for!
Nero!
I'm going to seal that devil's
power you're so proud of!
Mana Method: Sealing Magic ~ Eternal Prison!
I won't let scum like you take
the world or Loropechika!
We did it!
I did it. I sealed away Vanica's
mana and the devil's power.
Now Megicula's powers should
stop working upon this kingdom.
Loropechika's curse should be lifted.
No...
You are clearly weaker than us,
and yet you were able to produce
such unpredictable magic.
You truly are interesting.
This ominous mana... Oh, no!
Loropechika!
Captain: Yami Sukehiro
What's going on?
You really shouldn't look away!
Here we go! Take that!
Let's see how you do against this!
You must have thought of many
things in order to defeat us.
A little bit more, and you would have
successfully sealed away my powers.
You're truly splendid... All of you.
It makes me...
want to toy with you even more.
Megicula...
How? Nero should have been
successful in sealing you away.
Curse-Warding Magic: Decaying World.
It weakens spell arrays that affect me.
It was already activated at 70%.
It even managed to weaken the sealing
magic used by an arcane-stage mage.
That was an excellent experiment.
Hey, Megicula! Don't get in my way!
I'm trying to have fun here!
Loro...pechika...
This is the first time I've
ever cursed a Water Spirit.
This was also an excellent experiment.
So this is what happens when I curse one.
Un...dine...
Peeka...boo!
Oh, you're just adorable!
It's time to study.
Let's take the day off today.
What? Can we?
Of course.
Taking a day off never hurt anyone.
We can just do our best again tomorrow.
Okay!
She was always by my side.
You're doing wonderfully, Loropechika.
Really? You think my magic is okay?
It's perfect! Have more
confidence in yourself.
And she always consoled me.
Such a beautiful kingdom.
Yes. This is our kingdom.
Protecting this kingdom...
Do you think I can do it?
Of course you can, Loropechika.
She was always the closest to me.
Undi—
Oh, pardon me. Your curse must have
activated because I moved closer to you.
You probably can't move
due to the excruciating pain.
And now you can't use your water spirit.
This is the end.
Hey, hold on, my widdle Loropechika!
Things were just getting good!
You've still got some
spunk in you, don't you?
Undine...
Yeah, she's done.
You can die now.
Loropechika...
You two...
That's enough!
No one cares about you anymore!
You're no big deal without
Loropechika's magic, are you?
See?
So slow.
Noelle!
You're trying to get in Lady Vanica's way?
What a bad little girl.
You just need to stay
put and let me lick you.
There's too much of a power difference.
I'm just not in the mood anymore.
Not yet.
None of that matters!
This little girl...
There's no way that what you're doing...
should ever be...
forgiven!
Aw, too bad!
That was a good last push, but your
little attack has no effect on—
I won't let you...
kill Loropechika!
Point-Blank Sea Dragon's Roar!
Red Beast!
See? It's no use. Your attack
doesn't do anything to m—
Huh?
This is...
What was your name again?
Noelle Silva.
I'm royalty from the Clover Kingdom...
and one of the Magic Knights
from the Black Bulls!
You managed to injure my body again.
Absolutely magnificent!
But I rather hate this unsightly magic.
Very well, then. I'll show it
just to you, Yami Sukehiro.
The true powers of a human
who hosts a devil!
Bring it on. I guess I'll show you, too...
The true powers
of an ordinary human!
We were keeping watch until we
could attack the Spade Kingdom.
So how did things end up like this?
Should I try to go back up Yami?
Or should I go get some other
Magic Knights Squad captains?
No, I can't...
If I move now,
he'll kill me instantly!
Devil Power: 80%.
So 80% is what you call getting serious?
Where's all that mana coming from? Damn it!
Well, Mostly-Black-Line-Faced Man?
We devil-possessed share powers
with the devils in the underworld.
Since these exchanges take place
between our world and the underworld,
Underworld
we cannot unleash 100% of our powers unless
we open the door to the underworld.
This World
Though I'm not certain about
the devil-possessed over there.
Gravity Magic: Gravity Singularity.
As long as you're alive,
we'll have everything we need.
I guess I can tear off one
of your legs, at least.
Hey, come on, now. That would've
been way more than my leg!
Dark Cloaked...
Dimension Slash!
He managed to warp my Dimension Slash!
This gravity's way more powerful
than what he's been using.
If I hit him with Black Moon,
they might cancel each other out.
But as long as he's generating his gravity,
I can't afford to lose Black Moon!
I'll just have to get behind him by keeping
my Mana Zone condensed
and my senses razor-sharp!
No, wait a sec!
There's no point in cutting him
down if he'll regenerate!
I need a more powerful, precise attack.
I'll concentrate on one point.
You were quite enjoyable, Yami Sukehiro...
For a human, at least.
Ya...
Yami!
Captain!
Now, then...
Next up...
Right here, right now...
I'm going to surpass my limits!
I'd be a pretty lousy captain...
if I couldn't do that in front of my squad!
I'll take that condensed Mana Zone...
and condense it even further,
concentrating it to a single point!
Excellent, Yami Sukehiro!
But you cannot defeat me!
Dark Magic:
Death Thrust!
Wha...t?
I was going for a thrust,
but ended up with a cannon.
Holy crap... Captain Yami really is amazing!
My bad. I mean, you basically
looked like a target.
Impossible.
There should be no human who can
fight me when I'm at my best.
No, but there is one. Right here.
That's why I'm in this pathetic state now.
How truly annoying.
Thank you, Yami Sukehiro.
He couldn't be... Not from that state...
He's regenerating?
My innate magic is body magic.
The devil's power explosively
boosts my ability to regenerate.
I cannot die, age... or deteriorate!
But I'd rather not use my
body magic if I can avoid it.
I detest how ugly it is when
I regenerate or transform...
Because it means that I'm being pushed.
Hey, come on, dude...
This guy's not human anymore.
But at the same time, it's oh so gratifying!
Death Thrust!
You truly are magnificent, Yami Sukehiro!
Your instincts and techniques
in combat surpass my own.
I am deeply jealous.
But you see, I don't die!
That one overwhelming power is enough to
make it impossible for you to defeat me!
The world is unequal and unfair!
There are phenomena that are
totally out of your control!
Just like me!
It doesn't matter if the talented
or those who have trained
manage to miraculously point their blade
at my throat through trial and error.
In the end, I just have to crush
them completely, and I will win!
And that is supreme ecstasy!
Captain!
Captain Yami!
I can't get close enough to him!
If I get too far away, he starts
chucking rocks at me from all directions.
This bastard...
Captain Yami is fighting after
surpassing his limits, and here I am...
Stand! Move, my stupid body!
Damn it... Damn it!
Captain Yami...
Damn it!
Yeah... I can't win this on my own.
This dude won't die. He's insane,
creepy, and he has, like, infinite mana.
Hey.
I can't win this one without you...
Asta!
I'll kill you, brat.
Hey, brat. Were you watching that?
Hey, brat.
Why are you wimping out, you dumbass?
I don't give guys jobs they can't do.
Do something about him in your own way.
Well done, brat!
What? Are you worried about me?
You're thousands... No, a million
years too early for that!
Right!
Excellent!
Entertain me even more!
You'd better keep up, Asta.
Right, Captain Yami!
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
I Wanna Lick
I Wanna Lick.
I wanna lick... I wanna lick...
I wanna lick!
And I'd rather not be licked.
Will this do?
This is so sweet and yummy and worth licking!
Then how about this?
This is cold, sweet, and
has a mild yet rich flavor.
This is high up on the "wanna lick" chart.
Now we can put an end to
this pointless fighting.
But something seems to be missing.
Leave that to me!
This is what you were missing, right?
Oh, you know me so well.
Please, step on me harder.
Impressive, Noelle. I knew what he was
asking for, but I could never go that far.
Here we go, Asta!
We're starting our counterattack!
Right, Captain Yami!
I'm going to surpass my
limits and give it my all!
Next time on Black Clover,
Page 167: "Black Oath."
Page 167
Black Oath