And in the clover's fifth leaf resides...
a devil.
What Asta, who was born without magic,
gained from the five-leaf grimoire was
the power of anti-magic,
which nullifies any magic.
Meanwhile, the Dark Triad
of the Spade Kingdom
also possessed the powers of
the devils from the underworld,
and began invading the other kingdoms.
Asta continued to fight
while believing in himself,
along with his friends...
to protect this world!
Oh, I just had a great idea.
Hey, Megicula, let's not kill her after all.
Oh? And why is that?
I thought it would be better to truly
kill the wisdom of the Heart Kingdom.
Oh, who cares about that?
Let's take her to the Spade Kingdom.
I just remembered.
I fought some chick in armor
just like you, my widdle Noelle.
If I remember correctly... Ah!
She was my widdle Acier!
Oh, that was so much fun!
Back when I fought her,
she got super strong after
I took a child hostage.
If I take her hostage,
you'll get even stronger, too,
won't you, my widdle Noelle?
Not that I really understand, but she's
your precious little friend, right?
Right?
No one's going to complain
if I keep her, right?
Honestly... You never cease
to fascinate me, Vanica.
Well, I guess we're done here.
Loropechika! Noelle!
Lady Vanica, are we going back
to the Spade Kingdom already?
Could you wait just a moment?
Just a little more and I'll have her—
Don't talk to me. You're gross.
Actually, I don't need any of you anymore.
Huh?
Curse-Warding Magic: Exploding Life.
His mana is expanding.
Lady... Vanica...
What... are you...
It's a curse bomb!
You know that devil power
I gave you Dark Disciples?
It's going to go all kaboom now!
What?!
Wait... Lady Vanica...
Lady Vanica, you wouldn't...
Please wait, Lady Va—
This whole area's gonna go kablooey,
but I'm sure you can
survive that, Widdle Noelle!
Well, I'll be waiting in
the Spade Kingdom for you!
Get stronger, okay?
My wid-dle No-elle!
Vanica!
Black Oath
The key here is definitely Asta's anti-magic.
We have to somehow hit that
guy with Asta's sword.
Damn it! I'm definitely holding him back!
I'm only hanging in there
because of Captain Yami!
My six months of training isn't nearly
enough to stand against him.
More... Entertain me more!
This is all just feeding my pleasure!
If I don't try to use all of the
unknown powers that are inside me...
Hey, you're watching, aren't you... my devil?!
Welcome.
Who the hell are you?!
Well, that's cold.
I'm the one who's been the closest
to you this whole time.
I remember now.
We've met like this before,
though you seem a bit different now.
Kill...
Kill... I'll kill them! They will pay...
I felt your rage earlier.
I'm not sure why, but you want to
defeat that guy, too, don't you?
I should've had a real heart-to-heart
with you much sooner.
I'd like to do that now.
So please... lend me your powers!
Please!
Very well...
I'll give you some of my true power.
But as things stand right now, it won't work.
I'll need something equal in return.
Something in return?
I'll be taking a part of your body!
You're making a deal with a devil.
Are you sure you still want this?
Even if I become a devil...
No matter what I have to do...
I have to surpass my limits.
I can't win this one without you...
Asta!
Those words mean that much to me.
If I can't get through this, there's no
way I can become the Wizard King!
You're funny, kid.
Join my squad.
And then, someday,
become the Wizard King.
I will become the Wizard King.
But before that...
I want to be someone who can live up to
Captain Yami's hopes and expectations!
Very well. I'll give it to you.
Gravity Magic: Gravity Singularity!
This is everything...
that I've got right now!
Fifty seconds.
That right arm is no longer the same as when
I was just dribbling some power into you.
It is power itself.
Your body won't last more than fifty seconds.
That's plenty!
Excellent, boy!
The way he's fighting... He's definitely
on guard when Asta attacks.
Is there anti-magic coming
from his right hand?
If Asta can get a clean hit in on Dante...
We can win!
Kick-ass job, Asta!
Then I guess I need to...
work a bit harder, too!
You, too, Captain Yami!
What's that going to do now?!
Excellent, you two.
More... More!
Asta...
Yami!
Entertain me...
Entertain me even more!
Both of them are
moving at insane speeds...
But it's like they're totally in sync.
Time Until Asta's Devil Powers Run Out
Despite everything going on,
they look like they're having fun.
8 Seconds Remaining
Even so...
Even so, in the end...
I will crush everything...
and win!
Demon-Dweller!
Demon-Destroyer!
You're mine!
3 Seconds Remaining
I am...
immortal!
This is the end!
Yeah, for you.
We win!
Well done, Asta, you crazy son of a bitch.
Thanks.
You guys!
That was amazing!
Yeah, you guys are just... You're amazing!
Thanks.
Damn straight.
Did... you... win?
I... What...
Gauche...
Gauche!
Th-Th-Th... Thank goodness!
Uh, Grey...
Huh?
I-I-I-I'm so sorry!
Why are you apologizing?
Well, well... What's going on with those two?
What's the matter, Yami?
He may be dying, but we need to restrain him.
Oh, good point!
Talk about a gigantic pain in the ass.
You hardcore psycho stalker freak.
Well, we captured the enemy's
top devil-possessed.
Guess it's happily ever aft—
Man, I'm beat.
I can't wait to just dive into my bed.
Ya...
Yami!
I screwed up... I can't move!
Who... is that?!
That's... the Captain of the Golden Dawn!
The thing that connects this
world with the underworld is...
a magic channel called the Tree of Qliphoth.
And to create that Tree of Qliphoth,
we need dark magic and world
tree magic at the arcane stage.
I was concerned about the magic
fluctuation and came to check.
All life is within the palms of our hands.
You said all that, yet lost? How pathetic.
A spatial magic user?
You bastard!
I'm still affected from the
fight with my last opponent.
I'm glad I got him early.
I'd like to take this one, too, but time's up.
You're not going anywhere!
Don't let him leave!
The world will end!
Captain!
Please...
Devil!
You can claim more of my body if you want!
I need to borrow your powers again!
No.
Your body can't move anymore.
Right now, it wouldn't be
able to handle another deal.
It can't...
handle another deal?
That's because...
you're weak.
Finral, please!
Rouge!
If we can just...
touch the captain, even a little!
Captain Yami!
We have achieved our goals.
N-No... Yami...
What are we supposed to do now?
Next time on Black Clover, Page 168:
"Stirrings of the Strongest."
Page 168
Stirrings of the Strongest