The Faraway Future
Devils are born in the underworld.
From the moment they're born, devils have
an established spot in the pecking order
that cannot be overturned.
Since I was born with no magic,
I was definitely at the very bottom.
How do you like that?
I spent every day covered in my own blood.
You're so weak, we can't
even kill time with you.
If only that didn't exist.
All devils want to go to the human world.
But because the gates of the
underworld block their way,
the powerful oppress the weak,
and then the weak oppress those
who are even weaker to pass the time.
That's how shitty that world is.
Go on. Cry and scream like you usually do.
I didn't care about anything anymore.
Not even about dying.
Why, you little... Who do you think you are?!
I thought I'd crash into the gates,
and my body would shatter into pieces.
But because I had no magic,
I slipped right through the gates
and actually ended up in the human world.
Maybe it was because I had
no magic and was helpless...
Or maybe it was because I was so beat-up...
But I had no feelings toward
the humans whatsoever.
However...
Look over there! Those horns... Could he be...
A devil! He's going to curse us!
We need to contact the Magic Knights!
Because I'm a devil, I was chased down
by humans with powerful magic.
My body stopped moving,
and I was ready to accept my death.
At last... this worthless life will be over.
Hey, you're awake? Oh, thank goodness!
My name is Licita. Nice to meet you!
This is my house.
Don't worry. No one else knows you're here.
This is my magic.
As long as something lacks mana, I can
put it into and take it out of containers.
I found you while I was gathering
firewood and carried you back in this.
But talk about a surprise!
The other day, I found a
five-leaf-clover grimoire,
but I didn't think I'd
actually run into a devil!
You're... not scared of me?
Why would I be scared of an injured child?
Besides, you don't have
any magic, and you're so weak.
Still, I'm a devil.
Tsk, tsk, tsk...
I can give you a run for your money
when it comes to being loathed.
My body robs magic and life
from whatever's near me.
Just like that.
So I live out here by myself, away from
the village, so I won't bother anyone.
But wait!
Maybe it's because you're
a devil without any magic,
but it looks like I'm not
stealing away your mana or life.
Don't you think...
this is destiny?!
You should totally be my kid!
Huh?
A devil... adopted as a human's child?
I couldn't wrap my head
around what she was saying.
But...
Come on! This way!
Woo-hoo! Dinner secured!
That human...
Isn't this beautiful?
Yeah...
For someone like me who was
born in a dark, shitty hellhole,
tormented for being a devil with no magic,
and who cursed the fact that I was ever born...
She changed my world.
Just because you're a devil doesn't
automatically make you a bad guy!
Because...
You're not a bad guy!
You saved me from the
suffering of being all alone.
Thanks, Liebe!
I... did... that?
Liebe! What's wrong, Liebe?!
I... am...
Lucifero!
To think there'd be a devil
out in the human world
without making a contract with a human.
I'm glad I decided to kill
some time looking for you.
One of the highest-ranked devils?
My body won't do what I want it to...
What an excellent find!
I'll use him and try to find a way to
manifest my own body in the human wor—
Who the heck are you?! Get out of Liebe's body!
Foolish human.
Even though I cannot use most of my powers,
you're still no match for...
She's... draining my mana?
Insolent human... You must have a death wish!
No...
I won't let go!
I'm never...
letting go again!
I won't...
I won't let you...
take my son!
Inconceivable... To think a human
like her would get in my way...
But I can meddle with a lower devil anywhere.
I shall return.
L-Licita...
I'm sorry... I'm not very bright...
This was the only way I could think
of to protect you from that guy.
I'm going to use my magic to
seal you into this grimoire.
By the time you emerge, I'm sure
you'll have grown big and strong.
Live, Liebe...
My beloved son.
Mom!
Hurry up...
and hand over that body!
This ki... is filled with an
insane amount of rage and hatred.
And...
Sadness.
You must have your reasons, too.
Then I'll accept your feelings and fight...
And I'll win!
You can't be serious!
You're missing an arm and don't
have any magic! Like you could win!
I'm totally serious!
I'm gonna win with these muscles!
The true nature of the
anti-magic that the devil uses
is the power to nullify magic.
Since Asta can't use magic anyway,
this doesn't put him at a disadvantage.
But...
That's great, but I'm not losing!
Captain Yami's katana!
Without my powers, these would
just be rusted hunks of metal!
No matter how physically skilled you are,
you don't have any magic,
so you can't use spatial transfer!
And you can't shatter steel!
You'd stand no chance against a
higher devil's magical powers!
You'd never be able to win!
I was sealed within the five-leaf
grimoire and unable to escape.
They won't get away with this...
I'll kill them.
I'll kill all of them!
I hate them...
I'll kill them!
So I spent all of my time cursing
Lucifero and the other devils, and then...
I gained the power of anti-magic,
the power to nullify magic.
I'm going to use my powers to get revenge!
And that was when the five-leaf
grimoire chose a human.
By some twist of fate,
he was also born with no magic.
It looks like I'll have to
use this human as a host
to come back out into the human world again.
Even if I have to steal
his body, I'm going to...
Every single devil is a piece of shit!
And that's exactly why I'm going
to kill every last one of them!
Even if I have to steal your body,
my hatred is going to win!
I'm finally starting to understand you.
That must be how you really feel!
What are you—
You can't use magic or anti-magic...
So what the hell can you possibly do?!
As long as I concentrated and read your ki,
your movements with those swords
were super easy to read!
You're right. I don't have any magic.
And without you, I can't even use anti-magic.
But I have strong, unbeatable feelings,
along with all the people I've met!
I was taken in at the church at
Hage Village the same day as Yuno,
and I didn't have a lick of mana.
On top of that, Yuno's hot and a genius!
But still, he's my rival, and we promised
to see who would become the Wizard King!
And that's exactly why I was able to keep
getting stronger so I wouldn't lose!
Because I met Captain Yami
at the entrance exam...
Because I met the rest of the Black Bulls...
I am who I am today!
That's not all!
I've met so many people up until now!
I fought so many enemies.
Some of them even became
my friends after we fought,
and some didn't... but I won't forget them!
I won't forget any of them!
All of these encounters
helped make me who I am!
Merit that proves they are the best.
Why are you taking forever
over there, Asta?
I can't win this one without you...
Asta!
This little...
Even after the five-leaf grimoire appeared,
and I was able to use anti-magic...
This whole time!
In order to be like
all of the magical swordsmen
I'd fought alongside and against...
I kept training!
Is that your limit?
I know you can do better than that, Asta!
Yeah!
No matter how hard you train,
your body still has limits.
You still don't stand a chance
against powerful magic.
But...
It looks like all that hard
work wasn't for naught.
You're not just fighting against
some guy who can't use magic.
You're fighting against a guy
who can't use magic...
and has fought against countless
powerful warriors!
There's no way I can lose...
I spent so much time cursing them!
All alone...
All—
I... win!
Well done.
Now the preparations for the
devil-binding ritual are complete.
You will make a contract with this devil that
gives you complete dominance over him,
and you will make him your servant.
Just think, "Obey me."
Then he will follow your every order.
He'll be able to aid you as your familiar.
That is the path you should take
to become the ultimate warrior.
I see. In that case...
Let's be friends!
Huh?
What? Devils don't even
know what friends are?
Friends are like, uh...
Hold on a second. Are you trying to
make an equal contract with that devil?
Yeah!
I said this before we fought, but he's
the reason I was able to fight until now!
But I didn't know anything about him,
even though we'd been together all that time.
I want to know even more about him!
So first, we need to be friends!
What are you talking about?
There's no guarantee that
this devil will listen to you.
There's not a single merit
in a contract like that.
Nah, I mean...
He wasn't fighting seriously to begin with.
He kept saying "kill" and stuff,
but he was definitely holding back.
You can't actually kill anyone, can you?
You're someone who can hate or be
sad for someone else's sake, right?
That's why we can get along!
And that's why I want us to be equals!
This isn't a devil-binding ritual.
It's, uh... Oh! A devil-befriending ritual!
He's a real idiot, Mister Nacht.
He sure is.
And it seems like we want to
take down the same guys!
Let's beat down the bad guys together!
You and me!
Yeah, I can't believe how
unbelievably stupid you are.
I don't know if destiny
actually exists... But he's...
Hey, by the way, what's your name?
Name?
What? You don't have one?
Then maybe I'll just give you one myself!
Liebe!
Starting today, you're Liebe!
He really is...
Licita's kid.
I'm... Liebe.
The heck is this thing?
My right arm is back!
Thanks so much!
The contract is complete.
Unbelievable. That contract
was unprecedented.
I never imagined you'd be such a fool.
However...
You chose what was right.
But that doesn't mean people who
are right will always be rewarded.
So you need to get stronger,
to keep yourself from losing to unjust evil.
Are you prepared to become the
strongest in the next two days?
Yeah!
Loropechika... I'm going to
save you, no matter what.
Okay, everyone! Let's do this!
We're gonna do this.
If the enemy is tremendously strong,
then we'll just surpass our limits!
Because we're the Black Bulls! Right, Yami?
I've been doing everything
I can to defeat Zenon.
But as for the actual results...
Why don't you stop hiding and just come out?
I thought maybe you could use someone
with spatial magic to spar with.
I suppose I should help you
out with your training, huh?
As much as I'd like to handle this on my own,
this is something that affects
all of the Golden Dawn.
You've become stronger, too, haven't you?
So I will gladly accept your offer.
You're still an insolent brat,
but it looks like you're able to
be a bit more straightforward now.
I'm going to save Captain Vangeance.
All right! Just wait, Captain Yami!
No matter how powerful they are,
I'm gonna defeat them...
and protect this world!
In this world where magic is everything,
there was one boy who couldn't use magic.
But he never let that hold him back.
He trained through blood, sweat, and tears,
and became stronger with his childhood rival...
to one day become the Wizard King.