Not yet. I'm not finished...
I'm going to be... the Wizard King.
You? The Wizard King?
I have the ability to find out
just how much magical power
one has with these chains.
And you have no magic whatsoever.
You must've been born that way.
No wonder you couldn't get a grimoire.
To think that you lack
even an ounce of magic
in this world where magic is everything.
What a priceless find!
Huh?
What the hell?
Then no matter how hard I try,
I won't be able to use magic?
To think that someone so pathetic existed.
You won't even be able to find a job,
let alone become the Wizard King!
I'm sure your friend, the great
genius over there, mocks you, too.
Yeah, maybe.
Yuno's so amazing that he
was chosen by the four-leaf.
I'm just...
You can't do a thing in this world.
Just give up on everything.
You were born a loser!
He's right.
No matter how hard I try,
some things just can't be helped.
I'm just going to give...
Hey!
Who are you calling a loser?
Asta, it's true that you won't be
able to become the Wizard King,
no matter what.
You hear that? Even your little friend
is telling you it's impossible.
That's because I'm going
to become the Wizard King!
What?
He's no loser.
He's...
Asta's my rival!
Huh?
Him? Your rival?
This brat who has no
magical power whatsoever?
Not... Not yet.
Sorry you had to see me
looking that pathetic, Yuno.
Just a sec...
I'm gonna kick this guy's butt!
A gri... moire?
I knew it.
There's no way that Asta
wouldn't have been chosen!
Asta's always been that way.
He always does the unthinkable.
He always has before...
and he's doing it now.
I'm gonna become the Wizard King...
and protect you and everyone else.
I'm gonna make everyone even happier!
So we can have even nicer things!
And then, I'm gonna prove to everyone...
Prove?
That even if you're poor... or an orphan...
you can still become the Wizard King.
The Boys' Promise
Grey words can't make anything happen
I know, yeah I know
Wishing to fly freely across the sky
I dreamed it all my life
Step by step I go, though
it's a doubtful world
Don't care how much I fall
Instinct is my guide, I never give up
To faraway future, I burst out running
Go beyond even the unseen fears
The vision I had, so I can be myself
Someday I will write the next page
You are my hope
Like that page from someday
I was able to meet you
I call this a miracle
10 Years Ago
W-Wait!
Yuno! Are you okay?!
Come on, Yuno.
Asta...
Jeez. You're such a crybaby, Yuno.
Well...
It's okay!
I've got your back, Yuno! Okay?
Yeah.
All right. Let's get going.
Everyone's waiting at the top!
It's good, but...
It's hard.
That's our Sister Lily.
You're such an amazing cook!
When I grow up, will you
marry me and cook for me?
It was Father who baked those.
Would you like to marry him?
No! You're the one I wanna marry!
Sister! Marry me! Marry me! Marry me!
Marry me! Marry me! Marry me!
Very good.
Asta, it's not possible.
Sister is, um... a woman of the cloth.
I'm not done yet, Yuno! I won't give up
until I'm an adult, no matter what!
Well, good luck with that.
"And then the world was covered
in deep, deep darkness.
Just when the demon tried
to destroy the world..."
He's not gonna get away with that!
"...a very brave mage appeared.
The brave mage fought the demon
to bring the dawn back to the world.
And finally, he defeated the demon.
The mage's light shone ever so
brightly upon the whole world.
The long, long night had come to an end.
This was the dawn of our world."
Yes!
"And so, the mage was dubbed the
Wizard King and became a legend."
The Wizard King...
"And they all lived happily ever after."
Hey, Sister.
The Wizard King still exists, right?
Yes.
The title of "Wizard King" has been passed
down through many generations.
All along, they've been
protecting us with their magic.
It's because of the Wizard King that
the Clover Kingdom is so peaceful.
That's awesome!
Is the Wizard King really important?
He's the most important after the king.
Okay, I've made up my mind!
About what, Asta?
I'm... gonna be the Wizard King!
Sister?
I'm sorry. I just wasn't expecting that.
What brought this on?
Well, he defeated the demon, right?
That means he's super strong!
And that's so cool!
I wanna be cool, too!
And...
If I become important...
If I become the Wizard King,
I'll be able to make everyone
even happier, right?
You'll be able to wear nice clothes
and eat all the good food you want!
I'm gonna make this crappy
little church huge and amazing!
Crappy?
I'll get you whatever you want, too, Sister!
I'll look forward to it.
Right, Yuno?
Yeah.
The Wizard King...
I'm gonna be the Wizard King!
So, Sister! Marry me—
That's a completely different subject.
Not yet! I won't give up!
No.
Not yet, yet, yet, yet!
December
Why?!
Why is it I still can't use magic?!
Sister! I'll hang up the laundry!
Thanks, Asta.
So marry m—
No.
Mar—
Nope.
No.
Marry me, please...
Don't you start crying, too, Yuno.
Nash... won't stop crying...
Yuno! Leave this to me!
Asta...
I'm gonna be the Wizard King, after all!
Making a baby or two stop
crying is a piece of cake!
H-Hey! There, there! There, there, there!
There, there.
Way to go, Wizard King.
Shut up.
There we go.
Hi there. I was wondering if one
of you would run an errand for me.
Me! Me! Me! Me, me!
I'll go!
Would someone deliver this to the mayor?
Me, me! Me! Me! Me! Me! Me!
It's a very important letter, you see...
Yuno, could you do it?
Huh? Me?
Well, it's a very important letter,
and I'm hesitant to leave it in Asta's
hands, so I'm counting on you.
I have to go see the mayor
in the next village over.
I have to ask him to spare us some
food to make it through the winter.
As it stands now, we just
don't have enough tatoes.
Yuno, I'll go!
No. Father asked me to go.
I-I'll go.
Will you be okay by yourself?
I'll be fine.
I'm heading out!
Come on, Asta. Chop some wood.
You can't use magic, so at
least do some manual labor.
Shut up! Did you even dig up the
tatoes you were supposed to?
I dug up the ones for
today a long time ago.
Huh?!
It looks like it's going
to get chilly tonight.
That's enough! Get out of my shop!
The hell are you doing?!
If you want to drink any more,
you gotta bring some cash.
You ain't getting any for free!
I don't want your stupid
booze anyway, you jerk!
Damn it...
Whoa...
Ow...
The snow's getting pretty thick.
I'll have to be careful not to slip.
Oh, thank you. Please tell
Father that I received it.
I will. P-Please excuse me.
It's late, so be careful getting home!
Thank you very much!
I'm... sorry.
Yuno's taking an awfully long time.
I'm hungry.
And Father isn't back yet, either.
Let's just eat without them.
No! That's not fair to Yuno!
Boo.
My pendant... That's mine...
I'm just gonna exchange it for some cash.
Give it back...
You miserable little brat. Where do you
get off having something this extravagant?
Give it... back...
Give it back...
That's mine...
What the heck is that?
What do you expect to do
to me with magic like that?
You want to fight me...
and die?
Yuno!
Who the hell are you, brat?
That's Yuno's!
Give it back!
Don't touch me with your filthy hands!
You... stupid little brat!
Not yet!
Cut it out!
I'm not done yet!
Damn it!
Damn little brat just won't give up.
What the hell's his problem?
Asta!
I'm sorry. I... I...
Don't worry about it.
I told you, I've got your back.
Asta...
Asta's always done the unthinkable.
Wh-What is that grimoire?
That sword!
Just who are you?!
You little wretch with no magical powers!
He... nullified my magic?
Even without magical powers...
I'm going to become the Wizard King!
Not giving up...
is my magic!
I built up my muscles
since I couldn't use any magic.
Looks like they came in handy after all.
Asta...
Asta, are you okay?
I'm so sorry. It's all
my fault... I'm sorry...
This is nothin'!
I'm gonna become the Wizard King.
I'm gonna become the Wizard King...
and protect you and everyone else.
I'm gonna make everyone even happier!
So we can have even nicer things!
And then, I'm gonna prove to everyone...
Prove?
That even if you're poor... or an orphan...
you can still become the Wizard King.
We can?
Yeah.
Can we really?
Anyone can... if they work hard enough!
Anyone?
Me, or even you, Yuno!
I'll... never cry again.
Maybe I... no...
Yuno?
I will...
I'll become the Wizard King, too!
I'll get stronger, and protect
you and everyone else!
I'm gonna make everyone happier!
So we can have nicer things!
Yuno! Look, look! I got my own grimoire!
It's insanely shabby, but I'm gonna take
good care of it for the rest of my life!
There, there, there, there, there.
There, there, there, there.
I guess...
you saved me again.
I'll repay you for this someday.
Asta...
Do you remember our promise?
So you're gonna become the Wizard King, too?
That means...
Yuno, you're...
Asta, you're...
...my rival!
You mean you remember it?
I thought you were just making fun of me.
I have no interest in being
too friendly with my rival.
But you're the one who gave me hope.
Even if you're poor, an orphan...
or even us...
We can become greater than anyone
else in this world. And to prove that...
To make Sister and everyone else happy...
Let's see who can become the Wizard King!
No one can escape from here
Once again in the small closed off classroom
The star of the class was shining yet again
They shine so bright that I close my eyes
I've thought many times
That the revolution was within my hands
Isn't it strange? If you want
to laugh, go ahead and laugh
The rest of us who were left
behind wanted to become something
We repeat the same morning over and over
You're the only one who
can choose your tomorrow
Let's go beyond our current selves
Even though I can't use magic,
I'm going to join the Magic Knights!
So that I can become the Wizard King!
Black Clover, Page 3: "To the Royal
Capital of the Clover Kingdom!"
Page 3
To the Royal Capital of the Clover Kingdom!
Not giving up is my magic!