It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
The Clover Kingdom's royal capital
suddenly fell under attack.
Flames rose in five spots
throughout the capital,
and the Magic Knights deployed to each
location to help the panicked citizens.
They battled an unknown enemy.
Come at me yourself!
Don't get cocky, you little brat!
Come forth, Alfred.
Number Two, Alfred.
Go, Alfred!
I would always close my eyes
And cower at reality
I can't stand the idea
Of just making excuses to give up
Stand right there
I don't want to be near you
Any minute now
Just wait right there
(The decisive battle is still a long way off)
Black and blue
I'll give up on giving up
And get the world on my side
I'm looking for the reason I'm alive
Every time somewhere under this sky
Break through the tearful nights
And head where the light shines
I want to keep my promise
I'll deliver it to you
shape of love
The Crimson Lion King
Central District
Something's wrong.
Their numbers are great,
but they're far too weak.
What does the enemy want?
Where is their main force?
What are they after?
The king?
Where is the Wizard King?
During an emergency like this,
he should be the first to rush to the side of
King of the Clover Kingdom
Augustus Kira Clover XIII
Augustus Kira Clover XIII,
King of the Clover Kingdom.
His first priority should be
to protect me. That is...
the most important duty of
the most powerful mage in
the kingdom,the Wizard King!
You are absolutely right, Your Majesty.
Rest assured, we, the advisors of
the Wizard King, will protect you.
Curse that Julius.
He's gotten full of himself because his
authority equals mine when we're at war,
hasn't he?
Honestly...
I'm the only leader of the Clover Kingdom!
Castle Town Kikka
Chef! What are you doing?
The royal capital is under attack!
We need to take shelter!
You idiots! Like a true chef could
leave in the middle of cooking!
I will deliver the best dishes,
no matter the situation!
That's what it means to be the best!
Uh, but all the Magic Knights have
been deployed, so there's no one here!
They left for battle.
What?! How could they have left
without eating my main dish?!
Well, our kingdom is in trouble!
Let's hurry and escape!
La!
Wh-Who's this little shrimp?
This main dish you mentioned...
Please let me eat it!
A Magic Knight's robe...
Which means she must be one
of the big shots that got
invited to the decoration ceremony.
And...
Her glaring eyes are practically on fire.
Her glaring drool is practically on fire.
She's...
someone special!
All right, you've got it!
Just wait!
I'll cook you up the best main dish ever!
What?!
Yay! Woohoo!
Let's just run!
Cooking...
is more important than my life!
Yay!
North District
Too bad, you stupid brat!
Your special anti-magic blade doesn't
mean anything if it can't hit its target!
Mister...
This is your chance!
Run!
O-Okay.
Please help him.
I know. Don't worry, he's...
a dear friend of mine!
Okay!
Come down here!
Are you stupid?
Who the heck would come down
just because someone told them to?
Back at the dungeon...
Yeah, leave it to me.
I'll throw enough at him from the both of us!
I don't have any magic,
but I've got...
my friends!
My magical powers combined with Asta's sword.
If only I could help him now like I did then,
even if the enemy is in the air...
Black Bulls girl!
I, Leopold Vermillion, shall assist you.
I shall not let him harm my rival any longer!
Right.
You two can deal with him!
Muddy Water Magic...
Mine's a poor match for that.
Asta...
His wound from that attack earlier...
You told me earlier, didn't you?
To come at you myself?
You fool!
I'm not going to fight. I'm going to control
my corpses and enjoy the show!
I'm going to win just by watching.
That's how I fight!
Unlike a meathead like you,
I actually know how to use my brain.
Moron!
Damn it...
That stupid jerk doesn't even
think of people as people...
I don't wanna lose to him!
What's that look for?
Guts alone won't gonna get you
out of this, you stupid brat!
Alfred!
Asta!
Damn it! What should I...
Kill him!
M-My Alfred... turned into
charcoal in an instant...
He's...
Damn it... I couldn't defeat him on my own.
I apologize for horning in on your fight.
But I thought it would be a shame
to let a man like you die here.
Forgive me.
You fought well for a peasant
with no magical powers.
You're funny, kid.
Join my squad.
I hate to admit this, but it looks like
Yami's foresight was better than mine.
Asta, wasn't it?
You mentioned that you were going to
become the Wizard King, didn't you?
Huh?! Become the Wizard King?!
There's no way a stupid brat like you who's
way weaker than me could become that!
Then...
I guess you're my rival, too.
So you're gonna fight me?
Finally, someone worth fighting...
Captain of the Crimson Lion Kings,
Fuegoleon Vermillion!
Asta,
leave the rest to me!
Asta!
Fuegoleon!
A captain of a Magic Knights squad...
I guess you're my rival, too.
Did he just say...
This is no time for me to be a wuss!
I can still...
do this!
No, you can't.
My head, my face, and my stomach hurt!
I'm sure they do.
As a warrior, you need to constantly
be aware of your condition,
and determine if you're
able to fight or not.
You are definitely not
in that state right now.
Your exuberance may be your greatest
weapon, but keep a cool head, too.
If you truly wish to become
the Wizard King, that is.
Now, let's hear it.
What are you after?
Your actions are too scattered
for an invasion and
too organized for indiscriminate terrorism.
Who are you?
Who am I? You don't recognize me?
I guess I'm the only one
enjoying this reunion.
What?
Six years ago, I was the top choice
for a Magic Knights squad.
What? You're a former Magic Knight?
I guess you wouldn't remember.
I wasn't important enough for
you people to bother with.
He's a commoner, but he has
tremendous magical powers.
All who wish to offer,
please raise your hand.
I see... You're from back then.
What's your name?
It's Rades!
That's right.
I believe you joined the Purple Orcas.
They expelled me!
Expelled?
Rades, with all of your talent... Why?
They said that my magic was
dangerous and forbidden,
and kicked me out of the
squad and the kingdom both!
Because I was a commoner,
no one stood up for me. No one!
Even though my powers were
better than everyone else's!
Greater than the nobles'...
greater than anyone's!
I thought magic meant
everything in this kingdom!
And that's why!
I'm getting my revenge on the
Magic Knights and this country!
With my powers! That's what I'm after!
Though we do have another goal.
For such a childish reason...
You can't be serious, you fool!
Childish?
Reasons are always simple!
Leo!
Fuegoleon?
Do you need help?
Definitely not!
Not at all!
Hey...
Very good!
Wha—
If you understand, take care
of things quickly!
Yes, sir!
Wh-Whoa, those brothers are Spartan for sure!
Way to ask the impossible!
Our attributes are lousy against each other.
Not like I'm going to let you help him, but...
Sorry, but I can't control
the intensity of the flames.
Flame Creation Magic: Leo Rugiens!
A magical barrier...
Number One, Carl!
When he was alive, he was
an expert at defense magic!
So I added my curse magic
and made him even tougher!
He's bringing out one of those things again!
Asta.
Y-Yes, sir!
Do you remember what I said a moment ago?
Watch carefully.
Why are you so calm?!
Defense isn't the only thing he can do!
Flame Creation Magic: Ignis Columna.
Trying to match Carl's barrier spells, huh?
Well?!
What do you think about this invincible
barrier and super barrage?
Indeed, there is nothing I can do right now.
Is that all you've got,
Captain of the Crimson Lion Kings?
Flame Magic: Sol Linea.
In the instant you attack,
for just a moment, the mana of
the barrier thins in places.
That's what I aimed for.
I deal with difficult magic every day.
Listen well, all of you!
As long as you are Magic Knights,
you will find yourselves constantly pitted
against powerful enemies and magic!
But when that happens,
if you gauge the ability calmly
and maintain a bold fighting spirit,
you will never lose!
Is that clear?!
Yes, sir!
He instantly saw his opponent's weaknesses,
and even psyched up his allies.
So that's a Magic Knights Captain.
H-He's awesome!
I-Impossible! My Number One
was defeated so easily...
D-Damn it! Damn it!
Rades, wasn't it?
Even if you possess extraordinary abilities
and polish them to their fullest,
without a righteous spirit,
your deeds are nothing but violence!
No one will acknowledge something like that.
I have a report, Your Majesty.
Most of the attackers have
been dealt with, it seems.
Took them long enough.
The Magic Knights need to work harder.
And? Where's the Wizard King?
Why hasn't he come to my side?
He's on an important mission.
Honestly... There's no way it
could be more important than me.
West District
What were those things, anyway?
Regardless, they're apparently
no match for us.
East District
I can't believe you fools
tried to attack my sis!
Only the women of the Blue Rose
Knights are allowed to touch her!
Sol, don't say things
people will misinterpret.
The only ones who can touch
Sis's soft, velvety skin are...
That's not what I meant.
Central District
What? Finished already?
But I wasn't done playing.
Something is off.
Northwest District
I guess that's most of them.
Th-They were so gross.
I need to get stronger so things like
this don't trouble me so much.
Th-They're so strong!
Hooray for the Magic Knights!
Hooray! Hooray!
It's too early for you to
be cheering just yet.
I think everything's about ready.
Now for some lively sow's mana...
How exciting!
My dry emotions gaze at the me from that day
And push me forward
(I can't find a place to go)
Even the faintest light can
still break through the darkness
And change the flow of time
(I will keep believing in you)
In this ever-vivid place
(Break free yourself)
In order to grasp my endless dream
If there is a path that I should choose
(Do you wanna try? Do you wanna try?)
Wherever it may lead us
Until my life comes to an end
I will accept any pain that comes my way
(We can try again, we can try again)
Even if we can't see tomorrow
Holding onto feelings too intense to voice
I'll keep screaming them in my heart
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Palace Three-Second Cooking
Palace Three-Second Cooking.
The time where I, the royal
head chef of Clover Kingdom,
introduce a three-second dish
that anyone can make.
Today, I'd like to make some
curry in three seconds.
I'm going to be using simple curry
roux procured at the market.
Next, you'll need carrots, onions, potatoes,
some mushrooms, and maybe some tomatoes.
If you try adding secret ingredients
like chocolate or coffee,
you can make an even more fragrant curry.
Now, then... You take
those ingredients, and...
Immediately chop them up using
your magic, and simmer them!
Make sure you use plenty of love and passion!
And it's finished. Wasn't that easy?
Time to eat!
So good!
And that concludes this episode of Palace
Three-Second Cooking, dishes anyone can make!
See you next time!
But that's impossible!
Magic Knights, hurry up and
take care of the attackers.
Black Clover, Page 24: "Blackout."
Page 24
Blackout
Eating and napping is the job of
the King of Clover Kingdom,
Augustus Kira Clover XIII.