It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
You're right there!
I'm impressed you found me.
What are you, an animal?
But it appears that it's over now.
Over?
What's over?
We've completed our mission.
We're leaving before the other
Magic Knights come back, Rades.
Asta, wasn't it?
I'll eventually kill you and make
you into one of my toys.
Look forward to that, you little brat!
Not giving up is my magic!
And my sword can...
Cut through magic!
What?!
Ow! What the hell are
you doing, you little shit?!
Not good...
You have the nerve to say that
after hurting all those people?!
This...
is pain!
This is what you did to innocent people
as you laughed about it!
This isn't good... We can't
afford to lose Rades, too.
Pathetic.
We received orders from Master
to come here, and look at you...
You're struggling against
this lot. How pathetic.
There are five new enemies!
I was only scratched... but thanks to
that curse, the bleeding won't stop.
It looks like the tables have turned!
I would always close my eyes
And cower at reality
I can't stand the idea
Of just making excuses to give up
Stand right there
I don't want to be near you
Any minute now
Just wait right there
(The decisive battle is still a long way off)
Black and blue
I'll give up on giving up
And get the world on my side
I'm looking for the reason I'm alive
Every time somewhere under this sky
Break through the tearful nights
And head where the light shines
I want to keep my promise
I'll deliver it to you
shape of love
Wounded Beasts
Things have quieted down.
Has the enemy been taken care of?
Yum, yum, can't move.
Can't move, can't move...
My meal-saving prince...
I hope the Magic Knights are okay.
Asta!
You...
Now I can keep fighting!
Please watch me, sir!
This brat... He struck himself with his
own swords to get rid of the curse?
Unbelievable... He's so stupid!
Wow, he's fun. Can I dissect him later?
Quiet.
Boo. You're such a spoilsport.
All I've ever faced since
I was born... was adversity.
No matter how many come at me,
no matter what happens,
I'll blast them all away!
All right! Come at me!
It seems he's lost his mind
in the face of our numbers.
Whatever. He's about to die anyway.
There's no use in fighting.
You need to learn when to give up.
Oh, so that's him.
So this is the anti-magic
brat our master spoke of.
Your exuberance may be your greatest
weapon, but keep a cool head, too.
If you truly wish to become
the Wizard King, that is.
Keep a cool head... Right, sir?
I'll stay calm... while I kick their butts!
This little...
Flame Magic: Exploding Flames!
Wow!
You think I'm going to let you people
throw your weight around
after what you did to my brother?!
Let me join you, my rival!
Sure! Go right ahead!
They say beasts are more formidable
when they're wounded. These two...
are dangerous.
What the hell are you doing?!
Hurry up and kill them!
We know.
They aren't our targets...
But we'll kill them now!
Noelle!
Don't think that you can
kill my friends so easily!
Wow...
That's quite the defensive spell.
Judging from your appearance, you must
be a member of the royal Silva family.
In that case, I'll use my grimoire
against you. I wouldn't want to be rude.
Tree Creation Magic: Magic-Draining Roots!
Asta!
I know.
What are you planning to do?
No... They swallowed my torrent.
Your fighting instincts are admirable.
Wind Creation Magic: Tornado Needles!
He's...
He's too fast.
Asta! Leopold!
Now, let's end this.
N-No way...
No!
Ooh, what's this magic? I've never
seen anything like this before!
E-Everyone...
The Magic Knights...
How dare you send us that far away?
Impossible... They managed to return
here from that distance so quickly?
We really didn't want to, but we
all worked together to get back.
I suppose you could call it
super compound magic.
Joining forces once in a while isn't so bad.
Well, I guess men aren't completely useless.
I'll acknowledge their abilities.
Nothing more.
I'm never working with them again.
We really don't play well with others.
But our nine Magic Knights squads exist
solely to protect the peace
of the Clover Kingdom!
Noelle!
Mimosa, please take care
of Captain Fuegoleon.
No... How could something like this happen
to someone like Captain Fuegoleon?
Not to mention Leopold and Asta...
Hey, wake up!
You're alive!
They put Captain Fuegoleon
and the others in such a state.
Who...
It'll cost us if we keep fighting. Let's retreat.
Don't be in such a hurry.
Mercury Magic: Rain of Silver!
Gel Magic: Sticky Salamander!
My magic will just pierce
through magic like that.
And then...
Dark Magic Item: Special
Properties Plus Alpha... absorbed!
They managed to deflect the captain's
magic as if it were nothing!
What... is that magic item?
No—
Mine!
What do you plan to do with him?
It's a secret!
Remember this, Magic Knights.
We are the Eye of the Midnight Sun...
The ones who will destroy the Clover Kingdom.
Asta!
Gel Magic: Sticky Salamander!
My magic will just pierce
through magic like that.
And then...
Dark Magic Item: Special
Properties Plus Alpha... absorbed!
They managed to deflect the captain's
magic as if it were nothing!
What... is that magic item?
No—
Mine!
What do you plan on doing with him?
It's a secret!
Remember this, Magic Knights.
We are the Eye of the Midnight Sun...
The ones who will destroy the Clover Kingdom.
Asta!
They took... Asta.
We have to save him!
Noelle, we can't.
But—
It's unfortunate, but we have
no way of tracking them.
Yes, but—
No.
Right now, strengthening the royal
capital's defenses takes priority.
There's no guarantee that
those were the only enemies.
We don't have any time or magic
to spare on someone like him.
How are Fuegoleon and Leopold doing?
The best I can do with
my magic is first aid!
He needs to be taken to the medical ward
for more advanced healing magic, or he'll...
Some captain he is. How pathetic.
The Vermillions sure aren't what they used
to be. Makes me embarrassed to be a royal.
Solid, how could you say that?
We are Magic Knights.
Our existence is pointless unless we win.
Nozel...
That's right! This is going to ruin the
reputation of the Crimson Lion Kings...
But Solid...
As we were not present at the fight,
we are even less than he is.
Strengthen the defenses so that
there won't be further damages.
Right.
They've spread around magic that
blocks transmission spells,
and the chain of command is in chaos.
Because of that, reinforcements from outside
the Noble Realm couldn't arrive.
We can't let our guard down yet.
Sol, we're going to reinforce the area.
Don't let your guard down.
You got it, Sis!
Call me "Captain."
I know, Captain Sis!
My goodness. Looks like we'll have to
wait on dessert a little while longer.
Klaus, go to headquarters
and get reinforcements.
Yes, sir.
Asta...
Rades, we ended up with a huge headache
because you stepped out of line.
Don't get carried away just because
the master has taken a liking to you.
How dare you say, "I want
to fight a captain alone.
I want to lay waste to the capital"?
You conceited fool!
Shut up.
If you'd just done what you were told, we
wouldn't have to go through all this trouble.
My toys were the victims in all of this!
This doesn't concern any of you!
I heard that Catherine was captured, though.
Who the hell cares about that old hag?
Hag...
We got what we went there for, so who cares?
By the way, Sally...
We won't be able to take that brat with us.
Kill him.
What? No way!
He uses anti-magic!
This is on a different level than a
mere magic-weakening effect!
I'm going to use him in my research!
Let me take him! Please? Please?
Where am I...? What is this?
It feels sorta nice.
Only those acknowledged by
the master can go there.
Don't cause any more unnecessary trouble.
Kill him before our master arrives.
What?
Aw...
I know! Let me kill him!
I'll make him into my toy!
Crap, I've...
Shut up, Rades.
What?!
I've been captured by the enemy?
Hey, you're awake.
A-A girl?
You should help me convince them!
I want to study everything about you and
your grimoire, and do some experiments,
and then dissect you in the end!
You want every last cell of yours
to help with my research, right?
She's really bad news!
Right? Right? Right?
And this is a super bad situation!
I can't move! I can't run!
Please? I'll ask properly, so please?
Don't blame me for whatever happens.
Give him to me!
Nope!
Hi there.
I've been waiting for you.
Wha—
Ooh!
H-He's...
The Wizard King, Julius Novachrono?!
What's he doing here?
How was the royal capital?
Kill him!
I-Impossible!
I killed them.
It would've been too difficult
with your numbers...
Restraining all of you, I mean.
Wait, what?
You guys attacked the royal capital, right?
You didn't actually kill people without
being ready to die yourselves, did you?
Such power...
This is the Wizard King?
Crap... I don't have any magic left...
That being said, you all seem pretty skilled.
You'll probably give me some trouble.
How about it? I'll let one of you
survive, so why not surrender?
It'll be first come, first served.
What do you think?
Don't underestimate us!
Wha... How is he moving like
that?! I can't keep up!
I guess I don't have a choice.
I might be able to handle these numbers.
Time Binding Magic: Chrono Stasis.
What... is this?
I can't move...
...at all.
I guess I was able to restrain all of you.
Were you more worn out than I thought?
See how it feels to live
in one unending moment.
Ow...
Hey there, Asta.
We seem to be connected by fate somehow.
R-Right...
He managed to take care of all of
them despite how strong they were.
This is the Wizard King's power?
This is...
You want to become the
Wizard King someday, right?
In that case, watch carefully
and don't look away.
This is only a small fraction
of what you'll have to surpass.
He's my goal! The strongest guy there is!
He's the strongest mage in the
kingdom that I need to surpass!
Can you stand?
I can't stop shaking after witnessing
the Wizard King's power firsthand!
You idiot!
Stop shaking! Stop!
You can't lose here!
I guess you didn't need my help.
All of you had some interesting
magic. I was surprised.
Now, then... I have some
questions for you all.
What are these jewels and this stone slab?
I've never seen these characters
or patterns before.
What are you trying to accomplish with this?
Well, it's not like you can answer
that while you're in that spell.
I guess we can take our time back at
the Clover Kingdom to talk about this.
Something's coming?
That's blinding!
What is this light?!
My dry emotions gaze at the me from that day
And push me forward
(I can't find a place to go)
Even the faintest light can
still break through the darkness
And change the flow of time
(I will keep believing in you)
In this ever-vivid place
(Break free yourself)
In order to grasp my endless dream
If there is a path that I should choose
(Do you wanna try? Do you wanna try?)
Wherever it may lead us
Until my life comes to an end
I will accept any pain that comes my way
(We can try again, we can try again)
Even if we can't see tomorrow
Holding onto feelings too intense to voice
I'll keep screaming them in my heart
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Cringing at Salamander Bowls
Cringing at Salamander Bowls!
Gel Magic: Sticky Salamander!
Mander!
How adorable!
That's no big deal! Nero's much cuter.
If you put him in a bowl, he's delicious.
Ma?!
She's dangerous!
Looks nummy!
They're all dangerous!
Wow! The Wizard King himself showed up!
I wanna research him. I wonder
if he'd become my sample.
Black Clover, Page 27: "Light."
Page 27
Light
If you want to be researched,
come see me, Sally!