It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
Clover Kingdom Royal Capital
Time has passed, and the title
of the Wizard King has been
passed down through generations.
The Wizard King commands the Magic Knights,
and they protect the kingdom together.
The Magic Knights are comprised
of nine squads of mages
that specialize in combat, all under
the command of the Wizard King.
This band of heroes protects
the kingdom with their lives.
To become the Wizard King or a Magic Knight
is the aspiration of all in the Clover Kingdom.
To the Royal Capital of the Clover Kingdom!
Grey words can't make anything happen
I know, yeah I know
Wishing to fly freely across the sky
I dreamed it all my life
Step by step I go, though
it's a doubtful world
Don't care how much I fall
Instinct is my guide, I never give up
To faraway future, I burst out running
Go beyond even the unseen fears
The vision I had, so I can be myself
Someday I will write the next page
You are my hope
Like that page from someday
I was able to meet you
I call this a miracle
Nine hundred and ninety-five...
Nine hundred and ninety-six...
Nine hundred and ninety-seven...
Nine hundred and ninety-eight...
Nine hundred and ninety-nine...
One thousand!
Now to down some moguro leaf juice!
Gross!
One more gulp!
You want some, too?
What the heck?
I got my grimoire.
I'm gonna keep climbing up,
even if I don't have any magical powers!
All right! I'm not done yet!
Not even close!
One thousand and one!
I'm sure Yuno's been training, too! I can't lose!
One thousand and two!
Asta was training for the
Magic Knights Entrance Exam,
which was to be held in the royal capital
of the Clover Kingdom in six months.
So was Yuno.
I should wrap up for today.
No, just a little bit more.
I'm sure he's also...
One thousand and one!
One thousand and two!
Each one's goal was to one day
become the Wizard King.
One thousand, five hundred and... three!
Well, I can understand Yuno...
But are you really considering allowing
Asta to take the exam, too?
Well, he's saying he wants to do it.
And the ones I was counting on...
W-We can't do it...
We can't become Magic Knights!
If someone who was kicked out of
the Magic Knights was that strong...
There's no way!
We're sorry!
...decided against taking the exam.
Again, I believe Yuno will be fine,
but I don't think Asta's up for it.
Well, he's saying he wants to do it.
Again, I believe Yuno will be fine,
but it'll be pointless for Asta to take them.
Well, he's saying he wants to do it.
Actually, the idea of Asta going to the royal
capital just makes you feel lonely, doesn't it?
Aw, Father!
Th-That's not...
I just believe that if he's
going to fail anyway,
he's better off not taking
it in the first place.
A-And you know... The little
ones will miss him, too.
Not me! But they'll have one
less person to play with!
Why are you looking at me like that?
Not you, too, Tower Master!
Well, I'll feel a little lonely with
both Yuno and Asta gone, Father.
Well, of course, I raised them, and I've lived
with them ever since they were babies.
I'd be lying if I said I wasn't
a bit sad to see them go.
If possible, I'd like for them
to stay at the church.
But I also want to let them
do what they want to do.
Indeed.
Besides, you know... Yuno will be fine,
and Asta might fail the exam
and come right back anyway.
Y-You're right. Right!
Yuno will be fine, but the
other one will come right back.
Um... The book that Asta obtained...
Is it truly a grimoire?
Asta can't use magic. How was
he able to obtain a grimoire?
I'm not sure.
But that's...
Yes?
No...
Look! Look!
My very own grimoire!
I don't even know how,
but I was able to get one!
The five-leaf clover... It couldn't be.
Training's not over until
I'm back at the church!
Eat my dust!
Goal!
Yuno! Asta!
Welcome back.
Wh-Who got here faster?
Hmm... Yuno was just a tiny bit faster.
Seriously?! Were you even looking?!
Then I'll race you into the church!
I win.
Yuno can be pretty childish sometimes.
Yeah, I mean, getting so worked
up over Asta, of all people?
Not to mention, Yuno...
How many years will this last us?
I'm gonna become the Wizard King.
Yuno?
Did you come to watch me train?
Nash?
What's up?
Nothing. I was just bored.
I just came by to make fun of the
idiot doing something idiotic.
Whaddya mean, idiotic?!
Well, it is!
You can't even use magic, and you're going
to take the Magic Knights Entrance Exam?
Of course you're going to fail!
That's not decided yet!
Just look!
I even got a grimoire!
I'm gonna get into the Magic Knights!
And then, one day, I'll become the Wizard Ki—
That's never gonna happen!
Orphans like us, who are poor...
aren't allowed to dream like that.
Nash...
You can't give up right from the get-go!
Possibilities exist in everyone!
Shut up! They do not!
No, they do! I'm going to
keep chasing my dream!
It doesn't matter if you're
poor or an orphan.
Anyone in this world can become amazing.
They can do anything.
They can make their dreams come true.
They can make everyone happy!
And I'll prove that to you!
Prove?
I'm going to join the Magic Knights
and become the Wizard King!
Tomorrow's the day Asta and Yuno
set out for the royal capital.
We have to send them off with a bang!
Father went to all the surrounding
villages asking for tatoes.
Father!
What's that look for?
This isn't just for you!
Actually, it's mostly for Yuno.
Father!
Well, you know... Yuno might make it
into the Magic Knights, but you're...
Father!
Asta, there's no need to be embarrassed,
even if you fail the exam.
Huh?
No one believes you're going to pass, anyway.
Are you trying to encourage
me or make fun of me?!
You can come back at any time.
Your home is this church.
No matter how crappy or poor
it may be, it's your home.
That's right, Asta.
I'll be lonely without Asta here.
Yuno, too.
We're all family.
Y-You should say that to Yuno, too.
Tell him he can come back
whenever he wants.
Yuno will be fine.
What do you mean?! Besides, I'll be fine, too!
I'm gonna become the Wizard King!
And then... I'm gonna come back for Sister!
So when that happens, marry m—
All right, let's eat.
We have stewed tatoes,
tato tempura, grilled tatoes,
fried tatoes, stir-fried
tatoes, steamed tatoes,
Hage-style boiled tatoes, tato juice,
and even special tato pudding!
Yay! Let's eat!
So flaky and delicious!
Yummy!
Hey, that's mine!
Don't eat it all yourself, Asta!
So good!
Take care.
You better write us, Yuno.
Sure.
Good luck!
Come back soon!
He'll be back soon... Asta, that is.
Nash!
But you know...
If, just if, and it's a very huge if...
If you get into the Magic Knights...
Yeah?
I'll believe in possibilities.
I'll believe I can become anything.
And then one day, I'll get into
the Magic Knights, too.
No, never mind.
I'll be waiting for you.
Well, I'll be off.
Hey, wait, Yuno!
Answer me, you handsome jerk!
Just because we're rivals doesn't
mean we can't get along!
Hey!
Well, bye, guys!
Have a safe trip!
See ya.
Yuno and Asta... You've both grown so much.
Asta's always been full of energy.
This is Sister Lily. She'll be
working here starting today.
All of you, be kind to her.
Wow... Sister Lily.
Yes?
Please marry me!
I'm sorry! I didn't mean to!
Lily...
He seems happy.
It might be because of Asta...
But Yuno's become so strong.
Asta...
He's so beaten up.
It's all my fault.
He was protecting me.
What?
Yuno, you sound so...
Asta, stay with us!
Sister Lily...
Asta...
Please marry me.
Thank goodness.
Do your best, you two.
It is summer. Asta and Yuno start their
journey to the royal capital in order to take
the Magic Knights Entrance Exam.
The royal capital is a long,
long way from Hage Village.
The royal capital, huh... I wonder what it's like.
I wonder if we'll get
to meet the Wizard King!
First, we need to pass the
Magic Knights entrance exam.
Then we'll talk.
I'm so excited!
Excited? Aren't you scared?
Huh? Why would I be?
You never change.
Come on, let's hurry!
The royal capital's super far away!
Hey.
I've gotta hurry up and
become the Wizard King!
Just because you get there quickly
doesn't mean you'll become the
Wizard King any quicker.
I'm gonna become the Wizard King, and...
My, Asta, you look so impressive.
Sister... no, my Lily.
I came for you, just as I promised.
I've become the Wizard King. Now, get on.
Okay!
Hold on tight!
It could happen!
Can you even ride a broom when
you don't have any magic?
I-I'll make it work!
Will you?
I will! I got my grimoire!
I can do anything as long as I don't give up!
Come on, hurry up!
I'm gonna leave you behind, Yuno!
Let's train all the way to the royal capital!
You can't be serious.
Can't keep up, can you, Yuno?
Not done yet... Not yet!
Stop. We've got a long way to go.
Not yet! I'm not done yet!
Hot! Hot, hot, hot!
I wish everyone back at the
church could eat this, too.
Yeah.
This way!
No, it's this way.
H-Hey, wait!
Stay out of my way!
I just gave you a hand.
No one asked you to!
All right!
My precious moguro leaf juice!
What's the matter, Yuno?
Whoa, it's huge!
So that's the royal capital.
That's where the Wizard King is.
All right! I'm gonna do this!
I'll be right there! Just you wait!
I'm gonna become the Wizard King!
After a long and perilous journey,
Asta and Yuno arrive at the royal
capital of the Clover Kingdom.
The Magic Knights Entrance Exam awaits.
They will now have to compete with many
powerful opponents and pass the exam!
No one can escape from here
Once again in the small closed off classroom
The star of the class was shining yet again
They shine so bright that I close my eyes
I've thought many times
That the revolution was within my hands
Isn't it strange? If you want
to laugh, go ahead and laugh
The rest of us who were left
behind wanted to become something
We repeat the same morning over and over
You're the only one who
can choose your tomorrow
Let's go beyond our current selves
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
The Mystery of the Grimoire
The Mystery of the Grimoire!
Wait, what? We're small now?
But man... Our grimoires
are totally different.
He ignored me?
A grimoire's size and thickness are
determined by its owner's style.
All right! Let's compare grimoires!
No.
That thing's
filthy
No fair!
You scared you're gonna lose?
Not a chance.
You're getting a big head just because
you're a little handsome, aren't you?
Not a chance.
This is it, Yuno! The Magic Knights
we admire so much are here!
Our path to making our dream of becoming
the Wizard King come true starts here!
Black Clover, Page 4:
"The Magic Knights Entrance Exam!"
Page 4
The Magic Knights Entrance Exam
Not giving up is my magic!