It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
These children have had their
magic sucked out of them.
If left like this, they may never
be able to use magic again.
How could you do something so cruel?
I guess I'll just have to take
care of this peon myself.
I won't...
forgive you!
Three-Leaf Sprouts
Black Bulls' Base
Bah... ha!
Jeez... The Black Bulls are supposed
to be the closest to Nean.
So why aren't they responding?
Bah-ha?
But the Black Bulls are a
group of misfits, aren't they?
Bah-ha...
G-Good evening...
I'm here to ask for backup.
Bah... ha?
Right. I should go.
I-I'm not scared or anything,
but what else can I do if no one's here?
Actually, it looks like I scared
off the Black Bulls, bah-ha!
Instead,
I guess I'll just go ask at the garden of
beautiful women, the Blue Rose Knights.
So why am I wasting any more time... here?
The moon's beautiful, isn't it?
Bah-ha!
I'm Gordon,
I'm Gordon, but you can call me Don.
Wait...
Stop! I'm no one suspicious!
You're Sekke Bronzazza from
You're Sekke Bronzazza from the Green Praying Mantises, right?
You're Sekke Bronzazza from the Green Praying Mantises, right? Let's be friends.
Y-Yikes...
I haven't seen you since the Magic Knights' Entrance Exam...
That look... He's going to kill me!
Would you like to join me for tea?
S-Stop! Stay back!
Bah-ha...
Bah-ha!
Another freak just showed up!
Shut up!
Damn it. And I was sleeping so well...
"Bah-ha, bah-ha, ha-bah, ha-bah..."
Do you have any idea what time it is?
The Black Bulls' captain?
Huh?
Bah-ha...
I apologize for coming by so late. I've come
to ask the Black Bulls for backup—
Who the hell are you?
Huh? Are you here about my tab at the pub?
Ha-bah?! N-No! I'm from the Magic Knights—
I haven't been to any Magic Knights' pub.
But the town of Nean is—
I just paid off my tab in Nean!
Bah-ha?! Let's just drop
the tabs for a second...
You're telling me to pay them again?!
What?!
Would you like some sugar in your tea?
What the hell is wrong with this squad?!
I knew I should've asked
the Blue Rose Knights!
Bah-ha!
Neige! Don't just stand there! Do something!
Go!
You just don't give up.
Mirror Magic: Reflect Refrain.
Done already?
Then die, you wussy loser.
No... S-Stay back!
Snow Binding Spell: Snow Lime Rock!
I-I did it!
Brother...
That's not good. His mirror's been sealed.
Gauche! I'll save you!
Save me? Stop trying to act cool
in front of Marie, damn it!
What?!
You fool! This is no time to act tough!
Shut up! I'll take care of
him myself! We will, that is.
Neige, behind you!
Why... is there another one?
Mirror Magic: Real Double!
Real Double is a spell that summons my
other self from within the mirror world.
I'd already activated the
spell before you caught me.
Th-That's awesome! You're amazing, Gauche!
That young criminal...
He made snow fall over a wide area.
He has a tremendous amount of magic.
But Gauche has magic equal
to his, and most importantly,
he's excellent at fighting with magic.
He's strong, after all.
Though his glare and personality
are the absolute worst.
What's Neige doing?! He's so useless!
Damn it... My body won't move.
There has to be some way...
I know... If I use that—
Why did you do something so awful?!
Stealing other people's magic...
How would you feel if
someone did that to you?!
Like I care, you moron!
It doesn't matter to me if someone
else dies or loses their magic!
You bastard!
Stop!
This isn't enough pain to
make up for what you did!
You're gonna pay for this, starting now!
That's right. This scum isn't even
worth striking with your fist.
More importantly, we have to
do something about those kids.
Hey, tell us how to give
them their magic back!
At least let me go! Then I'll tell—
Don't mess with me!
He's rotten to the bone.
Asta, first, undo the spell
that's on the children.
As for you, don't try anything funny.
Like I could right now...
Mud Magic: Mud Men.
Where am I?
Mama? Papa?
My feet hurt!
Sister!
There, there. Come here, all of you.
Asta!
Luca! Everything's going to be okay.
Hurry up and treat
Marie's wounds, you old hag.
You don't have to tell me to
do it, you sister complex punk.
Flame Recovery Magic: Sacred Healing Light.
It's so warm!
Hey, you brats in the middle.
Make some room for Marie!
That way she'll get better faster.
Oh, stop it, Brother!
Bless you, Marie. You're as kind as an angel.
Angels belong in the middle!
The magic will work just the
same wherever she stands.
Marie, want some dried tatoes?
You'll feel better!
Marie's not going to eat your weird food!
Hey! It's what Hage is famous for!
Asta, you grew up at the
church in Hage, didn't you?
Huh? How did you know that?
Sister Lily came to our church to train once.
She told me about you then.
Heavens me! You know Sister Lily?
She was a fine young woman.
Isn't she?!
Wait, so Sister was talking
about me? What did she say?!
That you were a small and noisy child.
But she also said this...
After I finish this, all I
have left are the windows.
Hey, you're not going to last if you
work this hard from day one.
This is nothing at all. I know someone
who works even harder than this.
He can't use magic at all,
but he says he's going to be the Wizard King
someday and trains every single day.
The Wizard King? If he
doesn't have any magic,
he probably won't even be
able to join the Magic Knights.
Yes, you're right. But still, he always
says, "Not yet! I'm not done yet!"
He works really hard.
Which is why... Not yet! I'm not done yet!
She said you were a hard
worker with a strong heart
who wouldn't give up in the face of adversity,
and that she was very proud of you.
Looks like all of your hard work paid off.
But I've still got a long way to go!
I'm going to become the
Wizard King, no matter what!
I'm not so sure about that.
I will not give up!
Sister, I'm never, never, never, never,
ever going to give up on you, either!
Marie told me that you
were the one who hit her.
The only way to atone for that is death.
Stop that, Gauche!
Brother! I'm okay!
My injuries are all healed now, so let him go!
No, I can't.
I will eliminate anyone who might hurt Marie
now, before they have the chance!
Asking them how to return the
children's magic is more important.
You two. Why did you do this?
These children are the
future of this kingdom.
They're the three-leaf sprouts
that grace this nation!
I just wanted friends...
It hurts... What should I do, Baro?
Stop your whining,
you useless little brat!
It hurts, damn it! Why is
this happening to me?!
It's her. It's all her fault. She tricked me.
I thought it was a good way to make money!
Hurry up and get back here, you moron!
Wow!
That's...
There she is.
Took you long enough, for someone
who travels with spatial magic!
They got in the way of our
magic collecting! Help us!
Jeez, you're so whiny. But you
get a pat on the back this time.
Asta!
She's from the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
I'm so happy we get to see
each other again so soon!
It's that crazy lady!
What? There was an incident in Nean?
You should've mentioned
that earlier, you dumbass!
But I've been saying that from the start!
Quit making excuses!
What?!
You're asking me for reinforcements, but...
Nean, huh... I've always wanted to go
there once. But now's not the time for that.
I dunno what's going through
these guys' heads,
and I sure can't be bothered,
so I don't know what to tell you.
My friend's in trouble. I want to
save him with my curse magic...
Are these guys really Magic Knights?!
Everyone, stay calm.
Please get inside the church.
Marco...
Luca...
I-It's okay. They'll be home soon.
Despite how they look, Asta and
Gauche are Magic Knights.
And we'll be getting reinforcements
from headquarters soon.
Wow!
Really?
I think I'll make some dinner
while we wait. Help me out.
Okay!
Reinforcements are coming, right?
Hey...
I came here because you called me
with the magic transmission item,
but you haven't gathered that much magic yet.
It's all their fault!
Well, it's not like I care.
All of you stay right here. You hear me?
The Eye of the Midnight Sun... The terrorist
group that attacked the capital?
That's them!
So basically, you're the one who
put Marie through all this.
I'll kill you!
Gel Magic: Sticky Salamander!
Could you not interrupt our moving reunion?
While I'm at it, maybe I'll dissect you all!
What is that ominous magic?
Be careful, Gauche, Granny!
I heard she blocked the
Silver captain's attack, too!
Here I come!
Incoming!
Not yet! I'm not done yet!
Anti-magic is no problem
at all if it can't hit me!
Impudent pest!
Mirror Magic: Reflect Refrain!
She deflected all of it!
That's some fine magic,
but it gets refracted inside Salaman,
so there's really no point.
Things might be a bit different
if you have something stronger!
Gauche!
Here you go, Asta!
This is nothing!
Gotcha!
I can't move...
You look just like a normal human.
I want to know all about you!
Rawr!
Ow! That hurt! And you're scary!
Well, your blood's normal.
Next, I'm just going to take your pinky nail.
Stop it!
Flame Magic: Brilliant Flame Cross!
Aw. You melted my little Salaman.
That's enough of that!
I won't let you have this boy!
Hey, don't get in the way.
Th-That's amazing...
Thanks, Granny! You're super strong!
I may be old, but I'm a former Magic Knight!
I'm Theresa the Crimson She-Leopard!
Former Magic Knight
Theresa the Crimson She-Leopard
Huh?!
She's suddenly all pumped up?!
Wait... Former Magic Knight?!
Crimson... Then do you
know Captain Fuegoleon?
Oh, Fueggy? Sure.
"Fueggy"?!
When I served at the palace,
I was his tutor.
Fueggy, your mana's getting unsteady.
Y-Yes, ma'am!
Your enemies won't wait for you in battle.
Concentrate! And remain calm at all times!
Yes, ma'am!
He was such a snot-nosed brat,
but he grew up quite well.
I seriously can't picture that.
But Granny, Captain Fuegoleon was...
By them.
Yeah, I know.
We'll catch this one, no matter what.
Do something about this, you old hag!
What are you doing over there,
you sister complex failure?
You stupid old hag...
Three against one, huh?
That doesn't look so good.
Hey, you.
I'll back you up with my mud magic.
Just fix my body so I can move.
You can do that, right?
Well... There is a way, but are you sure?
Of course I am! Anything's fine, just do it!
Okay, I'll do it, then. But are you sure?
Yeah!
Are you really sure?
I told you, I'm sure!
Just shut up and do it!
Hey! What are you two whispering about?!
H-Hurry up and heal me!
And give me some money!
Then I'll help you out.
Yeah, right. Once I'm freed and paid,
I'm getting the hell outta here!
Okay. In that case... Hup!
What is she...
Baro?!
What the heck?!
What is that?! His magic is swelling!
Whoopsie! Looks like I messed up a little.
He can move now, and his magic's recharged,
but looks like his personality
wandered off somewhere.
Protect the children, Gauche! Asta!
Right!
Let's go, Marie.
B-Brother?
Go? But what about everyone else?
It doesn't matter! It's too dangerous
for you to be around that monster!
What?!
That fool.
I'm going to take you home
for sure this time, Asta!
Brother...
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Go! Go! Gordon!
Bah-ha! I managed to ask for
backup, so I'm going home!
Bah-ha!
But the Black Bulls' base
is like a maze... Bah-ha?
Wh-What the heck?!
Why are you following me?! Bah-ha!
What's this room?!
It's the captain's beast room
This is the bathroom
Bah-ha!
I should be safe here...
The water's great
Bah-ha-ha?!
Bah-ha! I'm going to be killed!
Where's the exit?!
I just want to lead you to the exit...
Mirror, mirror on the wall, who's the cutest—
No, you don't even need to answer!
It's Marie! I don't need
a mirror to tell me that!
Black Clover, Page 33:
"To Help Somebody Someday."
Page 33
To Help Somebody Someday
Protecting Marie is my magic!