It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
Vetto from the Eye of the Midnight Sun
suddenly appeared before Asta and the others.
He came to steal the magic stone
that was in the Underwater Temple.
Let's go, Kiato!
You got it, Asta!
How boring.
Slow movements and weak attacks.
I suppose I can't expect more from
no-magic trash and hick scum.
You sure know how to hurt a
guy's feelings, you hairy gorilla.
We'll show you what happens when
trash and scum get serious!
Asta and Kiato struggled,
but Vetto was just too strong.
Did you get your hopes up?
These childish attacks won't work on me!
Not yet...
No-magic trash! Prancing around
with weapons too good for you...
So what?!
You never had any hope of winning.
Now... scream! Despair!
Ib I gwabe up...
Fu curd I brotec?
Huh?
He said, "If I gave up, who could I protect?"
Awakening
Noelle...
Kahono!
I see that you two are next.
Try to entertain me at least a little bit.
Dad...
Magna... Luck!
Asta!
Everyone was defeated so easily...
Just how strong is this guy?
Not yet!
Losers... can get lost!
Asta!
Song Magic: Rhythm Cushion!
Thanks, Kahono.
That'll just be a thousand yuls.
I'll pay you back a hundredfold.
Can you heal everyone with
your song recovery magic?
I can, but do you think that guy's
going to wait for me to finish singing?
That's...
Hey!
Big Brother! Why are you sleeping?!
What happened to our promise to become an
idol and dancer, and then become huge stars?!
We were going to become sibling
idols who could sing and dance!
That's right!
Huh? He's your big brother?
Yup. That moron over there
is my big brother, Kiato.
Who are you calling a moron?!
Ow...
If I hadn't softened the blow of
that punch with my dance magic,
he would've taken my head off.
He's unbelievably strong.
But...
The two of us dream of going to the surface!
That's right! If we want to fulfill that dream,
we can't just sit around napping!
Let's go, Kahono!
Yeah!
Her mana's getting stronger?
Combo Spell:
Sea God Slash!
Sea God Slash is a song
and dance combo spell.
Dancing to Kahono's song
reinforces my dance magic,
and unleashes magic slashing attacks!
Amazing...
Kiato! Kahono!
You can do it! The two of you have got this!
You've worked so hard ever
since you were little.
I guess that's enough for today.
No way. We'll never get rich if
this was enough to tire us out.
You're right. We can't become stars that way.
Yup. Besides, we need to make sure our
song and dance will please the sea god.
Yeah, so we need to work harder.
Okay, let's do this.
Yeah!
Your hard work...
...won't betray you!
Oh? All this power
from a little bird's song
and a mouse's dance.
Frontier magic is truly intriguing.
That's right! This spell was
created because we're here!
We served the sea god, praying,
singing and dancing...
We spent a long time that way,
weaving the magic into our lives!
That's right! Ever since we were
little, we've offered up this song
and dance to the sea god
and the rest of our people!
This spell...
...is our bond with the people
of the Underwater Temple!
You can do it!
Kiato! Kahono!
Go, Kiato! Kahono!
We're not going to let you...
...break that bond!
Did they do it?
So what?
No way...
Wha...
Kiato!
Big Brother!
Run, Kahono!
Dreams? Bonds?
People like you have no right
to talk about such things!
Kahono!
Curse you!
Game Magic: Monster Toy!
Every last one of you thinks
this is some child's game.
We're the ones who truly
have dreams and bonds...
We, the Eye of the Midnight Sun!
The ones you broke...
Our golden dreams and our bonds of blood!
What is that fool talking about?
You devil!
Now you won't be able to perform your
silly songs and dances ever again.
In other words, your cheap little
dreams just went down the drain.
Well, weakling? You grounded little bird...
Did you get a good taste of despair?
I don't like those eyes.
In that case, I'll have to rip
off your wings one by one...
A bird that can't sing has no reason to live.
I'll just...
Stop!
Let her go!
You think you can stop me with words?
If I miss, I might hit Kahono...
You never had any hope of winning.
Now... scream! Despair!
I couldn't attack earlier, either.
In any case, would my attacks
even work on someone like him?
Are you finished? Then just
watch from there, you loser.
Everyone's fighting, even though
they're getting torn to pieces.
And yet, I...
I...
It's all right.
Kahono?
That immense power inside you...
You'll be able to control it now, Noelle!
Because you're fighting to protect
what's important to you.
You're fighting to win!
What's important to me?
You'll be fine! There's no doubt about it...
Because I'm your friend, and I say so!
Hey...
It's shaking?
Wh-What's going on?
So you finally showed up,
Noelle!
I'll tell you one more time.
What is this power?
Let my friend go!
Black Bulls girl,
you're not letting what your
siblings said get to you, are you?
There's no time for that on the battlefield!
One wrong decision and a life could be lost!
You're standing here right now
as a member of the Magic Knights!
If you joined the Magic Knights
of your own free will,
then steel yourself and get stronger!
Steel myself?
Being weak is nothing to be ashamed of.
However, staying weak is!
Let my friend go!
This power...
Girl, you're royalty?
So what if I am?
That has nothing to do with this!
I'm Noelle Silva of the Black Bulls!
How dare you hurt my friends and comrades?!
I see...
I knew it.
You're from the most corrupt clan!
Very well!
Come at me with all of your strength!
I'll force you and that
sinful mana to your knees!
I'll defeat you,
whether you ask me to or not!
Water Creation Magic: Sea Dragon's Roar!
Th-The sea god?
I did it!
Take a look at that power!
Noelle, you little... I think you
might've killed your limits there.
She's the sea god incarnate...
No, she's a goddess!
I always figured she had
incredible latent ability,
but who would've thought she
was such an attack mage?
Come live with me.
It's not you who should despair.
It's the people of the Clover Kingdom.
Remember...
your true self.
May you two be happy!
What...
This can't be!
The humans?!
I'll kill them!
Impressive... You managed
to draw me out, human.
What's with that eye?
And this eerie magic I've
never felt before...
Mythical Beast Magic...
N-No way!
What in the world is that?
He regrew the arm he lost?
There isn't any magic like that!
The best that even the most powerful
recovery spell can do is close wounds.
These guys aren't just terrorists.
They're something weirder...
Something abominable!
Run... Get out of there, Noelle!
Run?
I...
won't run!
That's some fine resolve for an insect.
Now, it's payback time.
Vanish!
Mythical Beast Magic...
Sea Dragon's...
That last spell drained all my magic!
A-Asta!
Kid!
Not yet...
Not yet, damn it!
We haven't given up yet!
Not yet? Yes, not yet!
Starting now, I'll show you true despair!
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Mythical Beast Magic!
Hey, what were you saying during
your mythical beast magic spells?
Very well, insect. I'll tell you.
Who are you calling an insect?! I'm royalty!
This is the spell!
Easy, right? Read it.
I can't read that.
It's...
Say what?
Peter Piper picked a peck of pickled peppers?
That's not it at all!
It's...
The only difference between a
whale and a dolphin is their size?
Udon
Somen
Hiyamugi
The only difference between udon, somen,
and hiyamugi is how thick they are!
Hawk
Eagle
Apparently hawks and eagles
are the same birds, too.
I did not know that!
Of course I knew that! I'm a royal!
What were we talking about again?
Insects, I'm getting tired
of your incessant buzzing!
I'll crush you with my own hands, one by one!
Black Clover, Page 47: "The Only Weapon."
Page 47
The Only Weapon
My magic is Mythical Beast Magic!