It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
Despair...
You've lost!
Asta mustered up everything he had
and used it on this blow to Vetto.
How do you like that, you bastard?!
But the battle wasn't over yet!
I'm taking you all down with me... No...
I'll blow this whole temple to smithereens!
And then...
Right, consider it brought.
Hey, you dumbasses. You good?
Captain Yami!
Accepting all the feelings of
Asta and the other members,
Yami dealt a fatal blow.
It doesn't matter how strong your magic is!
Dark Magic: Dark Cloaked Dimension Slash!
Consider that my thanks for
looking after my squad.
See ya, Mister Despair.
Stay there and watch for a while.
You're going to be my main dish...
After I season you with despair,
as you watch all of your friends die!
I dealt with you in the end.
Hopefully, you can pass on now.
Sorry, but I didn't despair at all, either.
We're being led far away
Until we shatter the road
between light and darkness
Yo Guess who's back
Everybody get down
Guess who's back
Hey step up step up!
End of the Battle,
End of Despair
I'm falling down because of a twist of fate
The harmony we had is in the past
Still left behind
The scent of you is stuck in my head
Can't shake it
Waiting just isn't enough anymore, Yai yah!
Hey Guess Who is back!?
As I hold on to my wish
The roulette points to tomorrow
Hey Guess Who is back!?
Let the light shine
In the dark maze
Hey Guess Who is back!?
Until we seize the hope in front of us
Heave ho... Heave ho...
Hang in there! We're going to
take you right to the hospital!
There...
Bah-ha... Bah-ha?
That monster's presence... vah-hanished?
Captain Yami!
Hey!
I-I didn't ask for your help.
But I guess you saved us.
You should've shown up sooner.
Who do you think you're talking to?
Oh, Captain! I've fallen
for you all over again!
You're invincible! Absolutely amazing!
Now, drink up.
Maybe later.
I thought I was going to die...
I saw my life flash before my eyes...
You were surprisingly useful for once.
Yes, surprisingly!
Y-You were amazing, Captain!
I'm so embarrassed!
Who were you again?
La! You were amazing!
Well, aren't you guys fluffy?
Captain.
We're done here, so can I go see Marie now?
Take the hint. You're supposed
to praise me right now.
You're so awesome, Captain Yami!
It only took one hit!
You're just so...
You're annoying me!
Yeesh...
Gramps.
Sir Yami Sukehiro...
And members of the Black Bulls.
Congratulations on defeating the
Eye of the Midnight Sun team
and beating the game!
And...
Thank you from the bottom of my heart
for saving our Underwater Temple!
Thank you! Thank you!
Please allow me, as the high priest,
to grant your wish!
Sure. So just as we promised,
we'll be taking the magic stone that
you have here at the Underwater Temple.
Come on, hand it over.
What's the magic stone?
Huh?
Hey, Gramps, I thought you
knew about the magic stone.
You guys are after the
magic stone, aren't you?
If you want it, why don't
we play a little game?
That's what you said, remember?
Uh... I just heard you guys talking
about how you were looking
for something called a "magic stone."
It's a "magic stone," so I assume it's a stone...
What kind of stone is it? What does it do?
You old bastard...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, calm down! Calm down!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
It's been so long!
I haven't felt this pain
since Saussy Village!
Hey, Nero. I wondered
where you'd gone off to.
I guess you were looking
for the magic stone for us!
Good job!
Ah, so that's the magic stone...
If that's all you want,
sure, go ahead and take it.
No need to hold back.
Why would we hold back?
All right, we'll be taking it.
This concludes our mission.
All of you...
Well done.
Yes, sir!
The moment I relaxed, all my strength just...
Asta!
I'm all out of magic, too.
Me, too.
Same.
I'm starving...
Oh, this won't do!
Let's tend to your wounds and help
you recover your magic and stamina.
To think that Vetto was actually defeated.
I won't forgive them. I will never
forgive those who make Licht sad.
We must take back the magic stone...
so that we can fulfill our dream as
the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
Damn it. I can't believe we have to
wait for Finral's magic to recover
before we can go back to the surface.
You're so friggin' useless.
Again, I have seniority.
So, Grey... It turns out
you're a super cute girl.
I-I'm so embarrassed!
Please don't look at me!
If your eyes get any pervier,
I'm going to sew them shut, Pervy Finral.
What?!
And Grey, if you're that embarrassed,
you're never going to make it in the world.
And you should be a little
more humble, you witch floozy!
Oh? Are you embarrassed, virgin delinquent?
Who you callin' a delinquent?!
I can't wait to fight again.
I'm so hungry, I can't even move.
Why the hell is it that you're just hungry?!
I wonder if that's yummy...
What really matters here
is that we got our asses kicked, so I didn't
get to look cool at all, damn it!
Nothing we can do about that.
This was the full extent of our abilities.
La? Is there a banquet?
Thank you, Black Bulls!
You guys were amazing!
You're the saviors of the Underwater Temple!
You guys were so cool!
We, the absolute worst
Magic Knights squad in history,
are being thanked by people.
Yeah, isn't it great?
I wanna get even stronger!
Then I'll get even stronger than you!
I want to see Marie more.
I wish I wasn't so easily embarrassed.
That girl's hot! That one's great, too!
Sounds like you're all better.
Being thanked by others is pretty nice.
I'm so sorry, Kahono.
You're my friend, but I
couldn't protect your voice.
I'm so sorry.
What are you talking about, Noelle?
Thank you for protecting my home.
Huh?
Your magic was amazing!
It's because you helped
me with my training.
Yeah, I know. You'd better be grateful.
Also!
I haven't given up on my dream.
So that I can go sing up on the surface again...
I'll make sure this heals.
So when I'm an idol someday,
you'd better come and hear me sing,
Noelle.
Kahono...
Yeah! I'll definitely go, so you'd better
save me the best seat in the house!
Promise!
I promise.
Oh, you should probably get
some rest. I'll come by again.
Sure. Thanks for coming to see us.
Okay, see you later.
You were awake, Kiato? What's wrong?
You look goofier than usual.
Such beautiful tears...
And such a beautiful smile...
That must be the sea goddess
everyone was talking about.
I'm in love!
Okay... I'm going to get my leg healed up fast!
I have to dance the courtship dance for her!
You have to introduce me to her later!
Help me win her over, will ya?
All right! I'm starting to feel better!
I'm pretty sure Noelle's unavailable, though.
Wh-Whoa!
We ended up getting the magic stone,
but so much happened that we didn't expect.
Hey! Where are you going?
Wait up! Stop wandering off like that!
Jeez... Don't blame me if you get lost.
What?
What's up, kid?
Wow, you're amazing, Captain Yami!
You must've sensed my ki.
I asked you what's up, didn't I?
Answer my question or I'll send you flying.
What?!
W-Well... Since we're leaving this place
tomorrow, I wanted go exploring a bit.
So I was wandering here and there.
Just full of energy, aren't you?
So did you find anything?
Yep! I found fossilized seashells, almost got
swallowed by a giant sea anemone,
and got attacked by this insane
swarm of wharf roaches!
Gross!
And then...
I happened to find these pretty flowers.
I can't forgive these guys.
I don't know what it is,
but these guys must've had something
they can't forgive, either.
Something that makes them
hate humans so much.
Dreams? Bonds?
People like you have no right
to talk about such things!
Now you've done it, human!
Don't think that you have hope just
because you've banded together, humans!
There is no way that I would
lose... against you humans!
I thought that maybe he was feeling
more despair than anyone else.
You're an idiot, aren't you?
Huh?
I asked if you were an idiot.
Answer the question or I'll send you flying.
Huh?! Yes! I'm an idiot!
Idiots don't need to think so hard
about stuff like that, you idiot.
You just need to keep chasing your dream.
My dream?
At least for now.
I can't see! And I can't push it back up!
Captain Yami! Both of my arms are broken!
Hello? Captain Yami?
Huh?
Captain Yami!
For now, I just need to
keep chasing my dream, huh?
My dream, no, our dream is...
Yuno! Look, look!
I got my own grimoire!
It's insanely shabby, but I'm gonna take
good care of it for the rest of my life!
There, there, there, there, there.
There, there, there, there.
I'll repay you for this someday.
Asta...
Do you remember our promise?
So you're gonna become the Wizard King, too?
That means...
Yuno, you're...
Asta, you're...
...my rival!
You mean you remember it?
I thought you were just making fun of me.
I have no interest in being
too friendly with my rival.
But you're the one who gave me hope.
Even if you're poor, an orphan...
or even us...
We can become greater than anyone
else in this world. And to prove that...
To make Sister and everyone else happy...
Let's see who can become the Wizard King!
Not yet.
Not yet, not even close.
I still lack the strength.
Yuno's still ahead of me!
The captain's right!
I just need to chase my dream right now!
I'm gonna hurry up and get my arms
all healed, get even stronger,
and I'm definitely gonna
become the Wizard King!
Thank you!
You really were amazing!
Thanks!
Munchy, munchy, nom...
How long are you guys gonna thank us?!
They sure have a lot of energy.
Too much energy.
What's wrong with that?
It's nice and merry.
And there are so many cute girls!
Yum...
Eat as much as you'd like!
Well, see ya.
Thanks for everything.
Come back soon. We'll welcome
you with open arms.
Come back, damn it! Capisce?
I didn't get to look cool at all...
Even though I'm the strongest
at the Underwater Temple...
Charmy, how are the Eye of the
Midnight Sun guys you caught doing?
They're yelling something.
They won't be able to escape,
so we should be fine.
Hey, isn't that a ridiculously
powerful binding spell?
Is it?
Kiato! Kahono!
Don't give up on your dreams!
I'm sure there's magic that
can heal your leg and throat!
I'll do my best to fix both of my arms, too.
I'll be dancing on this
leg again in no time!
Asta, thank you.
I won't give up, no matter what!
Okay. Let's go.
Got it!
Good grief. I can finally go see Marie.
Th-Thank you for everything!
See you!
Bye-bye!
See ya!
Thanks for the yummy meals!
Come visit sometime!
Thank you!
4 AM in the morning
Why can't I sleep?
On such a bad day, whispering
"Bye Bye Black Birds"
Won't make my anxiety go away
for hours, lately
I've been crying for hours Baby
I wish you were here
All those letters that you gave to me
Every time I read them again, the pain's gone
We're not alone, cause we're perfect as four
Even though we're far apart,
we're connected, believing you
I always feel you next to me
closer to me and a "clover" for you
I wish you the best of luck
You know you're not alone,
cause we're perfect as four
Even though we're far apart,
we're connected, you live in me
I'll always be by your side
closer to me and a "clover" for you
I wish you the best of luck
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Bah-ha Forever!
So I worked really hard saving all
the Magic Knights on Raquey Beach.
Surprisingly true
Bah-ha!
I even got a star from the Wizard King!
I just don't know what to do with myself.
Amazingly, also true
I'm not even that amazing.
This, of course, is also true
Captain Jack was moved to tears!
This is a lie
Bah-ha!
I think I may be a bit drunk...
on myself!
You better not let your guard down
just because one mission's over!
The next one's coming right up!
What?! I have to stay behind at the base?!
Black Clover, Page 51: "Proof of Rightness."
Page 51
Proof of Rightness
Staying behind with everything
I have is my magic!