It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
Yami, Asta, Charmy, and Finral
came to report to the Wizard King
after their battle at the Underwater Temple.
And then...
I'm sorry to interrupt.
The border town of Kiten, which has a history
of skirmishes with the Diamond Kingdom,
is under attack by a
Diamond Kingdom squad.
Wh-What's with that massive horde of people?!
Three of the Eight Shining Generals.
What are the Eight Shining Generals?
The eight strongest from the Diamond Kingdom.
They're similar to the Magic Knights
Captains of the Clover Kingdom.
The first ones to arrive at Kiten
in their time of need were...
That's—
The Clover Kingdom's most
powerful Magic Knights Squad.
The Golden Dawn!
Yami and the others headed
to Kiten as reinforcements.
Just you wait, Yuno!
Let's make them regret barging into
our country with their muddy boots.
Whoever's Strongest Wins
Man, you girls sure are cute!
I know a meadow where there are
flowers as beautiful as you two.
Say, why don't we take a little
trip there with my spatial magic?
What's the matter? You look like you
just saw something really scary.
They're going to murder us!
Hey! What's the big idea?!
Relax, la.
Shut up! Hurry up and get
us to the town called Kiten!
Huh? But I thought we were off today...
You don't get any time off.
You can have all the time off
you want once you're dead.
What?!
Let's do this, Finral!
Hurry up with the portal
already, you bastard.
C'mon, let's see how far you can jump.
Are you mugging me now?!
We're counting on you, Finral!
Why are you so raring to go?!
My meal-saving prince!
What are you even talking about?
Let's go!
Huh, what?
Hurry it up!
Okay, fine! Here we go!
It's the Golden Dawn!
So you're the advance guard
for the Golden Dawn?
Not bad for a little brat!
Goodness.
Such a wretched form for a Shining General.
How unsightly.
Lagus!
I can't bear to watch. I'll lend you a hand.
No one asked for your help!
He's mine!
It appears that the people
have great faith in him.
Lagus! Listen to me when I'm talking to you!
In that case, let's see if you can protect
yourself as well as your people!
Arrows... Bell.
Yup! Leave it to me!
Wind Magic: Swift White Bow.
What?!
Impossible!
He easily deflected my fastest
lightning-coated arrows
and even broke through my barrier?
"See if you can actually protect them"?
That's my line.
Wh-Who are you?
Let's see if you can protect
yourself and your comrades.
Yeah! Yeah!
Yuno and I are one, right?
Hey, why are you ignoring me?
At least say something!
"Something."
Really?! Quit messing with me, you smart-ass!
Want my help now, Lagus?
How dare he make me look like a fool?
He's mine! Stay out of my way, Brocks!
He's mine! You stay out of my way!
He's mine!
Mine!
What are you talking about?!
Yuno's mine!
Not a chance.
Good grief.
The kid I encountered in the
dungeon has gotten a lot stronger.
Man, it's not fair how fast kids grow.
Way to make an old man feel older.
My girls are growing up fast, too.
When they were younger,
they always said they wanted
to marry me when they grew up.
But now they won't even take baths with me.
And they don't want my underwear
washed with their clothes...
A-Adjutant General Lotus?
And they say my breath smells like onions...
Steel Creation Magic: Fierce Spiral Lance!
There's no end to them!
All these people...
They're all so weak!
His magic keeps clinging to us,
making our spells not work properly!
There.
Slime Creation Magic: Mucusnail!
This spell drastically weakens
the magic of anyone it catches.
You'll never be able to get out of there.
I just love watching powerless
weaklings writhe in agony.
Wow, that looks like a
tough spell to deal with.
Though, I mean, it's pretty
useless against me.
What was that spell?
Spatial magic?
Yikes... The one thing about this spell
is that it sort of destroys anything.
Oh, well. I guess someone will
just have to rebuild it.
Let's see... That guy's definitely
the leader of the Golden Dawn.
I wonder why he's just
standing there. How creepy.
He's got his grimoire open, so I
think he's using magic, but...
All I see is what looks
like tree roots spreading.
A spell to grow a huge tree?
That sounds nice and peaceful.
But there's no one who could summon a spell
big enough to protect this whole city.
He's using other people's magic?
Why do I always notice stuff like this?
Calling the three generals!
This is Adjutant General Lotus.
The enemy general,
the captain of the Golden Dawn,
Mine!
seems to be activating a
large-scale magic attack.
Mine!
At the very least,
the range will include all of Kiten.
Mine!
I repeat! The captain of the Golden Dawn
is activating a large-scale magic attack.
And they're definitely not listening.
What should I do? Run?
The time is at hand.
The great tree shall now bloom!
What the heck is this insane magic?
World Tree Magic: Great Mistilteinn Tree.
All for the Clover Kingdom's prosperity.
So this is Kiten.
Wait, whoa! What the heck is this giant tree?!
Trees like that grow around here?
Do you think there's giant fruit up there?!
Okay, that's enough out of you idiots.
This is probably Captain Shiny's spell.
Wait, what?! This is a spell?
Maybe they didn't need us after all.
Really? Let's go back, then! Please?
Nah. I'm gonna go check and
see how the battle's going.
I'm assuming Captain Shiny's up top.
I'm gonna head up there. You three help
the townspeople, and try not to die.
Leave it to us!
Hey! Y-Yami!
First, I'm gonna get me
a piece of that fruit.
Asta's hurt, and Charmy's... drooling.
Yeah... I'm nervous.
Good grief.
Apparently, there was an incredible
amount of magic on that battlefield.
I suspect this cleaned up most of it, though.
We've suffered a huge loss!
Our army's basically wiped out!
Our army... has basically been wiped out?
Curse you!
You know what they say
about people who get greedy.
How unsightly.
My arms might be useless,
but I've still got my legs!
Everyone! Please come this way to escape!
Please get on this, la.
Are you hurt? Please, come this way.
Thank you.
It is our duty as Magic Knights to
save the citizens of the kingdom.
If you're not busy,
why don't we... get some tea later?
Whoops. If I look down, my tears will...
La?
Someone's going head-to-head with
one of the Diamond guys in the sky.
Yuno!
My meal-saving prince!
Go! Go! My lovely prince!
You can do it, you can
do it, my lovely prince!
La!
This young man is so strong...
Inconceivable! I'm one of
the Eight Shining Generals!
You shall fall before my beautiful magic!
Beautiful?
Beauty doesn't matter in battle.
Whoever's strongest wins.
That's all there is to it.
So beautiful...
He defeated him with a single blow!
Such a refreshing breeze...
I thought I saw a familiar little speck.
What are you doing here, Asta?
That guy joined the Magic Knights
the same time Asta did.
Not to mention you're all torn up,
scrambling around, and soaked with sweat...
Talk about ugly.
He worked his way up into
the Golden Dawn's elite?
Of course he'd make fun of the Black Bulls.
All that and he's handsome, too.
He's probably super popular.
The fact that you're so beat up means...
You got stronger again, didn't you?
Huh?
I'm not losing to you, Asta.
Yuno's... smiling?
La...
I-I could eat a hundred bowls
of rice along with that smile.
Look who's talking! You got
crazy strong, too, you jerk!
I'm not gonna lose either, Yuno!
He's an elite in the Golden Dawn,
has super powerful magic,
and is super handsome...
Yet he's competing with Asta,
a member of the Black Bulls,
who's a meathead with zero magic!
They must be great rivals.
Are you all right, Yuno?
Are you hurt at all?
Asta!
What happened to your arms?!
Are they gravely hurt?! Are you all right?!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Not that I was worried or anything.
You got hurt because you let your guard down!
Pay more attention!
R-Right...
I'll heal you immediately
with my recovery magic.
I'm fine. Go ahead and
heal all the citizens.
Oh, my goodness! I shouldn't
have been so forward!
I'm so sorry!
That's right! We don't have
time to deal with you!
Let's go, Mimosa.
Right.
Yuno, you stay near Asta.
I'm sure you can't fight
with your arms like that.
But I'm not trying to spoil you or anything!
You can go now.
Please take care, Asta!
Bye-bye! Ow...
I finally found you.
You must be the captain of the Golden Dawn.
I had completely underestimated you.
Who knew you'd have such tremendous magic?
You've got impressive magic yourself.
There's no reason to perish in vain.
Take your comrades and leave this land.
What?
Diamond soldiers never retreat!
Red Clay Magic:
Brilliant Armor Heavy Artillery!
What's that weak little spell supposed to do?
Let me guess... You must
be out of magic already.
Victory is mine!
World Tree Magic: Mistilteinn Seed.
You should be honored.
Your magic has nourished the Clover Kingdom.
A Diamond ambush? He must've been
hiding with his magic concealed.
Yami!
'Scuse me... Shiny Oddball Masked Dude.
Ouch.
I thought that if I could manage
to bag the Golden Captain,
I could turn things around, but...
To think the guy I fought
back then would show up.
And he's even stronger now to boot.
Please stop leaving this
old guy so far behind.
Looks like you owe me one, Vangeance.
You saved me, Yami.
Ki, was it? How astounding.
Hey, old Diamond dude that I don't know.
Wanna surrender?
Wait, really? You don't remember me?
Look. Right here.
I've got no interest in
your filthy-looking chest.
Don't make me cut you down.
D'oh...
So, what's it gonna be?
This is definitely bad news...
But now's the time to show you guys
what a true Diamond looks like, and...
Retreat!
Didn't hesitate one bit. I like that.
Well, then...
Now that we're alone in a
spot with such a great view,
why don't we have a little chat, Vangeance?
Man, your world tree magic
is as impressive as ever.
Please. It's possible thanks
to the enemies' magic.
Right... Your magic is world tree magic.
It is.
Exactly what are you trying to say, Yami?
I'm someone who believes his gut instincts.
Vangeance...
Could you take off that mask?
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Charmy's Seven Transformations
Charmy's Seven Transformations!
To all you Charmy Pappitson fans throughout
the world, no... the universe.
This is the moment you've been waiting for.
Today, we'll be answering all your requests
to see all those cute Charmy moments!
I've been waiting for this!
Transformation one... Wandering Charmy.
Munchy, munchy, munchy...
Transformation two...
Deet de-deet de-deet de-deet and go!
Festival
Happi Coat Charmy.
Transformation three...
Happy Birthday Charmy.
La!
Transformation four...
Lightning God Charmy.
La!
Transformation five...
Alien Charmy!
La, la, la, la, la, la...
And last but not least, transformation six...
Merlion Charmy!
La, la, la, la, la, la...
Amazing!
So there aren't seven transformations?
Did you see, Asta, how unbelievably
strong I've become?
I'm never going to lose to you...
not in strength, looks, or height!
Black Clover, Page 53: "Behind the Mask."
Page 53
Behind the Mask
I'm the one who's going
to become the Wizard King!