It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
The party headed to the Witches' Forest
to break the curse that Vetto
had placed on Asta's arms,
and they found Vanessa in a wretched state.
Miz Vanessa!
Vanessa!
Hey! What the hell are you doing?!
I don't know who you think you are,
but get your foot off of her right now!
You must be the brat
Vanessa was talking about.
This foolish little thing
told me she'd become my slave and
live out the rest of her days here
in exchange for healing your arms.
Miz Vanessa...
In order to save Vanessa,
the party began their battle with
the Queen of Witches, and then...
They were much faster than I expected.
New enemies arrived at the Witches' Forest.
The Eye of the Midnight Sun...
Flame Spirit Magic: Salamander's Breath.
Witnessing how powerful the enemy was,
the Queen of Witches healed Asta's arms
and let him protect the forest.
This is great! They're completely better!
All right! Let's go, guys!
Yeah!
Because of the Queen of Witches's healing
magic, Asta's arms were better than ever.
His battle with Fana, who was
filled with hatred, began.
I'll kill you once and for all.
Bring it on! I'll just keep throwing
your attacks right back at you!
Flames of Hatred
I'll just keep throwing your
attacks right back at you.
Yeah.
Over and over...
Come at me as much as you want!
I'll just keep throwing your attacks right
back at you over and over and over and over!
Damn it, you bastard!
I guess he's built up a lot of stress
since he couldn't use his arms.
I hate you...
This time we'll...
destroy you!
Here they come!
Flame Spirit Magic:
Salamander's Talon.
Wha—
Seriously?!
It's so powerful!
So that's Salamander,
said to have the highest attack
power of the Four Great Spirits.
We're up against a spirit that matches
the military power of an entire nation...
Amazing!
Spirits are mana-based lifeforms.
Asta's anti-magic sword can
slash apart mana itself!
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
Man, that was scary! But it's so cool!
Man, you're so lucky! I want a Salamander!
Asta...
But that old guy, Vetto, was much
faster and had better senses.
We can do this!
...has a chance of winning this!
Honestly... Watching you makes
being scared seem silly.
Jeez... Why are these flames so powerful?
It's like throwing water on burning rocks.
I'm basically just wasting mana.
I hope Asta and the others are okay.
Why did you hurt us?
I hate you.
Okay, time for our counterattack!
Yeah! Yeah...
Hey, you! Let's sit down
and talk this through.
Wha—
What are you saying, Asta?!
She's not someone you can just talk to!
What's with all this hate business?
What exactly do you hate so much?
Would you mind telling me why you
hate the Clover Kingdom so much?
How are we supposed to understand
each other when all we ever do is fight?
Are you ready to talk?
Shut up.
What the heck are you doing?!
Finral!
You got it!
Your friend also really hated us.
The ones you broke...
Our golden dreams and our bonds of blood!
Despair!
And... he was full of despair.
Tell me why!
Can't we just understand each other?
Licht, is that person human?
Yes. He's my friend.
There's something strange about him.
I believe that this will become
a world where our peoples can
live side by side as friends.
We'll be able to understand each other.
Elves' mana is truly amazing.
If we combine that with our techniques
in creating magical items,
we'll be able to make this place
even more prosperous and safe.
Let's do our best to live together.
We wish you happiness!
The mana is giving us its blessing.
I'm so happy that our child will be welcomed
into this world with your blessings.
This child is our future,
the one who'll bring the
elves and humans together.
The humans are attacking!
Hey, wake up!
My love...
Why... Why?!
Only that human knows where we live!
He... He must've betrayed us!
It can't be...
This can't be!
Who...
Who would believe you?!
This magic...
Can you handle all of my hatred?
She's got a third eye, too!
Th-That thing just got bigger?!
Asta!
Not only did it get bigger, it's using
magic with different attributes?
Come on, give us a break!
Let the flames of my
hatred burn you to ashes!
Damn it! In that case...
I'll just have to bring out my special move!
She's no ordinary mage.
I just got a great idea!
Now!
It's so hot!
The wave of hot air was
enough to blow me away.
I won't be able to get closer to her alone.
Miz Vanessa, Finral, are you guys all right?
Somewhat. But...
Her insane amount of magic is
creating a mana force field.
I'm having a hard time manipulating space.
The second I put my magic
thread out, it gets burned.
That magic power is ridiculous.
Is this the power of spirits?
It's like a god incarnate.
Die!
Damn it!
Water Creation Magic: Sea Dragon's Cradle!
What are you guys doing?!
Noelle!
I keep putting out the fires in
the forest, but there's no end to it!
I guess I'll have to extinguish...
Wh-What the heck is that thing? It's scary!
L-Looks like I'll have to
extinguish the source first!
Noelle uses water magic.
And water can beat fire!
It's evaporating...
Fire Spirit Magic: Salamander's Talon!
Hang on tight!
Look out!
Thanks!
What the heck is that monster?
But... I'm the one who uses water magic,
so I have to do this.
I can do this... I know I can do this!
I can do this, I can do this, I can do this!
You can't do it.
You've been damaged goods
ever since you were born.
Of course you can't do it.
The only way you managed
to pull off the attack
at the Water Temple is because
you let your rage take over.
You're a failure.
I really can't...
You're strong!
Noelle! You're strong!
You can do this!
I can't do anything about that flame!
I'm counting on you!
Come on, come on, come on!
You can do anything if you have the guts!
A-Asta!
He's so loud. My ears are ringing.
You hear me, Noelle?!
You can figure anything out with guts!
Asta?! You're a bit too loud!
Hey, Finral! Why are you plugging your ears?
Feel this wonderful breeze!
You got this, Noelle?
Yes.
Get a grip, Noelle.
Just as Asta gave me courage...
You can do it!
You don't need to tell me!
I'll do it, Stupidsta!
I'm going to give Asta courage, too!
Here we go!
It's going to fire.
Right now, I'll probably only be
able to use Sea Dragon's Roar once.
I'll bet everything
on this one attack!
I'm not a failure anymore!
Water Creation Magic: Sea Dragon's Roar!
She dodged it?
Disappear.
Noelle!
I'm not done yet!
We did it!
Wh-Whoa! That's our Noelle!
I'm saved...
I'll never forgive you.
Did you see that, Asta? That's my true power!
Y-Yay, I did it!
Damn, that was awesome!
That's my comrade! All right!
Noelle's attack managed
to subdue the salamander.
Now's our only chance!
Next...
It's your turn!
It's my turn!
All right! Now it's finally time
for my special move!
I won't let you...
Mineral Creation Magic: Harpe!
Huh?!
Why?! How is she able to use
magic besides flame magic?!
That's so not fair!
This spell...
Flame Recovery Magic: Phoenix Robe.
And she can use recovery magic, too! Damn it!
And this spell, too...
I knew it!
Hey, lady!
You wouldn't happen to have a brother
with a really pale face
and spiky hair, would you?
He's over on the other side
of the forest right now!
What are you talking about, Asta?!
I don't know anyone like that!
If I have any siblings, they're Licht
and the people of the village!
Know their grudge against you!
I'll massacre every last one of you!
I can't get through to her at all!
I'll just have to stop her with my
special move before she recovers!
Hang on a sec, Asta! What's this
special move you keep talking about?
Yeah, what is it?
Glad you asked!
You see, I'm gonna hold out
both swords in front of me
and charge straight through
the air at super speed!
I call it...
How could you possibly do that?!
Huh? I can't?!
Not without us, you can't!
You always come up with the craziest ideas.
Let us help!
Asta... Remember what I said earlier?
Your friends are there to help you win
against a fate you can't defeat on your own!
That attack of yours...
will end up being incredibly powerful!
Here we go!
Too late!
I won't let you kill anyone!
Bull Thrust!
He did it!
All right!
My special move was a complete success!
No...
Licht...
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Over and Over
Over and Over!
Come at me as much as you want!
I'll just keep throwing your attacks right
back at you over and over and over and over!
Come at me with all the narutos you want!
I'll just eat all the narutos you throw at me!
Come at me with all the natto you want!
I'm natto gonna let it get me down!
Ew! It's all over my swords!
I wouldn't want to be stabbed by those swords.
Damn it, you stupid natto!
We did it, Asta! We defeated Salamander!
Black Clover, Page 60:
"Defectors' Atonement."
Page 60
Defectors' Atonement
No, Charmy. "Atonement" isn't a kind of food.
It's when you make up for
something bad you did.