It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
The Eye of the Midnight Sun
arrived at the Witches' Forest,
searching for a magic stone.
Wanting to take advantage of
the chaos they were causing,
the Diamond Kingdom came to steal
the Queen of Witches' secret.
Million Lasers!
Guess I'll just have to kill this chick first!
Don't!
Your lessons got through to me.
Fanzell's former student Mars, who was
still in the Diamond Kingdom's army,
decided he would side with him.
Why are you protecting us?
As Ladros said, we're traitors.
And you lost your memory...
Don't worry. I'm on your side, Master.
Deflect it over here!
I don't know what's going on, but okay!
By taking advantage of Asta's anti-magic,
they successfully defeated Ladros.
But the moment they tried to finish off Fana
of the Eye of the Midnight Sun's Third Eye,
who was weakened by Noelle's spell...
Fana!
It's me! It's me!
Don't you recognize me?
My student Fana?
Fana, who had lost her memories,
fell into a deeper state of confusion
and tried to self-destruct, but...
Everything should just... disappear.
Asta and Mars risked their lives to stop her.
Let's go see the world together!
Okay.
It's a promise, Mars.
Fana regained her memories.
Those Who Boost Each Other Up
All right!
Asta.
I couldn't have done it without you.
Thank you.
There is no reason for the weak
to stand on the battlefield.
I was born to break people like you.
You're in my way...
Begone!
The weak will perish,
and only the strong will remain.
Someone as naïve as you
cannot win against me!
That was all your strength!
I'm glad you were able to
save your childhood friend!
Is he your friend, Mars?
Wow! So you made a friend
in the outside world!
No, I wouldn't say he's—
Yeah, he's totally my friend!
We did fight once, though.
Ow...
So hard!
I'm glad you calmed down, too.
But what the heck happened?
You stupid dummy! Why do you have to do
such drastic things every single time?!
Were you born just to try to kill yourself?!
You barely have any clothes on!
You're a magnificent student.
Thank you, Master.
Master Fanzell!
Your powers exist to protect others.
Don't ever forget that.
Yes, sir!
I'm so glad you're both alive.
So you barely remember anything?
Yes.
After the final training, I...
I can hardly believe she's
started breathing again.
Is this the power of the magic that bears
the Phoenix's name? Or could it be...
How fascinating.
We'll fit Fana with a mage stone, too.
What a disappointment.
Not only did it fail to increase her
magic, but she hardly has any left.
I guess that was the last dying ember of it.
Get rid of her. She's of
no interest to me anymore.
You poor thing.
My old friend...
It's just as it was long ago.
Humans even hurt other humans.
As you wish, I shall destroy them.
But... I need your body.
You will live on!
I don't have any memories after that.
It felt as though someone
else entered my body.
Like I was being controlled...
All I remember is that
person's fierce hatred.
What about the third eye
and pointy ears you had?
I'm really sorry.
I don't know anything about them.
You went through all that?
I had no idea, and I...
Mars, you don't need to
feel bad about anything.
I mean, we got to meet again.
Right. I'll never let you go again.
Yeah... Let's stay together forever.
Y-Yeah...
My, my! Aren't things heating up over there?
He's stiffened up as hard as a
chunk of ore. How adorable.
Childhood friends tragically torn
apart and reunited by destiny...
That's really great!
Whoa, he's bawling over there!
What's the matter, Finral?
I'm jealous and envious and bummed out!
Huh? You don't have any childhood friends?
No! I don't have any cute
childhood friends like that!
Nope! Nope! Nope! Not one, damn it!
I have childhood friends!
Lots of them, actually!
Just so you know, I'm not jealous!
Why'd I just get slapped?!
I'm royalty!
Anyway, why did the Eye of the
Midnight Sun come to the Witches' Forest?
I still feel a strong desire in my head
to retrieve the magic stone.
Magic stone?
So that means there's a
magic stone in this forest?
Let's hurry and go see the Queen of Witches!
No, before that, we need to save Domina,
Mariella, and the wounded witches.
What is this ki?
Impossible! His magical power should be gone...
Everyone, run!
Man, that was some intense magic.
It took forever to absorb it all.
Thanks for the meal!
I must admit, I thought I was going to die.
Ladros... But your magic
power should've been depleted.
I emitted it all, and then took it back in.
You rely too much on your
magic detection, Teach.
Really, though, why do all of you
keep putting your own lives
in danger to protect others?
M-Mars...
That's exactly why I'm
gonna end up killing you!
Well, well, some weirdo just showed up.
This doesn't concern you,
so could you get lost?
It's got lots to do with me!
He's my...
friend!
Why do all of you
keep putting your own lives
in danger to protect others?
M-Mars...
That's exactly why I'm
gonna end up killing you!
Well, well, some weirdo just showed up.
This doesn't concern you,
so could you get lost?
It's got lots to do with me!
He's my...
friend!
Asta...
Mars!
I need to use a recovery spell!
I can't cast anything?
What happened to my body? Is my magic gone?
Just hang on! I'm gonna pound this guy!
Whoa, wait a sec! You're that one guy, right?
The anti-magic knight or whatever.
I totally feel your pain, man.
I was born without a magic attribute myself.
Even when I was a kid, everybody made
fun of me and called me bland.
But hey, you're even more worthless than me.
What'd you say, you bastard?!
I kinda feel bad for you.
Give me some of your magic, then!
I would if I could.
Oh, I know.
Here. All yours if you can reach.
What a great reaction! I think
we'd make great partners.
Wanna team up?
You can be my right-hand man.
I'll talk to the Diamond Army for you.
Let's rise up through the
royal army's ranks together!
We'll teach the guys who get all cocky
just because they've got talent a lesson!
Just kidding. I'm gonna make his
anti-magic powers all mine, too!
I refuse.
Huh?
I'm gonna become the Wizard King
of the Clover Kingdom!
Wizard King? Seriously?
This is why I hate idiots! Million Lasers!
I heard about how you fight.
Without that spatial magic guy over there,
you can't do a thing about
long-distance spells, can you?
You make the perfect target!
That ricochet trick won't work on me, either.
Recycle, recycle!
There's no way you can win! Just give up!
Who's gonna give up?
You hurt my friends.
And you won't get away with that!
Friends?
There's no such thing.
There are only two kinds of people
in this world: the users and the used.
I won my way to the top by
using the people around me.
I'm gonna use Mars over there
and the girl next to him to
get myself even further ahead.
Maybe I'll let the military use them
for magic research until they die!
What's the matter? You're not
letting me get away with this, right?
You can be my stepping stone, too!
Huh?
What is this?
N-Not good! My magic's draining away!
I-It won't come out!
Huh? Wait... You're kidding me!
From this? Really?
Crap! Everything I've worked for...
Crap! All I did was take my
eyes off of him for a second!
I'd made it to the rank of
the Eight Shining Generals!
This is bad! Bad! Bad!
No way! No way! No way!
Did he really just throw this stupidly
heavy sword all the way up there?!
What kind of decision was that?
What the hell were you thinking?!
Shit! Shit! This is crazy!
Are you telling me I'm gonna be
taken out by a dumbass attack like this?
Damn it! Stay back! Stay away!
I couldn't have made it this far on my own.
People taught me how to use
my power and how to fight.
We got through life or death
situations together.
We helped each other out
while improving how we fight.
The reason I've been able
to react to the attacks
is because of something called "ki"
from back in my homeland.
Ki?
Where I come from, we've got this saying...
"A warrior never goes back on his word."
You said you were going to
become the Wizard King, didn't you?
Surpass your limits. Right here, right now.
There's no other way.
Yes, sir!
Water Creation Magic: Sea Dragon's Cradle!
What are you guys doing?!
Noelle!
I'll bet everything
on this one attack!
I'm not a failure anymore!
Water Creation Magic: Sea Dragon's Roar!
We did it!
Let us help!
Here we go!
That attack of yours...
will end up being incredibly powerful!
Too late!
I won't let you kill anyone!
Bull Thrust!
He did it!
All right!
My special move was a complete success!
Friends are only meant to be used?
Not my friends! My friends and I...
We boost each other up!
I-I was wrong!
I'll stop hurting people! Please spare me!
Please! Take out this sword!
I can't get it out on my own!
No!
Huh?
I know how strong you are,
so I'm not gonna get careless!
If I take it out and you attack me,
I have no chance of winning!
Besides, if I'd missed when I
threw it at you, I would've lost!
I'm an idiot, so I can't afford
to mess up to begin with!
No, please... I-I'm begging you!
If it doesn't come out, I'm gonna die!
That's not enough to kill anybody!
I missed your vital points on purpose!
Damn it! I thought I'd be able
to trick an idiot like him if I
tugged at his heartstrings,
but he's not buying it!
Shit! Shit! Shit!
This twerp's been through
his share of battles!
So I'm gonna whack you
again and knock you out!
Damn it all!
This is all of my remaining magic.
If I attack him and he blocks it,
I'm really finished!
I'll just have to use reinforcement
magic and force it out!
Ow!
I've got enough left for two magic bullets...
That bastard!
You're Fana, right?
Ladros!
I don't know how you got those powers,
but use that huge magic of yours right now!
Huh? Huge magic? What are you talking about?
Quit playing dumb, and hurry it up!
Do it or I'll kill...
him!
Mars!
The next shot will really kill him.
Stop!
And there it is!
Okay, then...
Time for the ultimate gamble!
This magic's insane!
I feel like my body's gonna burst!
This is the greatest magic I've ever eaten.
Impossible! This power
surpasses the spirit's!
It's not an amount a human can emit!
Ladros, you...
You bastard!
Payback time.
I tracked it with ki, but it was still
so fast that I couldn't dodge it.
I've obtained the ultimate power!
If I use this, the other Eight Shining
Generals don't stand a chance!
Forget them! I can take
over the whole kingdom!
Woohoo!
I'll murder everyone who
ever looked down on me!
But before that, I guess
I'd better finish you off.
I won't get careless again.
I'll keep hitting you with ranged
attacks that you can't block...
until you're in pieces!
Asta!
He's turned the tables.
Since he can use that sword, I thought
he might be their descendant, but...
Show me who you really are!
Now, then, how many more shots can
that body you're so proud of take?
Huh?
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
How Does It Taste?
This is the greatest magic I've ever eaten.
Take that!
Ah, that tastes very regal.
That's royalty for you.
Take that!
Ah, yes. Yours tastes a little mature.
This tastes really nostalgic.
Ladros!
It tastes like pickles!
So you're saying that not only do I look
old, but my magic tastes old, too?!
You got it, Teach!
Tee-hee!
Queen of Witches, what did you do to Asta?!
Asta's grimoire is giving off an eerie light.
You almost look like... a demon!
Black Clover, Page 63: "It's Nothing."
Page 63
It's Nothing
A black meteor shoots across the sky.