It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
And currently...
Now that my arms are better, I need
to make up for all the time I've lost!
It appeared as though peaceful days
had returned to the Black Bulls.
Man, there haven't been any
incidents lately. It's so boring.
It's so peaceful!
But a single mage destroyed it all.
Raging Bull
One potato! Two potato! Three potato, four!
All right, all eyes up here.
He was called the Captain of the Black Bulls,
and for some reason,
he was wearing a happi coat.
So, yeah, there's a festival happening.
A festival?
A Fun Festival Double Date
Captain Yami!
What's this festival all about?!
To put it simply, it's a
friggin' awesome festival!
Understand now?
I see!
Or not at all!
That was a bit too simple.
Finral, explain this festival in more detail.
Huh? U-Uh, sure...
But I have seniority...
As you all know, the Wizard King awards stars
to Magic Knights Squads to
recognize their achievements.
All of the squads compete to
see who can get the most stars.
Then they announce the number
of stars won in a year
and determine the top squad for that
year. That's what this festival is.
Heck yeah! Let's shoot for number one!
Considering how much trouble
our squad causes each year,
I'm sure we're always fighting for last place.
Nope!
Last Year's Star Numbers
1: Golden Dawn 96
2: Crimson Lion Kings 93
3: Silver Eagles 88
4: Purple Orcas 74
5: Blue Rose Knights 72
6: Green Praying Mantises 65
7: Aqua Deer 53
8: Coral Peacocks 51
9: Black Bulls -50
We're dead last, without contest.
I mean, we're the only squad in the negative.
What?! We're causing way
too much trouble, then!
Also, this festival is held
in full view of the public,
and is the biggest, most-loved
festival of the year.
And it's called...
The
Raging
Bull
Star
Festival
...the Star Festival!
The Star Festival
Festival
Whoo! Mister Yami!
He's really into this!
Captain Yami is surprisingly into this!
Right. I can never get into this
stupid festival, but let's go.
Yet you're dressed like that?
I'll go with you, Mister Yami!
Festival! Festival! Festival! Festival!
Girls! Girls! Girls! Girls!
Oh, sorry to interrupt, but Finral...
Girls! Girls! Girls... hm?
There are some people
I'd like you to bring with us.
This is awesome!
All right! Go live it up, you dumbasses!
Raging Bull
Festival
There's still time before
they announce the rankings!
Woohoo! I'm drinking tonight!
La! Noms!
I'm gonna go get some food, too.
I wonder what I should get for Marie.
I wonder if there's anyone strong around.
Hey...
Where'd you buy that funny-looking mask?
This is my face.
Stop that!
I'm super excited!
I wish I could show this
to everyone back in Hage!
Don't get so excited that
you end up getting lost.
W-Well, I guess I'd better
go around with you.
Hey!
Oh, there they are!
Kahono! Kiato!
I've missed you guys!
Asta! You're looking great!
Yeah!
What brings you here, though?
I had Finral bring them over.
Always happy to help out one
of my adorable juniors.
Now, if you'll excuse me, I've got
some kayute girls waiting for me.
Flirty, flirty, flirt!
So this is what a festival
in a surface city is like!
It's amazing!
I'm already grateful enough that you
guys saved the Underwater Temple
from those terrifying
Eye of the Midnight Sun guys.
Thanks for inviting us, Asta.
And there's my beautiful goddess!
Kahono, you still can't talk,
so don't get too excited.
I'm sure Kahono really wants to sing.
And I...
Kiato, did you bring your leg?
Huh? Yeah...
We preserved it with water
magic. Why do you ask?
Good.
In that case...
My leg!
Awesome! We got secret witch
spells from the Queen of Witches,
and that was one of her healing spells!
This is amazing!
I can dance! Just like before!
No...elle?
My voice... I can talk!
I... can....
sing again!
Noelle!
Thank you!
Kahono!
Thank you so much, Noelle!
I'm so happy for you!
Thank you so much, Asta!
S-Sure...
Everyone can hear my song again...
Thank you so much!
That was so pretty!
What a magnificent voice!
I guess now we can strive to be idols again!
Yeah! I'm gonna get even better,
and then get filthy rich!
O-Oh, right...
That's her main goal.
Kahono's way more responsible than I am.
Money's important!
Hey, this festival only
happens once a year, right?
Let's have a total blast!
Yeah!
Your heart is mine, my beautiful goddess.
Shrimpsta!
Magna! What's that giant thing?
What else? It's a cannon to shoot fireworks!
Fireworks?!
I'm gonna be shootin' them off once the
sun goes down, so you better help me!
Heck yeah!
Oh, but I'm about to go enjoy
the festival with them.
What? You aren't going
to listen to your senior?
There're two guys... and two girls.
H-Hey... Are you guys going
on a d-double date?
Double?!
Not bad, Shrimpsta.
Uh, what's this double whatever thing?
Huh? A double date's—
Th-That's not it at all!
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-What are you talking about?!
I certainly won't complain about
a date with my beautiful goddess.
Jeez... I see you still have
a problem with being honest.
That means I'll just have to...
Oh, come on!
It's been forever since we've seen
each other, so let's all have a blast!
I know! Let's actually make it a double date!
What?!
What the heck's about to happen here?!
Okay! Let the double date begin!
A d-double date? That's w-way too bold!
For Kahono to bring this up...
Does that mean she likes Asta?
Kahono... She's doing this to bring
me and my goddess together.
Well done, little sister!
Your big bro's gonna do his best!
What the heck's a double date?!
Whoa!
Come on, Asta. Let's go have some fun!
Ah, so a double date means having fun!
S-So I was right?! Goodness, she l-linked
arms with him right in front of me!
Shall we dance as we go?
Yup. She's panicking.
Noelle, if you don't do something,
I'm going to enjoy this festival with Asta.
If you don't fight and win,
your wish won't come true!
So good! Yum!
Could you write "my beloved goddess"
in mayonnaise for me?
"My beefy glasses"?
No, "my beloved goddess."
I can't shoot!
Sir, you've got to use your magical power.
In that case...
Use some of mine.
Thanks!
Hey! What're you doing, miss?!
Ugh! What's your deal?!
I found this lovely mask that'd
be perfect for you, my goddess!
Woohoo! I got a prize in the magic gun game!
You're awesome, Kahono!
I got some smaller balls
as a consolation prize!
Those two seem like a good match.
Wh-Why do I have to care
about something like that?!
My beautiful goddess, a crêpe for thee!
Ugh, why aren't you even trying, Noelle?
At this rate, I'm just getting
in the way of your crush.
I guess I'll just have to change things up.
I know the perfect spot.
Hey, Noelle. What's this place?
I-It's a haunted house, duh!
What's that?
Huh?! You seriously don't
know anything, do you?
They didn't have these things at
the festivals in Hage Village.
Places like this are well-known for being
extra scary and bringing couples super close!
Otherwise known as the couple
establishment factory!
At this rate, I'm just going
to have to force them together!
K-Kahono, don't leave my side!
I can't let my goddess see me like this!
Come out, ghosts... Or should
I say, cupids of love!
Bah-ha! Let's go over this one more time.
You'll scare the customers,
and then I appear!
Bah-ha... Miss, are you all right?
My, what a brave gentleman!
Indeed! I'm the bravest!
I am the most powerful of
the Magic Knights, after all!
< Lies >
Just between you and me,
I'm confirmed as the next captain
of the Green Praying Mantises!
< Lies >
But I've fallen head over bah-ha for you!
Complete Nonsense
Let us enjoy this night together.
Yes!
And that's how I'm going to
get the girl! Easy peasy.
Yeah, for you.
And here they come. Give it your all!
So when are these ghosts coming out?
H-How am I supposed to know?
Phati!
Aphro!
Huh?
There we go. They're scared.
Asta and Noelle should be clinging to
each other for dear life right about now.
Phati!
Or not?!
Get lost! You stupid insect ghosts!
You guys had the nerve to attack
the royal capital again?!
Bah-ha?! Th-They're...
Save me!
Don't come over here! Hey! Look closer!
It's me!
You must be the boss!
Bah-ha?!
Oh, so they were all fake.
Of course they were! We got
kicked out because of you.
You flew off the handle too, you know.
Y-You're just imagining things.
I-I was so scared...
Another failure! Noelle has to
work harder, but Asta's too dense!
I wonder how he really feels about Noelle.
Hey, Asta.
What does Noelle mean to you?
Huh?
What does she mean to me? Hmm... Let's see...
Mommy!
Is she lost?
Where the heck are her parents?
Hey, you oka—
Look at her shabby clothes.
What an eyesore.
I wonder if her parents are peasants
who came here to find work.
What a noisy brat. Peasants can't
even raise their kids properly.
How dare those lousy peasants
spoil the Star Festival for us?
Only those who possess strong magical
powers can live in the realms above us.
There's prejudice against
those who lack magical powers.
Even though we're all human.
Huh...
Hey!
What's the matter? Why are you crying?
Hey! I can't help you
if you just keep crying!
Get a hold of yourself!
H-Hey...
I know!
Hey, lookie over here!
Hup! Hup! Hup! Hup!
I got you...
Asta the Superman can do anything!
He's tiny, but his voice sure is huge!
He's dumb, but he's bursting with muscles!
He can't use magic, but he
can slash through any spell!
Are you making fun of me?!
He can't use magic,
but there's nothing he can't do!
Superman, Superman, Superman Asta!
Asta the Superman can do anything!
Bursting with muscles!
Slashes through any spell!
Ta-da!
There's nothing he can't do!
Superman, Superman, Superman Asta!
Wow...
My goddess, behold this dance,
which I offer to you!
So, tell me your name.
Emma.
Kahono, could you use your song magic to
broadcast this girl's name to her parents?
Oh, yeah! Leave it to me!
Emma!
How can I ever thank you?
I'm glad your mom showed up.
Thank you, everyone.
Didn't I tell you to stay put?
I'm here to work, remember?
I'm sorry. The festival seemed so fun...
Thank you so much.
Those ornaments... You're royalty?!
From the House of Silva?
I-I'm so terribly sorry!
My daughter didn't offend
you in any way, did she?!
Sh-She's royalty?
She has silver hair... She must
belong to the House of Silva!
It's rude enough for any
peasant to even speak to her!
Yes, I am royalty.
We're said to have the best
magic in this kingdom.
And that's exactly why we should
extend a helping hand to everyone.
Being arrogant because
you think you're better
than everyone else and
looking down on others...
Only those with shallow hearts do that!
You can enjoy the festival too, Emma.
It doesn't matter if you're a royal,
an aristocrat, a commoner, or a peasant!
Everyone should have fun together!
You're so cool, miss!
What does Noelle mean to you?
Well...
I guess...
I like Noelle quite a bit.
Take that!
Whoo! Fireworks!
Huh? What's wrong?
Finally!
Come on, Noelle!
Tell him how you really feel!
Where...
Where the heck did that come from?!
Have you lost your mind?!
What the heck?!
That's hot!
Whoa...
That's royalty for you.
Is he okay?
Yeesh...
Asta, did you fly off in
consideration for my feelings?
Jeez... He's so dense, and she just
can't be honest with herself.
What was that?
I-I thought I was going to die...
Festival
I've wanted to settle the score
with you for a long time.
Wh-What's going on?
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Hitman
Hitman.
My angel... No, my client, Marie...
As you requested, your big brother
is going to end that man's life.
The target is that doll.
We are hoomans.
Marie likes that thing a lot lately.
I'm going to bring it down.
With all my magical powers!
Mirror Magic...
Real Double! And then...
Reflect Refrain!
Hoomans... Hoomans...
Wha— We missed!
Hoomans...
Oh, this really short, buff
kid broke that gun earlier.
He's going to die!
I went on a d-date with you, so
you'd better be grateful, Stupidsta!
Wait, who said it was a date?! I'm a royal!
Black Clover, Page 68:
"Battle to the Death?! Yami VS Jack."
Page 68
Battle to the Death?! Yami VS Jack
Uh, what are you doing, Captain?