It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
The Star Festival, held in the
royal capital, had begun.
The Star Festival was held
to acknowledge the Magic
Knights Squads' achievements
and announce who had received the most
stars from the Wizard King that year.
Kahono! Kiato!
Asta had invited Kahono and Kiato from
the Underwater Temple to the festival
and used the Queen of
Witches' secret witch spells
to heal Kahono's injured throat
and Kiato's injured leg.
Asta and the others enjoyed
the festival, but...
Hey, Asta.
What does Noelle mean to you?
Huh?
What does she mean to me?
I guess...
I like Noelle quite a bit.
Where...
Where the heck did that come from?!
Have you lost your mind?!
What the heck?!
Festival
Asta ended up stumbling upon
Yami and Captain Jack the Ripper
of the Green Praying Mantises facing
off in a rather heated situation.
Battle to the Death?!
Yami VS Jack
Hey, mister! Can I get another drink?
Come one, come all!
Behold the song and dance
of the Underwater Temple!
Such a beautiful song!
And that boy dances so elegantly.
Kahono can sing again,
and Kiato can dance again.
That's so wonderful.
Don't you think so, Stupidsta?
Wh-Who the heck are you? I'm royalty!
I'm terribly sorry.
I forgot. I blasted him away.
How dare he fly off somewhere?
Stupid Stupidsta.
Stupidsta, where did you go? Hey!
How about some food, missy?
Maybe later.
Want to take a shot or two, miss?
Would you like to try one, miss?
Maybe...
Gulp.
...later.
I guess common food is okay.
This isn't bad at all.
Anyway, I wonder where Stupidsta flew off to.
Mana seems to be concentrating over there...
How about some squid?
Raging Bull
Everyone, come try out Captain Yami's
yummy—I mean, Yami—grilled squid!
Bah-ha! Bah-ha! Bah-ha!
Captain Jack's meat dishes are the best!
You only need one bite to feel satisfied!
It's piping hot! Your mouth can't help
but go bah-ha, bah-ha, bah-ha!
You mean they'll be going
aph, aph, aphew! That's hot!
Your heart and stomach will
feel phat and content!
No shit.
Festival
Raging Bull
What the hell, kid?
Where are all our customers?
If you don't get us some customers, I'll kill you.
Y-Yes, sir! Mister,
how about a squidtastic squid?
Whaddya say?
Hey, don't run away!
Come on! At least try one!
Newbie! If you don't get me more
customers, I'm gonna slice you up.
B-Bah-ha?! I promise he's
not scary, everyone!
Please buy some, bah-ha!
Come on, you two! Bring in some customers!
Got it.
Please, buy one!
Please! Please buy some, bah-ha!
Come on, please? Come buy one!
Buy some!
Please!
Sir? They won't even look at me.
The unpopular captain of the Black Bulls
and our captain are right
next to each other.
There's no way anyone's gonna buy from us.
Bah-ha, bah-ha...
Phati, phati...
Aph, aph...
What was that?
This is delicious! Super delicious!
Please buy some!
I promise it's not poisoned!
I was wondering why mana was concentrating
over here. What are you doing?
Help me out, Noelle!
Huh? Oh...
Guess you're here, too, Bah-ha.
Specialty
Grilled Squid
Young lady from the Black Bulls...
My name is not "Bah-ha," it's Sekke.
I'm Sekke Bronzazza, bah-ha!
Oh. Whatever.
So, what are you and Bah...
er, Sekke, doing, Asta?
Captain Yami and...
...Captain Jack...
I've wanted to settle the score
with you for a long time.
Your food stall and my food stall...
Let's see who sells the most!
It's on!
Bring it! There's no way I'm gonna lose!
You grandpa-faced fisherman!
If you lose, I'll flay you alive!
Bring it on, you giant string bean!
If you lose, I'll make you wipe my ass!
It's on! I ain't gonna lose!
No matter what...
...I'm gonna win!
Grilled Squid
Er...
Say what?
That's why we got roped
into bringing customers in.
But neither stall has sold anything.
How about some grilled purple
snakes I just caught over there?
That sounds super tast—I'm kidding!
It sounds gross!
Stop getting distracted by other stalls.
But purple snakes...
My rainbow squids...
I risked my life catching them in
a storm off the coast of Raquey,
using my years of fishing experience!
They're the finest you can get!
Don't you dare compare them to some snakes!
I'm sorry!
If I lose to Jack, it'll be all your fault.
H-How about some grilled squid?!
They were caught fresh of the coast of
Raquey! They're the finest you can get!
They're delicious, just like
the tatoes from Hage Village!
What are you trying to do? Ruin my business?
No!
So it is your fault that I
haven't sold a single one yet!
Squid... Squid, squid... Squid...
Stupidsta!
Tch. You're friggin' worthless.
Mine were useless, too.
We don't have time to wait and
see who can get better sales.
Imagine that. I was just
thinking the same thing.
Why don't we...
...fight each other with our own abilities!
Dead or alive!
Wait, what?
Look that way!
Huh?
Dead or alive!
Look that way!
What is this?
Take that!
Next!
We're not getting anywhere.
Guess we need to step it up a notch!
If I actually get serious, you're gonna die.
That's my line!
Let's change locations. We're gonna
end up causing a disturbance here.
We'll be going now.
Excuse us!
Asta! Stupidsta!
Noelle.
Get a hold of yourself! Stupidsta!
Noelle!
What?
Get Finral's ass down here.
Hey, this is...
We won't bother anyone here.
I'm on another level today...
Just like this grilled squid!
And I'll slice you in half,
just like that grilled squid!
Why did I have to come, too?
This is also pretty tasty.
Captain Jack can slice a
giant mountain in bah-half!
You may be the Captain of the Black Bulls,
but you're no match for Captain Jack!
Bah-ha! Bah-ha! Bah-haha!
What's got Bah-ha so worked up?
That festival had the girls so laid-back
that my flirting almost worked.
Man...
Yami and Jack having a
no-holds-barred battle...
I wonder what kind of
powerful spells I'll see.
I can't wait!
You ready for this, Jack the Ripper?
That's my line! Yami Sukehiro,
my blades are tingling!
They can't wait to slice and dice you!
Last time, you were almost dead, so slicing
you up wouldn't have been worth it.
Who was almost dead, now?
You, you dumbass!
You let those Eye of the Midnight Sun
bastards beat the shit out of you!
I was only acting like they
beat the shit out of me.
I was going to turn things around
right when you guys showed up.
Whatever. Looks like you're
getting worked up, Yami.
You'll actually be worth slicing up today!
Let's see who's gonna be slicing up who!
Well, I see they're as terrifying as ever.
Holy crap! I can feel their electrifying
ki all the way over here!
Why are all the Magic Knights
Squad Captains so weird?
Let's see what kind of battle unfolds!
Again, why are you so worked up?
Bah-ha!
Dark Magic: Dark Cloaked Black Blade!
Nice!
Severing Magic: Death Scythe!
Wow...
Hmph. That's nothing special.
If Captain Yami got serious—
You're amazing, Captain Jack! Bah-hahaha!
Hey, watch it, damn it!
He's okay!
Captain Yami's Lightless Blade
can draw out the enemy's spell!
So that's how he avoided that attack.
You're so awesome, Captain Yami!
Yami and Jack, both of your spells
are amazing! Well done, boys!
I guess I'll start this next round.
I'll show you an extra-special spell.
Extra-special?
I awakened a new spell during the
mission to the Underwater Temple.
My own talent scares me sometimes.
All right, bring it on!
A new spell?
Wait, don't tell me...
Bah-ha, bah-ha?
He's going to use that on Captain Jack?
Uh, Finral, shouldn't we be
stopping Captain Yami now?
Uh, what?
This is dangerous, even for Captain Jack.
Yeah! Stop them!
What if something happens to one of
the Magic Knights Squad Captains?
What do you expect me to do?
If one of them goes down, the other's
going to be held responsible.
And if that happens, the forces protecting
the Clover Kingdom will be weakened!
Then what do you think will happen?
What will happen?
The Eye of the Midnight Sun or
the Diamond Kingdom might attack!
If you don't stop them now,
it'll be all your fault!
It's my fault?!
It's all your fault! Bah-haha!
Seriously, who the hell are you?
Hurry up and stop them.
I'm royalty, remember?
What does that have to do
with anything right now?!
But I probably should try to stop them.
Either of them getting
defeated would be bad news.
If he actually uses Dimension Slash in here,
who knows if the rest of
this cave will even hold up?
And then...
Everyone will be in danger.
Since I have the most seniority here,
I need to stop them!
Yami! Stop! That's enough!
Finral!
Stay out of my way!
He's so useless.
Seriously, talk about pathetic.
What is your deal?
Here I come!
Come at me!
Dark Magic: Dark Cloaked...
Severing Magic...
Death Scy—
Dimension—
Time Binding Magic: Chrono Stasis!
I would've loved to have
seen Dimension Slash,
but as you mentioned, if something were to
happen to any of the Magic Knights Captains,
we'd be at a disadvantage.
Not to mention, this cave would
probably collapse from the impact.
I'll just have to look forward to
seeing Dimension Slash later.
Wizard King! Where are you slacking off now?!
Hey there, Marx.
Something really fun was happening.
Please stop fooling around and hurry back!
It's time for the meeting
concerning the Star Festival's
announcement of how many
stars each squad has earned!
Oh, is it?
Don't "Oh, is it?" me!
The king is waiting for you, too!
Please return right now!
You're always so angry, Marx.
Your blood pressure's going to go sky-high.
And whose fault is that?!
Well, you heard him.
I'm going to head back now.
I'll see you again later.
But before that, I should probably make
sure they don't fight again after I leave.
Abra and cadabra.
All done.
Dimension Slash!
Death Scythe!
Huh?
What happened?
Bah-ha?
What the hell happened to your pants, man?
Look who's talking!
Damn. I don't feel like fighting anymore.
Don't make me laugh. Now I don't
feel like slicing you up anymore.
Are they done now?
Thank goodness. I won't be
held responsible for this now.
Jeez! What were you going to do
if something serious happened?
You dumbass. Like this jackass
would go down that easily.
Right...
That's not the issue here!
They say the more you fight,
the closer you are.
But make sure you don't
fight too much, bah-ha.
Seriously, who do you think you are?
This isn't half bad.
Your meat dish isn't that bad, either.
Right? Now, I'll make you some dessert.
Hey, go get that one thing!
Bah-ha!
Ice
Now hold it down.
Bah-ha! So cold...
Raging Bull
Ice
Not bad.
Here ya go.
Thanks.
The more you fight, the closer you are, huh?
Maybe Sekke is right.
S-Stupidsta...
I-I don't mind f-fighting
with you once in a while.
S-Sure?
Well, I'll be going now.
I'm gonna go join everyone else.
Let's call it a draw for today.
That makes it 53 wins,
0 losses, and 34 draws for me.
Huh? What the hell are you talking about?
You mean it's my 98 wins,
0 losses, and 1 draw.
You must be going senile.
It's my 156 wins and 0 losses.
I'm the one with 567 victories here.
Oh?
You want a piece of me?!
I've been wanting to settle the
score with you for a long time now.
Guess tonight's the night.
You giant string bean!
You grandpa-faced fisherman!
Again?! Asta, stop them!
Me?!
Well, who else is there?
You go do it!
But I'm royalty!
Now, now, let's just—
Shut up!
See? There's no one else.
Okay, fine...
Raging Bull
U-Um, Captain Yami, Captain Jack...
Come on, we're at this super fun
festival, so let's not fight.
Let's just all get along, okay? 'Kay?
You're in my way.
Stay out of my way!
Stupidsta!
Everyone, thanks for your support!
We're going to become the biggest
idols in the Clover Kingdom someday!
Idols that can sing, dance, and use magic!
I'm Kahono!
And I'm Kiato!
We look forward to your support!
We look forward to plenty of yuls, too!
Oh, no!
Lots and lots!
Asta?
You're late, Finral. Where were you?
I bet you asked a girl out
again just to get rejected.
I mean, that happened too, but...
A few other things happened, too.
Other things?
I'm pretty exhausted.
Oh, come on. The festival just started.
Oh, thanks.
Go on. Drink up! Cheers!
Cheers.
I know.
Captain Yami must've summoned
you to use your spatial magic.
That must've been rough.
Thanks for all you do.
Cheers.
Y-You okay?
Captain Yami, I flew super far!
He's actually okay.
He's so tough.
Where the heck am I?
I need to get back to everyone else.
Wow, she's so beautiful.
She's so elegant.
Is she from some wealthy family?
Hey, go talk to her, man.
No way! How could I?
She is super pretty. I bet
Finral would love her.
But I feel like I've seen her before.
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Grilled Squid
Grilled Squid.
Today, I'll show you how to make
some delicious grilled squid.
Yeah!
It's super simple. Anyone can do it.
You say that,
but you're not going to cheat and use
magic like that one chef did, are you?
Just watch.
First, you pull out its insides
and cut slits into it.
Those are actually real instructions!
Then you season it with sugar,
salt, mirin, and ginger.
Still real instructions!
Then, you grill it.
This is normal cooking!
All done.
Yummy!
There you go. Simple grilled squid
that anyone can make.
There's no punchline this time.
Festivals are the best!
Girls let their guard down a little, too!
Okay, I'm gonna get me a girl!
Black Clover, Page 69:
"The Briar Maiden's Melancholy."
Page 69
The Briar Maiden's Melancholy
Whoa! Captain Charlotte has makeup on!
She's even more beautiful than usual!