It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
The Wizard King gives stars
to the Magic Knights Squads
for every achievement they accomplish.
The squads compete to obtain the most stars.
The Star Festival is where the
number of stars each squad
has accumulated in that year
is announced to the public.
While the usually peaceful
Star Festival was going on,
Yami and the captain of the
Green Praying Mantises, Jack the Ripper,
decide to battle it out
over something insignificant.
Abra and cadabra.
Their issues were resolved by
an unexpected turn of events,
and everyone returned to the Star Festival.
The Briar Maiden's Melancholy
Wow, she's so beautiful.
She's so elegant.
Is she from some wealthy family?
Hey, go talk to her, man.
No way! How could I?
She is super pretty. I bet
Finral would love her.
Truly exquisite. I've decided.
You will be my companion tonight.
That's Baron Balmain from
the House of Bamilton.
First, let us enjoy this festival together.
Come with me.
Ignoring me, are you? You've got some nerve!
Just who do you think I am? I'm—
Hey!
Huh?
That would be my line.
We don't get to enjoy festivals
like this every day,
Blue Rose Knights Squad, 3rd Class Intermediate Magic Knight
Sol Marron
so let's doll ourselves up a bit, er...
Who do you think I am?
This magic...
She's the captain of the Blue Rose Knights!
Blue Rose Knights Captain
Charlotte Roselei
Whatcha doin', Sis?
Call me "Captain."
You got it, Sis!
Come with you?
Were you planning to use
me as some accessory?
And without my consent, no less.
What were you thinking?
The House of Bamilton? I belong
to the House of Roselei.
Did you think you could approach me
so casually because I'm a woman?
Is there a single way in
which you are superior to me?
Honestly... where did Asta run off to now?
Well, he did take quite a flight.
I don't think I've ever seen so many people.
Feel free to take my hand at
any time so you don't get lost.
What's going on?
What's the matter? Use your magic
to do something about my briars.
Woohoo! You go, Sis! You're as cool as ever!
Call me "Captain."
You got it, Sis!
Wait, wait, wait!
You're supposed to stop her!
That guy's seriously gonna die!
Is something wrong? Did you find Asta?
Looks like some drunk is
dancing naked over there.
It's nothing for royalty to see.
H-H-Hey!
Hi there.
You're...
The little runt from the
distinguished service ceremony!
Who are you callin' a runt?!
I mean, you're definitely a little runt.
Shut up, you giant woman!
Huh? What was that, you little mouse?
You want me to stomp you?
Please don't!
More importantly, Sis!
Call me "Captain."
You got it, Sis!
I found this super awesome dress!
What I have on right now is fine.
I know you'll look great in it, Sis!
Come on. Let's go!
H-Hey!
Stop it, Sol.
Come on, don't be like that!
Woohoo! Your skin is as
lovely and pale as ever!
It's smoother than marble!
Hey, stop that!
Drinking at a festival is
on a whole 'nother level!
Yeah! Eating at a festival makes the
food taste even more delicious, la!
S-So many people!
I'm so embarrassed! Nom...
Oh, wow. It really is delicious.
I wanted to come with Marie.
It tastes special somehow.
Maybe it's because we're at a festival.
Oh, it must be because I'm
with you, Big Brother!
Festivals get me so pumped up!
The inner man in me is raring to get out!
I know, right? Wanna fight?
Hell no!
Festivals...
By being able to enjoy a different environment
than we ordinarily experience in our lives,
our bonds become even stronger...
It's such a special day.
An unforgettable page in
our book of memories...
I'm zero for five today.
I'm doing worse than usual.
Sniffity, sniffity, sniff-sniff...
I smell an extremely beautiful lady.
Pardon me!
What's his problem? There are plenty
of pretty girls right here.
Talk about rude!
More importantly,
what's taking the captain so long?
You look awesome, Sis!
That helmet you always wear looks
great on you, but so does this!
A goddess... I'm truly in the
presence of a goddess right now.
Wow, she's super pretty!
Quiet down, men. This isn't a show!
Huh?
The only ones allowed to get all excited
about Sis's beauty are the Blue Rose Knights!
What?!
Still, I can't let the other
captains see me like this.
Especially not him...
Seems pretty rowdy over here.
Y'all enjoying the festival?
Raging Bull
Festival
Hey, kid. You still in one piece?
Hey, come on! I almost got hurt!
Huh? Like that's enough to hurt you.
Y-Y-Yami!
Why in the world did he have to show up?
You're such a goddess, Sis!
No... I cannot lose my
composure in front of Sol.
Calm down... Calm down, me.
Just wait. He might not even
recognize me in this dress.
Hey, it's Her Cold and Prickly Majesty.
Badump!
What the hell's with the sparkly outfit?!
Breathe. Stay calm... Stay calm.
And what about you? What are those
strange clothes you're wearing?
Festival
Raging Bull
Especially your lower half!
What in the world is that?!
Hey! You're the dirtiest,
macho-est guy out there!
The Captain of the Black Bulls!
Huh? What's your problem?
Looks like you aren't training your
squad members properly, rose girl.
Shut up! Don't you dare come any closer
to Sis dressed in that weird outfit!
Sol, stop...
There you are, Captain! What are you doing?
Come drink with me!
Oh. Hey, Vanessa.
Who's this woman?
I'm not sure why... but I feel like
I can't afford to lose to her.
She's the Captain of the Blue Rose Knights.
Huh?
This woman... She's so incredibly
friendly with Yami.
Is she a member of the Black Bulls?
I'm so jealous!
Who do you think you are, glaring at Sis
like that? You're just a Black Bull!
I'm not glaring!
A Black Bull couldn't beat Sis
in a billion, trillion years!
A billion, trillion years, eh? Ouch.
I can't let the Blue Rose Knights
keep talking to us like that!
I can't embarrass Captain Yami any further.
Hey, you!
I challenge you!
Ridiculous. There's little time left before
our achievements are announced.
Why would anyone bother to—
Huh?! There's no way Sis would lose!
Let's do this, Sis!
You're actually doing it?!
What kind of battle shall it be?
Just so you know, I'm more powerful
now than I've ever been before!
You fool.
Do you have any idea who you're talking to?
I'm the Captain of the Blue Rose Knights.
Th-This is turning into a huge mess!
What are we gonna do, Captain?
Hell if I know.
Now, now, now, now, my lovely ladies...
We're at a festival, so why
don't we all just get along?
You're a man. Stay out of this!
Huh?
You only know how to flirt
with girls. Shut up.
So mean.
Then how about this?
It's perfect for a festival night!
A battle befitting two gorgeous ladies!
A cosplay contest!
You can't be serious.
What? Scared of losing?
Of course not! There's nothing in this
world that Sis can't look good in!
Things seem rather lively over there.
Well, we are at a festival.
There doesn't seem to be any trouble,
so I'm sure it's fine.
Let us head to where they will announce
the achievements. We mustn't be late.
Right.
The announcement of our achievements...
I'm so nervous.
There's nothing to be nervous about.
We will undoubtedly come out on top.
Right. But I think the Black Bulls
worked rather hard, too.
Indeed, they might have.
Actually, I know they have.
We must especially keep an eye
on all of Asta's achievements.
B-But he's still just a Black Bull!
They're full of problems,
regardless of their achievements!
They are no match for us, the Golden Dawn!
Right, Yuno?
The Black Bulls are the lowest
of the low. Them, beat us?
You can't be serious.
First up, we have the Captain of the
Blue Rose Knights, Charlotte Roselei!
The cosplay she chose is...
A sexy little witchie!
Talk about super rare! Yee-haw!
We chose the same outfit as that one witch
just to show how much better Sis is!
The difference is super clear!
Sexy little witchie Sis is awesome!
Of course. There's no way
I'd lose to that woman.
Also, call me "Captain."
Raging Bull
I-I'm so embarrassed!
Why must I wear something like this?!
Don't look! Don't look at me, Yami!
Actually, maybe there's a part
of me that wants you to look.
Maybe he'd be a little
friendlier to me if I dressed
like that girl who's way
too friendly with him.
But it's too embarrassing! Don't look!
Actually, look at me!
The Blue Rose Knights' captain
looks pretty good in that, too.
This is pretty hilarious.
Next up, we have a member of the
Black Bulls, Vanessa Enoteca!
The cosplay she chose is...
No one saw this coming!
She's dressed as a sister of the cloth!
Look at her slay!
Apparently, you don't know
anything about guys.
Guys like this sort of contrast.
She's usually exposing so much
that this is actually sexy, too!
May God watch over you all.
Miz Vanessa is glowing more than usual!
This is pretty hilarious.
All right, everyone! Send your magic
powers to the girl you like best!
I'm definitely voting for the
sexy little witchie, Charlotte!
The sister's good, too, though!
Man, I don't know which to choose!
And let's stop right there!
As for the results...
Unbelievable! They received
the same amount of points!
It's a draw!
What?!
Hmph. This doesn't matter anyway.
A draw? After I bothered to dress like this?
I've shamed the House of Roselei.
But...
I wonder what Y-Yami thinks.
Does he see me in a different light now?
Then my embarrassment might be worth it.
There's no way Sis got a draw!
Let's settle this once and for all!
Bring it on!
All right! Round two will
be a swimsuit competition!
All right, you two, stri—
I think I kinda like this...
I mean... I-I'm kidding.
Anyone who agrees with him
will endure the same fate.
Our Clover Premium Beer uses ingredients
from right here in the Clover Kingdom!
It's rich and smooth, but you can
still taste some fruity undertones!
Try a sip!
C-Captain, you like a girl who
can hold her liquor, right?
Huh? Where'd that come from?
Badump, badump...
Well, I guess so.
Then we can drink together. Why?
R-Really?
Looks like I'm gonna win.
We're going to have a drinking contest next!
This is nonsense.
I've entertained you this long,
but that's enough.
They're going to announce
our achievements soon.
We're ready to go, Sis!
Let's bring her down and show
that insolent girl who's boss!
The rules are simple!
The winner will be decided by who
can drink the most booze in an hour!
The beer we'll be drinking is
this special Clover Premium.
One of the Clover Kingdom's best!
No chugging allowed, though!
We can't have any little ones copying us,
and we need to savor the flavor
out of respect to the brewers!
Why is this happening?
All right, let the games begin!
You got this, Sis!
I have no idea what's going on,
but you can do it, Miz Vanessa!
It appears that this woman
is a pretty heavy drinker.
This may be a difficult match.
Come at me anytime!
What?!
It looks like she already
drank herself under the table!
I'm not drunk at all!
I can't believe she proposed
this battle in that condition.
I'm still good to go.
I can win this!
S-Sis?!
Yo! She can't hold her liquor at all!
But that's another thing
that's so cute about her!
The hell are those two doing?
I lost my cool because this was over Yami.
What was I thinking?
A curse... I place a curse
upon the House of Roselei!
When your daughter turns eighteen,
the curse will activate.
It will engulf you all and trap
you within a cage of time!
Oh, how can this be, Charlotte?
If only we could figure out
how to break the spell.
Please don't cry, Mother and Father.
I'll become stronger. Stronger than anyone else!
And I will overcome this curse!
Apparently, she raised her rank again.
That newbie from the
Blue Rose Knights is so powerful!
Not to mention beautiful!
Lady Charlotte, please marry me.
No, marry me!
If you cannot defeat me,
you could never accept my curse.
I'm surrounded by weak men who are all talk.
I will overcome this myself!
The curse!
The curse upon the House
of Roselei has activated!
It's no use. We can't stop it!
It won't... stop...
At this rate, the town...
Curses! How pathetic... I'm so pathetic!
I'm so sorry... Mother and Father...
What the hell's the big idea, you jerk?
You flung the pasta soup
I was eating everywhere.
Yami Sukehiro? To think I'd let him see
me in such a disgraceful situation!
What a failure I am.
On missions, you're as cool as a cucumber
and always raring to go. So what gives?
I like tough girls.
But it probably wouldn't hurt to ask
someone for help once in a while.
Our Magic Knights Squads are full
of strong people you can rely on.
To have my heart stolen by a man...
That was the way to break the curse.
Oh, sweet. It's disappearing. Lucky for us.
He's such a barbarian.
He's so aggravating, and yet...
You can't finish it, can you?
Didn't I tell you not to push
yourself too much before?
A-An indirect ki—
Looks like we have another draw!
Well done! Well done, Sis!
Great job, Miz Vanessa!
Festival
What the hell was this battle,
besides a waste of time?
They're about to announce the
Magic Knights Squad achievements!
All the captains are gonna be there!
I hear that includes the new captains of
the Crimson Lion Kings and the Purple Orcas!
I wonder what they're like!
Uh... All the captains?
Raging Bull
Festival
We're late.
Crap. What are we gonna do?
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Charlotte's
Seven Transformations
Charlotte's Seven Transformations.
The sexy little witchie
getup just isn't enough!
I wanna see Sis dressed
up as all kinds of things!
1. Sister Charlotte
Transformation number one! Sister Charlotte!
She's going to save us all!
Transformation number two! Bride Charlotte!
2. Bride Charlotte
Marry me, Sis!
Transformation number three!
Samurai Charlotte!
3. Samurai Charlotte
Slay me!
Transformation number four!
Schoolteacher Charlotte!
4. Schoolteacher Charlotte
Teach me all the things!
5. Policewoman Charlotte
Transformation number five!
Policewoman Charlotte!
Arrest me!
Transformation number six!
Kunoichi Charlotte, nin!
6. Kunoichi Charlotte
Sneak up on me!
I don't have time for this! Boom!
I thought there were seven transformations.
They're finally going to announce
the Magic Knights Squad achievements.
You can look forward to
the Black Bulls' results this year.
I know because I've watched
everything you've done without blinking.
Black Clover, Page 70: "Two New Stars."
Page 70
Two New Stars
We're friends forever.