It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
The fifth round of the Royal Knights
Selection Exam finally concluded.
Crystal magic stoppage confirmed.
B Team wins!
Fully bloom!
Full bloom!
C Team wins!
Flame Magic: Spiral Flames!
Crystal destroyed! E Team wins!
The crystal's been destroyed. G Team wins!
Picture Magic: Twin Storms of Fire and Water!
Sandstone Magic: Rock Storm!
The crystal has been destroyed.
I Team wins!
You guys were pretty good.
But I haven't quite managed
the ultimate painting yet.
The sixth round was about to begin.
It's finally our turn! I can't wait!
Make sure you don't go
running off on your own.
Let's hit 'em with our best performances!
Yeah!
And now, for the sixth round of stage one!
And... begin!
Bad Blood
Things are getting pretty intense.
Both teams are concentrating
their attacks at the center
of the battlefield for a magic slugfest.
Steel Creation Magic: Full Metal Fortress!
Take this!
His spell changed shape! That's awesome!
He added a page to his grimoire
and evolved the spell.
Lightning Magic: Thunderbolt Destruction!
How is his spell so destructive?
As I thought... This isn't a junior-level fight.
Luck and I have done tons of
missions over the last few months,
and we've gotten tougher every time!
Ain't no way we're still junior-level!
He's always had intermediate skills,
but apparently, he's gotten stronger.
But that goes for me, too.
Following Asta's example, I trained
my magic, my body, and my spirit!
Even if my hard work may betray me...
I will not betray my hard work!
Steel Creation Magic: Blazing Spiral Lance!
Way to go, four-eyes!
Fantastic, Klaus!
I guess you're not just some four-eyes
who's too serious and worries too much!
Nice! After this fight is over,
you should fight me!
Don't be stupid! Concentrate on this match!
Here he comes... Rob Vitesse.
He's left the crystal behind him.
We'll bust through our three opponents
and destroy the crystal in a single rush!
You got it!
You know... You two are pretty good.
Wing Magic...
She's actually flying!
Angel Flapping!
That's an attack for the enemy...
Go, Luck!
And a tailwind for my allies!
This is so much fun!
All right! Break through!
In the end,
it's individual power differences
that separate victory and defeat.
My spell didn't even faze him.
Not good... Crazy boy!
More...
He's fast.
Let's play some more!
In a single blow?!
The crystal has been destroyed. K Team wins!
Yes!
They did it!
Yay, yay...
Man, that was so much fun.
Luck! Y-You actually...
Boom, boom! You two are fantastic!
Yay!
Luck!
That bastard! You're getting
way too damn strong!
Our next opponent...
...seems even more fun.
...seems like they'll help me make
an even better picture!
Next up, the eighth and
final round of stage one...
O Team and P Team, step forward.
Which means it's finally...
La!
...time for Yuno and Noelle's team!
Finally, it's our turn.
After we're done here,
you're going on a date with me!
Whatever.
The other guy....
Let's... do our best.
The Green Praying Mantises 4th Class Senior Magic Knight
En Ringard
Everything will be okay
if we work together.
Are you okay?!
Let's win... no matter what.
Hey, is he going to be okay?
No idea.
And I heard that you grew up with Stupidsta.
I hope you're not as reckless as he is, too.
Look who's talking. You can't
control your magic well, can you?
It looked like it took all
you had to maintain
your Mana Skin at the volcano.
Can you actually fight?
Huh?! I'm royalty!
Can you actually think and fight, you violent
peasant who's Asta's childhood friend?!
What a noisy woman.
That wasn't even an argument.
That lame comeback...
Is Asta rubbing off on you?
What?! Why would I ever
be influenced by him?!
See?! You're just like Shtupidshta!
Calm down. Guess I was right.
I'm perfectly calm!
Come on, you two, grow up.
Learn to get along already.
I think you might be the
cause of this, Asta.
Who cares about you, Asta?!
More importantly... Why don't
we come up with a plan?
Who said you could touch me?!
I see you're having a friendly chat.
It's as though you think you
actually have the upper hand.
The Black Bulls just happened to
make a good showing for once,
and you really believe it was thanks to you?
Solid...
You can't control your magic,
and despite being from the House of Silva,
you couldn't even make it
into the Silver Eagles.
And you're going to fight me?
You're back again, shaggy bangs?!
You failure!
Why can't you do the same things
as us when you're also royalty?
Trash! How dare you eat before me?
Please stop, Solid. Please give that back.
You can't protect what's important
to you because you're weak.
Please stop!
If you're upset, then get back at me.
If you can actually hit me
with your spells, I mean.
There you are, you thieving raccoon!
The fairy dust! The fairy dust!
Don't worry. You can do it.
We all worked so hard together.
We're basically family.
We know you way better than
that brother of yours.
Now, believe in your friends
and yourself! Believe yourself!
What's he mumbling about over there?
Maybe he's cursing that
annoying brother of hers.
Hey, what are you doing?
We're up. Let's go.
Yeah, yeah.
Make sure you do your
best to run away, Noelle.
Nyah, nyah, nyah!
Let's finally end this!
We will now begin the
eighth round of stage one.
O Team: Sandler, Dimitri, and Solid
versus P Team: En, Noelle, and Yuno.
Sandler
Dimitri
Solid
O Team
En   Noelle   Yuno
P Team
Begin!
You've got this, Yuno and Noelle!
Noelle! Show them what the
Black Bulls' women are made of!
Noelle! No need to hold back
just because he's your brother!
I'll attack. You two support me.
I'll attack.
No, me.
No, me!
Me.
Me!
Then I'll support...
This fast?
Wait, what?
This is an annoying way to do it, but it's
a shortcut with a simplified version
of that compound magic from before.
We'll end this instantly!
They haven't moved their crystal.
This isn't good. They closed the
distance to our crystal in one sprint.
Wind Magic: Crescent Moon Sickle!
Flame Magic: Combo Eruption!
Water Magic: Sea Dragon's Lair!
Look at you, learning a defense spell.
Sand Magic: Suppressing Sand Mass!
It's sucking up the water.
At this rate, we'll spend the
whole match on the defensive.
Hey! Who gave you permission
to cling to him like that?!
I'm probably the fastest on this team.
I'll take advantage of that
and go destroy their crystal.
While I'm doing that, you two
somehow protect our crystal.
Wait.
Let me go.
Please.
None of you will be going.
You go, Noelle!
She's been fighting alongside Asta.
I'm sure she can do it.
It's safer if I'm the one
protecting the crystal, anyway.
If I go...
Hold it right there, Noelle!
Solid's bound to come after me.
Don't go off on your own!
I'll be your opponent.
Hey, did you hear about the
newbie with the four-leaf clover?
He actually defeated one of the
Eight Shining Generals from Diamond!
Seriously? That's insane for his first year!
Not only that, but when he did it,
he told the vice captain that he was going
to become the Captain of the Golden Dawn.
Wow, that's wild!
I guess you have to be on a different
level when the Wind Spirit chooses you.
It looks like Captain Vangeance
has high hopes for him, too.
You're saying you're going to guard
the crystal while dealing with me?
That attitude is sheer insolence!
Please come at me with everything you've got.
Why you?
Several Years Ago
I wasn't expecting an ambush.
As I was running, I fell deep into this cave.
No one will be able to rescue me here.
This is the end.
Are you all right, Alecdora?
He looked just like
the figure in a painting
I saw when I was little.
The figure of a god.
I sensed you here.
There's nothing to worry about now.
Master Vangeance has some other
mysterious power besides magic.
A warm power that seems to connect
him to his squad members.
I swore that I'd devote my
grimoire to his service.
I worked hard to ensure that the
Golden Dawn remained the strongest squad.
We are an elite team of nobles
chosen by Master Vangeance.
So why...
Why is that peasant in our midst?
Not only that...
I can tell.
Master Vangeance always interacted with
all his squad members equally, and yet...
With that boy... With him...
Yuno...
He's called him by name five times today!
Even though he hasn't even
spoken to me once yet!
Why him?
Is it because of his four-leaf clover?
And that boy...
The one Master Vangeance
expects great things from
said that he would become captain himself.
He's mocking Master Vangeance!
Don't get full of yourself just because
you lucked into getting spirit magic!
Getting chosen by me was
part of Yuno's power!
That guy's pissing me off!
Let's get him, Yuno!
Step back, Bell.
Are you planning on fighting
without my powers?
You can't just keep defending, Noelle!
What are you doing?
You're ruining our strategy! Both of us
are supposed to hit the crystal together!
Shut up! Don't boss me around!
Fine. I'll join you,
and we'll defeat her in one—
Heya.
What the heck is this?!
Fungus Magic: Running Mister Mushroom.
I put some spores on you a little earlier.
I won't let you get in Noelle's way.
Too bad, Noelle.
Now that I've caught up with you,
you don't have a chance in hell
of scratching our crystal.
I wouldn't be too sure about that!
Relax. I's me, En.
This is Talking Mushroom.
It lets you hear my voice.
Who gave you permission to
stick this thing on me?!
Now, now. More importantly...
I heard Solid's remarks before the match.
A big brother should never say
such things to his little sister.
I have ten younger brothers and sisters.
They're the ones I'm fighting for.
Big brothers exist to protect the younger,
weaker siblings born after them.
And yet you've only said
hurtful things to her!
Get him, Noelle! Thrash your brother!
Don't just give him an ordinary thrashing!
Make sure he never defies you again!
R-Right... You sure are energetic.
Humans are animals, too! Once you put
them in their place, they won't turn on you.
Who's going to thrash whom, now?
There's no way a failure
like you could beat me!
That's right. I was weak.
You've always been strong, so you probably
can't understand how weak people feel.
At this point, I don't care if
you ever acknowledge me or not.
Because even greater people
have acknowledged me!
I used to be really scared
of your magic, Solid.
But now, it feels really flimsy.
Just keep running your mouth,
you embarrassment to the House of Silva!
Water Creation Magic: Slashing Sea Serpent!
How much more do you intend to insult me?
Sand Creation Magic:
Sand-Armored Heavy Guard!
This spell contains all the attack
and defense powers that I have!
You think you can stop it
without your spirit magic?!
I'm the one who will make
Master Vangeance's dream come true!
Wind Magic: Towering Tornado!
From the inside?
What was that? He activated his
spell inside his opponent's spell?
He can even do that? That's what
separates us from hot guys, dang it!
I don't know anything about
other people's dreams.
The only dreams I see are my own.
Impossible...
Impossible! You can't be serious!
This can't be real!
What's that spell?!
You can't be serious!
Noelle couldn't cast a spell like that!
Solid...
It's all right if I hit you, right?
Just go ahead and try it!
It won't hit me! There's no way
her spell could actually hit me!
You complete failure!
Sea Dragon's Roar!
Noelle!
She destroyed the crystal in a single blow!
The crystal has been destroyed! P Team wins!
I'm not weak anymore!
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Charmy's
Seven Transformations,
Part II
Charmy's Seven Transformations, Part II!
In response to the incredible
number of requests we got from
Charmy fans across the universe
saying the seven transformations
from last time just weren't enough,
we bring you its sequel!
Transformation one...
Christmas Tree Charmy.
La la la, la la la, la la la la laa...
Transformation two...
Noms
Charmy the Ninja!
La! Nin nin!
Transformation three...
Lion Dancer Charmy!
Transformation four...
Noms
Foot Soldier Charmy!
La!
Transformation five...
Samba Charmy!
And to finish things off...
Transformation six...
Buddha Charmy!
Right. So we have six again.
It's finally our turn.
I'll show you that I can fight properly!
Wh-Where are you looking, Stupidsta?!
Black Clover, Page 78: "Peasant Trap."
Page 78
Peasant Trap
On the name of the Black Bulls,
I'm going to win, no matter what!