Black Clover is about to begin.
In the semifinals of the Royal
Knights Selection Exam,
Asta's B Team and Langris's
G Team were battling it out.
One fierce blow after another...
One intense blow after another...
One battle to the death after another.
You people...
are not the Magic Knights
that my father dreamed of!
Meanwhile...
Charmy had left the venue in order
to find some ingredients so that
she could make something yummy
for Yuno and the Wizard King.
But she accidentally bit into
a hallucinogenic mushroom
and dreamed a strange dream.
La...
It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by Charmy the Demon.
But a single piece of meat saved them all.
It's so nummy, la. So yummy, la!
Munchy, munchy, munchy, munchy...
This is bliss, la!
Now that I'm full, I'm tired, la.
The bone's meat was able to sate the demon,
and it became a legend.
This is a really famous legend,
so you've all heard of it, right?
Petit Clover!
The Nightmarish Charmy SP!
Charmy's Seven Transformations
Charmy's Seven Transformations!
To all you Charmy Pappitson fans throughout
the world, no... the universe.
This is the moment you've been waiting for.
Today, we'll be answering all your requests
to see all those cute Charmy moments!
I've been waiting for this!
Transformation one... Wandering Charmy.
Munchy, munchy, munchy...
Transformation two...
Festival
Deet de-deet de-deet de-deet and go!
Happi Coat Charmy.
Transformation three...
Happy Birthday Charmy.
La!
Transformation four...
Lightning God Charmy.
La!
Transformation five...
Alien Charmy!
La, la, la, la, la, la...
And last but not least, transformation six...
Merlion Charmy!
Amazing!
So there aren't seven transformations?
The Mystery of the Grimoire
The Mystery of the Grimoire!
Wait, what? We're small now?
But man... Our grimoires
are totally different.
He ignored me?
A grimoire's size and thickness are
determined by its owner's style.
All right! Let's compare grimoires!
No.
That thing's
filthy
No fair!
You scared you're gonna lose?
Not a chance.
You're getting a big head just because
you're a little handsome, aren't you?
Not a chance.
Asta
VS
The Anti-Birds!
Asta vs. the Anti-Birds.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Hey! Get away from me! Buzz off!
Whoa! Hey! What the heck are you guys doing?!
Hey, Yuno! Ow, ow, ow! Help me!
Unbelievable...
Who's the Most Similar?
The winner is...
this bird.
What?!
Cringing at Salamander Bowls
Cringing at Salamander Bowls!
Gel Magic: Sticky Salamander!
Mander!
How adorable!
That's no big deal! Nero's much cuter.
If you put him in a bowl, he's delicious.
Ma?!
She's dangerous!
Looks nummy!
They're all dangerous!
Honor Me
Honor Me.
I am Noelle Silva, and I am a royal (ouzoku).
A bandit (sanzoku)?
Who are you calling a bandit?
I'm a royal.
A pirate (kaizoku)?
Who are you calling a pirate?
I'm a royal!
Family (Kazoku)?
Y-You idiot...
Look at Me!
Hey, Stupidsta. Look at me!
How do I look in this swimsuit?
You're all sparkly.
Isn't it heavy?
That'd probably work great
as part of a scarecrow.
You sort of look like a cow back in Hage...
Crab!
Wh-What are you staring at?!
But you told me to look!
Ugh, I'm so embarrassed...
Crab...
Voice Change
Voice Change.
M-Marie's coughing?!
Did you catch a cold?
It was pretty cold in the cave!
Are you all right, Marie?
Yeah, my throat's just a little sore.
Huh?
My voice sounds strange.
M-My angel Marie's voice
sounds like Captain Yami's!
More importantly, Brother,
go save Asta and the others!
Take my magic.
The old hag's voice is weird, too?
I may only be able to use
my magic one more time.
You, too, Finral?!
Wait, now my throat is...
Your voice is cute!
Marie's in Danger
Marie's in Danger.
All right, one, two, three!
Marie! Are you an angel?!
I can do anything when Marie's around!
But there are times where I must steel
my heart and decline Marie's wishes.
For example!
Brother, go back and save
Asta and the others!
No! Going back would put you in danger!
Brother! I want to eat some
hot, extra-cheesy doria!
No! Eating that would put
your tongue in danger!
You'll burn it.
Brother, doesn't lying
out in the sun feel nice?
No! If you're in the sun too long,
your skin will be in danger!
UV rays are a fearsome enemy!
Brother, show me a really cool spell!
No... Just kidding.
Marie, look at me.
Mirage Brigade!
You're amazing, Brother!
No... Now I'm... in danger.
Brother? Brother? Brother?
Double Gauche
Double Gauche.
Brother!
Spin me around like Asta did!
I'll... kill him!!
Spin... Marie around?!
Brother?!
I can't disappoint Marie...
I'll have to rely on my clone...
Mirror Magic: Real Double!
Spin her around...
I can't put Marie in danger.
That's true!
Then I'll just have to do it for her.
See? We're spinning!
You're not doing it right.
What's Mana?
Asta, do you know what mana is?
Yup!
Mana
It's written like this!
It's written with the same
character for "magic"!
Serious
These both mean "serious"!
Yes. Mana is a powerful energy
that exists in this world.
Yup! And everyone has it...
Except me!
Mages use up their mana to use magic.
That's why if they run out of it,
they might not be able to use
magic again until they recover.
Do you understand?
Yes!
What a lovely flower!
Perfect for giving to a girl.
Finral!
Wow, you're so aggressive!
I've never met a flower like you!
Crackling Magna Typhoon!
Hey, everyone! How are you doing?
We can't hear you! Put a little
more umph into it, damn it!
Today, we're going to show you how you can
do an easy Crackling Magna Typhoon at home.
First, have a string of lightning ready.
No one can do that!
Then, you wrap that lightning
string around Magna, like this.
It's electrocuting me!
Oh, you'll have to get your own Magna.
They can't do that, damn it!
Once you wrap the lightning
string around him,
you're going to spin him with
all your strength like a top.
Just like this! Take that!
And that's the Crackling Magna Typhoon.
Easy, right?
You're the only one who can do this, damn it!
Save me!
See you next time!
Real Life!
Magic Knights 24!
Real Life! Magic Knights 24!
It's chilly.
Right, Mister Yami!
It's hot!
I can't see anything.
Right, Mister Yami!
Get out.
Sekke's Bah-Ha Seminar
Sekke's Bah-Ha Seminar!
Bah-ha!
Bah-ha.
Wrong! It's...
Bah-ha!
Asta, you have yet to learn
the ways of the bah-ha.
Bah-ha!
The ways of the bah-ha?!
Sekke's Bah-ha Seminar! Part 2
Sekke's Bah-ha Seminar, Part 2!
We're still doing this?
But of course, Asta.
You haven't learned the
ways of bah-ha at all yet.
Your Shooting Star's pretty cool!
Ah, so you understand how grand it is!
That part in front is especially awesome!
Good. You are starting to
understand the ways of bah-ha!
I see. So that's bah-ha.
Yes. Starting today, you
have attained bah-ha!
Bah-hahaha! Bah-hahaha!
Bah-hahaha!
Men are so stupid.
My Magic
My Magic.
I'll show you my magic. It's hex magic.
In the next ten minutes...
you'll blink.
Let's Gordon!
Let's... Gordon...
I'm right behind you.
Magical Detective Charmy
Magical Detective Charmy!
Hello, I'm Magical Detective Charmy.
A terrible crime has been committed.
Someone has eaten my cake.
To uphold my honor, I will
capture this vile criminal!
You're the culprit.
The criminal was bold
enough to go into my room!
My bedroom!
You're the damn culprit.
But the criminal made a grave mistake.
Look at this handprint!
That's your handprint, isn't it?
The culprit is...
You, right?
It's me!
Duh.
Palace Three-Second Cooking
Palace Three-Second Cooking.
The time where I, the royal
head chef of Clover Kingdom,
introduce a three-second dish
that anyone can make.
Today, I'd like to make some
curry in three seconds.
I'm going to be using simple curry
roux procured at the market.
Next, you'll need carrots, onions, potatoes,
some mushrooms, and maybe some tomatoes.
If you try adding secret ingredients
like chocolate or coffee,
you can make an even more fragrant curry.
Now, then... You take
those ingredients, and...
Immediately chop them up using
your magic, and simmer them!
Make sure you use plenty of love and passion!
And it's finished. Wasn't that easy?
Time to eat!
So good!
And that concludes this episode of Palace
Three-Second Cooking, dishes anyone can make!
See you next time!
But that's impossible!
Birthday
Birthday.
I was able to get the wind
spirit to listen to me.
I shall name her Bell,
and today is Bell's birthday.
This cake is for you, Bell.
Yay!
Should we say you're one year old?
Happy birthday, Bell.
So pretty!
Make a wish and blow out the candles.
Um...
Huh? Where's the cake?
Not a chance...
It's Not as Though
I'm Actually Worried
It's Not as Though I'm Actually Worried.
Yes, he's brushing each tooth carefully,
with short strokes, ten to twenty times.
You mustn't scrub so roughly!
The bubbles are heading toward his eye!
Safe!
He's not kicking off his blanket
and getting too cold, is he?
You're so kind, it's almost creepy, Klaus.
Not happening...
Family
Family.
Oh, my...
So you decided that you would treat all of
the friends you encountered like family.
That's so wonderful.
Yeah.
Family... So basically, it's like this...
Big Brother Klaus!
That tickles!
Little Brother, allow me
to bestow these upon you.
Yay, glasses!
Thanks, Big Brother!
Not a chance...
Resilient
Resilient.
Flame Recovery Magic: Phoenix Robe.
Isn't it hot in there?
It is.
Isn't it heavy?
And...
My face itches, but I can't scratch it!
I Wonder Why
I Wonder Why.
What's the matter, Asta?
I wonder why Fana doesn't get burned
when Salamander is covered in flames.
Probably because it's magic?
I wonder why your clothes don't get
wet inside the Sea Dragon's Lair.
Because it's magic.
Why doesn't konbu seaweed
flavor the ocean like dashi?
Leave any food questions
to me, Professor Charmy!
The component that gives konbu dashi its
flavor, glutamic acid, lies within its cells.
Those cells have what's called
"selective permeability,"
which gives it the ability
to take in what's necessary
and get rid of everything it doesn't need.
The glutamic acid that creates the dashi
in konbu is necessary for its survival,
so it doesn't leave its cells while
it's still alive within the ocean!
But once it dies and is dried,
the cells break apart,
causing the glutamic acid to come out,
which turns into dashi.
There's no way Stupidsta's
going to understand any of that.
Captain Yami's Lecture
on Magic Knight Rankings
"Captain Yami's"... Wait, what is this?
"Magic Knight"... Ugh, I can't be bothered.
Wizard King
Grand Magic Knight
1st-5th Class Senior Magic Knight
1st-5th Class Intermediate Magic Knight
1st Class Junior Magic Knight
2nd Class Junior Magic Knight
Wizard King
Grand Magic Knight
1st-5th Class Senior Magic Knight
1st-5th Class Intermediate Magic Knight
1st Class Junior Magic Knight
2nd Class Junior Magic Knight
3rd Class Junior Magic Knight
4th Class Junior Magic Knight
5th Class Junior Magic Knight
So the most important is the Wizard King,
and then there's Grand Magic Knight...
This is too much work.
Why are you making a
Grand Magic Knight read this?
I'll kill you!
What?!
Grilled Squid
Grilled Squid.
Today, I'll show you how to make
some delicious grilled squid.
Yeah!
It's super simple. Anyone can do it.
You say that,
but you're not going to cheat and use
magic like that one chef did, are you?
Just watch.
First, you pull out its insides
and cut slits into it.
Those are actually real instructions!
Then you season it with sugar,
salt, mirin, and ginger.
Still real instructions!
Then, you grill it.
This is normal cooking!
All done.
Yummy!
There you go. Simple grilled squid
that anyone can make.
There's no punchline this time.
Charmy's
Seven Transformations,
Part II
Charmy's Seven Transformations, Part II!
In response to the incredible
number of requests we got from
Charmy fans across the universe
saying the seven transformations
from last time just weren't enough,
we bring you its sequel!
Transformation one...
Christmas Tree Charmy.
La la la, la la la, la la la la laa...
Transformation two...
Noms
Charmy the Ninja!
La! Nin nin!
Transformation three...
Lion Dancer Charmy!
Transformation four...
Noms
Foot Soldier Charmy!
La!
Transformation five...
Samba Charmy!
And to finish things off...
Transformation six...
Buddha Charmy!
Right. So we have six again.
Charmy's
Seven Transformations:
Special
Charmy's Seven Transformations: Special.
Special transformation one...
Buzz
Rhinoceros Beetle Charmy!
Special transformation two...
Boo boo be laa
La!
Sexy Charmy!
Special transformation three...
Masked Wrestler Charmy!
One, two, three, four, la!
La
Special transformation four...
Dominatrix Charmy!
Laan?
Special transformation five...
Etoile!
Ballerina Charmy!
The final special transformation six...
La, ho, ho, ho, ho...
Santa Charmy!
Yup. I see we went with six
transformations yet again.
La?
La!
My meal-saving prince...
Oh, it was just a dream.
I need to find more ingredients
and return to the venue.
Thus ended Charmy's nightmare.
I'm not exactly sure if it was
a nightmare, but it's over.
But Asta and the others
haven't finished fighting!
Their battle is becoming
more fierce and intense!
This dumbass is actually
putting all his trust in me.
Damn it.
You people...
are not the Magic Knights
that my father dreamed of!
The battle between Asta, Mimosa,
and the mage who calls himself Xerx
and Langris, Fragil, and
Sekke reaches its climax.
What will they see beyond
this battle to the death?
Next time on Black Clover, Page 83:
"Burn It Into You."
Page 83
Burn It Into You
Look forward to our show again next week!