It appeared as though humanity
would be destroyed by the demons.
But a single mage saved them all.
He was called the Wizard King,
and he became a legend.
Asta and the other Royal Knights
finally got to the
Eye of the Midnight Sun's hideout.
The fight to get to the
center of the hideout,
where their leader Licht
should be, had begun.
Around the same time, the Black Bulls'
hideout was being attacked.
The ones who attacked were
Rades, Sally, and Valtos
from the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
Gauche, Gordon, and Grey stepped
up to protect their hideout,
but the enemy's brutal attack
put them in a dire situation.
Don't give up, Gauche.
We're going to protect our hideout!
Now, I'm gonna finish you off!
Emergency! Emergency!
What's... going... on... here?
Crazy Magic Battle
What was that shaking?
Curse that Rades. He must be
doing something reckless again.
Who the hell are you?
Wh-What are you doing in our hideout?
He's creepy.
You're in no place to say that!
Answer me! Who the hell are you?!
Well... you... see... my... name... is...
He talks so slow...
What are you doing in our hideout?
Who are you?!
Well... you... see...
We didn't get to hear his name
because you talked to him again!
Not my problem!
Oh? I was pretty sure there were only
three people at the Black Bulls'
hideout right now.
Like it even matters.
We just need to kill anyone
who gets in our way!
Get him, Mikael Caesar!
Wha?!
He dodged it by rearranging the hideout?
What the hell was that, you jackass?!
Well... you... see... my... name... is...
We're starting from there again?!
So slow!
Charmy and Vanessa were
talking about some ghost
that rearranged our hideout...
Could he actually be that ghost?
You actually exist?
No... He's still alive.
No doubt about it. I can feel it.
How the hell can you tell?!
Also, when did I start to
understand what you're saying?!
I'm incredible!
His hair!
Wow...
Hey... little... friends.
You're... so... warm.
He keeps birds in his hair...
I want to be friends with them.
I don't know what kind of
ability that's supposed to be,
but if all you can do is shake up a
building, you can't attack or defend!
What?
What's going on?
What?! He blocked it?
Wow, that's awesome!
That thing looks like a hand!
Now's not the time to be happy!
The hideout...
He's got complete control over it.
Well done, my new friend.
You... need... to... stop...
attacking... now.
You talk too damn slow!
Talk faster, damn it!
This must be similar to that geezer's
game magic from the Underwater Temple.
Magic that utilizes
specific things and places.
The mage is usually very
familiar with the object
and has been pouring magic into it
regularly, making it immensely potent.
To use magic on such a huge scale...
How long has he been in our hideout?
The hideout is always changing around inside.
Does that mean he's always been there?!
Has his magic always...
Gordon... Grey... Gauche...
You...
You know us?
Of... course... I... do.
I... mean...
Because... I...
Are you the resident ghost that
everyone keeps talking about?
Well... I'm... not...
actually... a... ghost.
Heya, I'm Yami Sukehiro.
I just became a Magic Knights
Squad captain recently,
and I'm looking for a hideout.
This place is pretty sweet.
I like it. You mind if I have it?
I didn't mind giving it to him.
But I was born with a strange
illness that left me unable to move,
so I told him that.
I told him that I can only
live within this house,
that I can't interact with others very much,
and that, to top it off,
I unfortunately had to borrow
bits of magical power from
others in order to survive.
I told him all about my strange disease.
I'm unsure if I was abandoned or
they were in some kind of accident,
but my parents had disappeared a few
months before Yami showed up.
No one would bother to come and see
someone as troublesome as me.
That's how I felt.
I was going to die soon...
so I asked him to wait until then.
But then he said...
Yeah, no.
Huh?
It'd be creepy to have a
hideout that someone died in,
not to mention unlucky.
I need you to live.
But... I...
Basically, you just need a lively bunch
of people to live here, right?
You probably had no idea,
but I know about all of you.
but all of you kept me alive.
You probably had no idea about me,
but you're all my precious friends.
Well... you... see...
my... name... is...
Henry Legolant
Henry.
Henry?
That's a great name.
I'll make a Henry doll right away.
I don't give a damn who you are!
Destroy that rickety building!
I... won't... let... you... do... that.
I sense mana coming from here.
There it is.
Back then...
This is the magic stone that Heath
failed to retrieve from Saussy.
To think it was here...
And we finally have it.
What's going on?
Recombination Magic:
The Raging Black Bull
The Raging Black Bull.
I... won't... forgive...
I won't forgive anyone who tries to hurt
my precious friends.
He transformed the hideout?!
What the hell?!
Wow! How's he doing that?
I want him for a specimen!
Well done, my good friend!
What kind of magic does he have that
lets him move something that big?!
Well... it's not just... my magical powers.
It's the accumulation of all the magical power
that I've received from all of you,
and I'm using it all at once!
This is the mana power of
all of the Black Bulls!
Thanks to all of you,
even though I was bedridden,
I could start wandering around
the hideout a few years ago.
So you really were the "ghost"!
I still can't control my condition,
so if I get too close, I'll end up taking too
much magical power away from them.
So I can't go see them face-to-face.
But...
One of them got lost in the hideout
once and ended up in my room.
He found out about me.
And he told me that he
didn't have any magic,
so I didn't have to worry
about stealing any from him.
He'd come by my room sometimes to visit.
That's right...
I'm one of the Black Bulls, too.
Crap. You're sucking quite a bit of magical
power from me, so I'm gonna head out.
I don't see a way around it,
so you're a member of my squad now.
Huh?
One day, when you can move and
want to protect your buddies,
you can put that on.
When I want to protect... them?
Now is that time!
A Black Bulls' robe?
He's one of us?
Just because you're huge
doesn't mean you're any
match for my Number Zero!
Mana Corkscrew!
Wh-What?!
Mana Rocket Punch!
What the heck is this insane magic?!
What are you doing, Mikael Caesar?!
I know that's not all you've got!
Quit dawdling! Get your
ass back up and fight!
It's a pretty sturdy corpse
that doesn't feel any pain...
But if he takes another hit like that,
he might be crushed to bits.
He seems like he'd be
pretty fun to dissect.
I guess it wouldn't hurt to show
off the results of my research.
Dark Magic Item:
Magic Scorpion Necklace!
It only lasts about ten minutes...
But it multiplies my
magical power tenfold!
Gel Magic:
Big Ol' Sticky Salamander!
What?! That thing just became huge!
Here we go!
Go...
Raging Black Bull!
Mana Corkscrew!
Like punching gel is going
to accomplish anything.
Now it's my turn!
Hup!
Dark Magic Item: Special
Properties Plus Alpha!
Raise the gel's viscosity!
Whoa...
That weird magic of yours is interesting,
but so is that bizarre body of yours!
Now, what should I do next?
Good work, Sally! Get him!
That's not good! We need to back him up!
Right!
We're coming, my dear friend!
B-B-But how?!
Gordon's magic and mine are
horrible matches with that woman's!
Grey, use your magic to change
the attribute of her magic!
I-I can't! N-Not with
something that big!
You'll be fine! Hey, Grey!
Y-Yes?!
Look at me!
Mirror Magic: Mirror Brigade!
Sh-She multiplied?!
Wowie!
P-Please don't look at me!
Transformation Magic: Magic Conversion!
Gel to Plant!
N-Now poison should be super effective!
I'm counting on you,
Gordon!
Leave it to me!
Poison Curse Magic:
Dwelling of the Poison Cloud!
Good work!
That's enough, you pieces of trash!
Mikael Caesar!
Wha—
Don't you dare...
lay a finger on my friends!
What?!
All right!
D-D-Don't...
Don't screw with me!
I'm gonna have to show you
losers my trump card now!
Whoopsie... I'm feeling kinda dizzy.
Maybe I used a little too much mana.
Wait.
Valtos!
That guy again... Where the
hell was he this whole time?
I've obtained what we came here for.
Let's go.
Huh?! You can't be serious!
We can't go back like this!
We cannot let this mission fail,
no matter what.
I will not indulge your
selfishness this time.
Screw you, Black Bulls!
Just so we're clear,
I'm not running away!
Bye-bye. Let's play
together again sometime!
I'm gonna kill you next time,
so you better be ready!
All is as Master Licht wills it...
You can't be serious!
Come back here, you Eye of
the Midnight Sun bastards!
What the hell was all that?
What did they take from our hideout?!
I'm not sure, but we won!
We worked so well together in this fight.
It'll be a wonderful memory.
Th-Thank goodness we and
the hideout are all safe!
I'm not sure if we can call this "safe."
Hey! Can you turn the hideout back to normal?
Well... you... see...
If my Marie collection's
damaged, I'll kill you!
We... might... be... screwed.
What?!
Marie!
Could you tell me more about yourself?
I don't have enough energy
to transform anymore!
Master Licht...
Leader of the Eye of the Midnight Sun
Licht
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It appears you've obtained it.
Well, duh!
I have it here.
Excellent work.
What a beautiful day.
The laundry should be dry in no time.
You're right.
Something is...
What's the matter, Sister?
Oh, it's nothing.
Man, that golden weird
mask captain sure is late.
Now only two remain...
Until the monument of the Tree of Life
can bring forth our true power.
And then, the day that our dream
will come true shall be upon us.
Yes.
Finally!
We can finally kill
all those Magic Knights!
I can't wait!
Where are the remaining magic stones?
We'll go get those for you, too.
Leave it to us!
We await your orders.
Yes, thank you.
But I am the only one who
can obtain the last two.
Master Licht...
You should get some rest.
I shall go...
Myself.
The leader of the Eye of
the Midnight Sun, Licht,
continues the preparations
necessary to his ambitions...
while Asta and the others are
fighting to stop those ambitions!
Eye of the Midnight Sun, we've come...
...to get our revenge.
How dare you do that to my rival...
To my foolish little brother...
You shall pay dearly!
I will be the one to take your leader's head!
Looks like someone dangerous has shown up.
Licht is gone right now, too.
Guess I've gotta stop being lazy and just go.
Petit Clover
Petit Clover!
Around That Time, Valtos Was...
Back then...
This is the magic stone that
Heath failed to retrieve...
To think it was here...
And we finally have—
What's going on?
What?!
You can't be serious!
Wait.
Valtos!
I've obtained what we came here for.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Something bad is going to happen.
Next time on Black Clover, Page 91:
"Mereoleona vs. Raia the Disloyal."
Page 91
Mereoleona vs. Raia the Disloyal
What's about to happen to our kingdom?